-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
as ADP - O
a DET - O
comparative ADJ - O
experimental ADJ - O
model NOUN - O
of ADP - O
migraine NOUN - O
pain NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Hypertensive PROPN - O
Cardiogenic PROPN - O
Edema PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Intravenous PROPN - O
High PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Dose PROPN - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
a DET - O
Patient PROPN - O
Presenting PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Signs NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Respiratory PROPN - O
Failure NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
Case PROPN - O
Report PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Review PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Literature PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Different ADJ - O
Spasmolytic JJ - B-PERSON
Regimens NNS - I-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
vs IN - I-PERSON
Verapamil NNP - I-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
the DT - B-ORG
Incidence NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Radial NNP - I-ORG
Artery NNP - I-ORG
Occlusion NNP - I-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
increased VERB - O
ADP NNP - B-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
O NNP - I-ORG
ratio NOUN - O
at ADP - O
the DET - O
higher ADJ - O
concentration NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
250 CD - B-CARDINAL
μg PROPN - O
/ SYM - O
ml PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
after ADP - O
stimulation NOUN - O
via ADP - O
complex NOUN - O
I PRON - O
and CCONJ - O
at ADP - O
the DET - O
lower ADJ - O
concentration NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
25 CD - B-QUANTITY
μg NNP - I-QUANTITY
/ SYM - I-QUANTITY
ml NNP - I-QUANTITY
) PUNCT - O
via ADP - O
complex ADJ - O
II NNP - B-PRODUCT
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Iloprost PROPN - O
Improve PROPN - O
Mitochondrial PROPN - O
Function PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Colon NOUN - O
Homogenate PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
instrument NOUN - O
used VERB - O
was VERB - O
the DET - O
modified ADJ - O
Sublingual NNP - B-NORP
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
Interview NNP - B-PERSON
Schedule NN - I-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
or CCONJ - O
glyceryl NOUN - O
trinitrate NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
GTN NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
long ADV - O
considered VERB - O
an DET - O
endothelium NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
independent ADJ - O
vasodilator NOUN - O
because ADP - O
GTN NNP - B-ORG
vasodilation NOUN - O
is VERB - O
intact ADJ - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
absence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
endothelium NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
presence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
endothelial ADJ - O
dysfunction NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
ointment NOUN - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
shown VERB - O
to PART - O
reduce VERB - O
the DET - O
incidence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
mastectomy NOUN - O
flap NOUN - O
necrosis NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
randomized VERB - O
controlled VERB - O
study NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
using VERB - O
45 CD - B-CARDINAL
g NOUN - O
per ADP - O
breast NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
treating VERB - O
one NUM - O
side NOUN - O
only ADV - O
in ADP - O
bilateral ADJ - O
cases NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Safety PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Effectiveness PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Field PROPN - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
Patients PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Suspected PROPN - O
ST PROPN - O
Elevation PROPN - O
Myocardial PROPN - O
Infarction PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
ointment NOUN - O
is VERB - O
commercially ADV - O
available ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
it PRON - O
has VERB - O
less ADV - O
systemic ADJ - O
side NOUN - O
effects NOUN - O
than ADP - O
other ADJ - O
topical ADJ - O
formulations NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
Ointment NNP - I-ORG
for IN - I-ORG
Reducing VBG - I-ORG
the DT - I-ORG
Rate NN - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Mastectomy NNP - I-ORG
Flap NNP - I-ORG
Necrosis NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Immediate NNP - B-ORG
Implant NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Based VBN - I-ORG
Breast NNP - I-ORG
Reconstruction NNP - I-ORG
: : - I-ORG
Correction NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Previously ADV - O
we PRON - O
have VERB - O
shown VERB - O
that ADP - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
antibiotic ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
Nitroglycerine NNP - B-ORG
+ CCONJ - O
Citrate PROPN - O
+ CCONJ - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
NiCE NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O

Shareholder NN - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NN - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
The DT - B-ORG
Unversity NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: : - I-ORG
Shareholder NN - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
inventor NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
to ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-ORG
Anti JJ - I-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Infective NNP - I-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
LLC NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Licensing NNP - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Lock PROPN - O
Solution NOUN - O
Is VERB - O
Highly ADV - O
Effective ADJ - O
in ADP - O
Eradicating VBG - B-GPE
Candida NNP - I-GPE
auris VERB - O
Biofilms PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Subcutaneous NNP - B-ORG
Injection NNP - I-ORG
of ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
at ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Radial NNP - I-ORG
Artery NNP - I-ORG
Puncture NNP - I-ORG
Site NNP - I-ORG
Reduces VBZ - I-ORG
the DT - I-ORG
Risk NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Early NNP - I-ORG
Radial NNP - I-ORG
Artery NNP - I-ORG
Occlusion NNP - I-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Nicorandil NNP - B-ORG
Versus NNP - I-ORG
Nitroglycerin NNP - I-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
Arterial NNP - B-ORG
Oxygenation NNP - I-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
NTG)-induced PROPN - O
migraine NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
type NOUN - O
headache NOUN - O
is VERB - O
the DET - O
most ADV - O
prominent ADJ - O
side NOUN - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
nitrate ADJ - O
therapy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Open ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
Label PROPN - O
Study PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Stability NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Sublingual NNP - I-ORG
Nitroglycerin NNP - I-MEDICINE
Tablets NNS - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Simulated NNP - B-ORG
Real NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Life NNP - I-ORG
Conditions NNPS - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin JJ - B-MEDICINE
inhalation NOUN - O
may VERB - O
provide VERB - O
dilation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
pulmonary ADJ - O
artery NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
reduction NOUN - O
of ADP - O
pulmonary ADJ - O
artery NOUN - O
pressure NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
improvement NOUN - O
of ADP - O
oxygenation NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Effectiveness NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
Managing VBG - B-ORG
Subacute NNP - I-ORG
Lung NNP - I-ORG
Bleeding VBG - I-ORG
Induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
Balloon NNP - B-ORG
Pulmonary NNP - I-ORG
Angioplasty NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Oral ADJ - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
Solution PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Does VERB - O
the DET - O
Use PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
Patch PROPN - O
Improve PROPN - O
Local PROPN - O
Anaesthetic PROPN - O
Effects PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Bier NNP - B-LOC
's POS - I-LOC
Block NNP - I-LOC
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Dobutamine NNP - B-GPE
and CCONJ - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
Versus NNP - I-GPE
Milrinone NNP - I-GPE
for ADP - O
Perioperative NNP - B-ORG
Management NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Pulmonary NNP - I-ORG
Hypertension NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Mitral NNP - B-ORG
Valve NNP - I-ORG
Surgery NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
remifentanil VERB - O
are VERB - O
among ADP - O
the DET - O
drugs NOUN - O
used VERB - O
to PART - O
induce VERB - O
controlled VERB - O
hypotension NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Controlled VERB - O
hypotension NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Middle ADJ - O
ear NOUN - O
surgery NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
Remifentanil NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DT - B-ORG
Unversity NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: : - I-ORG
Shareholder NN - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
inventor NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
to ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-ORG
Anti JJ - I-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Infective NNP - I-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
LLC NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Licensing NNP - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DT - B-ORG
Unversity NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: : - I-ORG
Shareholder NN - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
inventor NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
to ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-ORG
Anti JJ - I-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Infective NNP - I-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
LLC NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Licensing NNP - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DT - B-ORG
Unversity NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: : - I-ORG
Shareholder NN - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
inventor NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
to ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-ORG
Anti JJ - I-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Infective NNP - I-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
LLC NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Licensing NNP - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
administered VERB - O
in ADP - O
high ADJ - O
doses NOUN - O
for ADP - O
pulmonary ADJ - O
edema NOUN - O
is VERB - O
safe ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
effective ADJ - O
in ADP - O
reducing VERB - O
the DET - O
need NOUN - O
for ADP - O
intensive ADJ - O
care NOUN - O
unit NOUN - O
admission NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Shareholder NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
inventor NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
to ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-ORG
Anti JJ - I-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Infective NNP - I-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
LLC NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Licensing NNP - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
commonly ADV - O
used VERB - O
as ADP - O
an DET - O
antispasmodic NOUN - O
for ADP - O
treating VERB - O
spasm NOUN - O
of ADP - O
coronary ADJ - O
artery NOUN - O
bypass NOUN - O
grafts NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
induced VERB - O
a DET - O
concentration NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
dependent ADJ - O
relaxation NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
was VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
augmented VERB - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
severe ADJ - O
but CCONJ - O
not ADV - O
moderate ADJ - O
renal ADJ - O
failure NOUN - O
than ADP - O
in ADP - O
those DET - O
without ADP - O
renal ADJ - O
failure NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
application NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
coronary ADJ - O
arteriogenesis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Poor ADJ - O
Compliance NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Carrying VERB - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Aspirin NNP - B-NORP
in ADP - O
Patients PROPN - O
With ADP - O
Coronary PROPN - O
Artery PROPN - O
Disease PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
injection NOUN - O
enabled VERB - O
blood NOUN - O
aspiration NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
vasodilator NOUN - O
injection NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
not ADV - O
sheath NOUN - O
removal NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
enduring VERB - O
principles NOUN - O
of ADP - O
coronary ADJ - O
procedures NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Differential NNP - B-ORG
Development NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Facial NNP - I-ORG
and CC - I-ORG
Hind NNP - I-ORG
Paw NNP - I-ORG
Allodynia NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
a DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Induced PROPN - O
Mouse PROPN - O
Model PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Chronic PROPN - O
Migraine PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
Role NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Capsaicin PROPN - O
Sensitive PROPN - O
Primary PROPN - O
Afferents PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DT - B-ORG
Unversity NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: : - I-ORG
Shareholder NN - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
inventor NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
to ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-ORG
Anti JJ - I-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Infective NNP - I-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
LLC NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Licensing NNP - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DT - B-ORG
Effect NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Low NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Dose NNP - I-ORG
Nitroglycerin NNP - I-MEDICINE
Ointment NNP - I-ORG
on IN - I-ORG
Skin NNP - I-ORG
Flap NNP - I-ORG
Necrosis NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Breast NNP - B-GPE
Reconstruction NNP - I-GPE
after ADP - O
Skin PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Sparing NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
Nipple NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Sparing NNP - I-ORG
Mastectomy NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Valproate NNP - B-ORG
Plays VBZ - I-ORG
a DT - I-ORG
Protective JJ - I-ORG
Role NNP - I-ORG
against IN - I-ORG
Migraine NNP - B-ORG
by ADP - O
Inhibiting NNP - B-PERSON
Protein NNP - I-PERSON
Kinase NN - I-PERSON
C NN - I-PERSON
Signalling NN - I-PERSON
in ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
Mice NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Letter NOUN - O
by ADP - O
Jin PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
shan PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Xue NNP - B-PERSON
- HYPH - I-PERSON
bin NNP - I-PERSON
Regarding NN - I-PERSON
Article NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
" PUNCT - O
Physiology NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Angina PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Its ADJ - O
Alleviation NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
: PUNCT - O
Insights NOUN - O
From ADP - O
Invasive PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Laboratory PROPN - O
Measurements PROPN - O
During ADP - O
Exercise PROPN - O
" PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
Role PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Other ADJ - O
Nitrogen PROPN - O
Oxides PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Cardiovascular NNP - B-ORG
Therapeutics NNPS - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
found VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
the DET - O
most ADV - O
acidic ADJ - O
among ADP - O
the DET - O
nitrogen NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
rich ADJ - O
explosives NOUN - O
studied VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
a DET - O
prototypic ADJ - O
NO DET - O
- PUNCT - O
donor NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
triggers NOUN - O
migraine VERB - O
in ADP - O
humans NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
ointment NOUN - O
has VERB - O
a DET - O
rapid ADJ - O
onset NOUN - O
of ADP - O
action NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
time NOUN - O
to ADP - O
full ADJ - O
clinical ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
with ADP - O
high ADJ - O
efficacy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
relatively ADV - O
low ADJ - O
adverse ADJ - O
event NOUN - O
rate NOUN - O
for ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
SCI NNP - B-ORG
experiencing VERB - O
AD NN - B-CARDINAL
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

et PROPN - O
al PROPN - O
to ADP - O
Letter PROPN - O
Regarding VERB - O
Article PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
" PUNCT - O
Physiology NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Angina PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Its ADJ - O
Alleviation NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
: PUNCT - O
Insights NOUN - O
From ADP - O
Invasive PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Laboratory PROPN - O
Measurements PROPN - O
During ADP - O
Exercise PROPN - O
" PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Commentary NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
The DT - B-ORG
Effect NN - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Systemic NNP - I-ORG
Nitroglycerin NNP - I-MEDICINE
Administration NNP - I-ORG
on ADP - O
the DT - B-FAC
Kynurenine NNP - I-FAC
Pathway NNP - I-FAC
in ADP - O
the DET - O
Rat NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- HYPH - I-PERSON
Derived VBN - I-PERSON
Pd NNP - I-PERSON
/ SYM - I-PERSON
Pa NNP - I-PERSON
for IN - I-PERSON
the DT - I-PERSON
Assessment NNP - I-PERSON
of IN - I-PERSON
Intermediate NNP - I-PERSON
Coronary NNP - I-PERSON
Lesions NNPS - I-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Co PROPN - O
- NOUN - O
Inventor PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Ethanol NNP - I-ORG
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Rosenblatt NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
and CCONJ - O
Shareholder NN - B-NORP
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NOUN - O
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
UT NNP - B-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
Co NNP - B-PERSON
- NN - I-PERSON
Inventor NNP - I-PERSON
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Rosenblatt NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
s NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Scientific NNP - B-ORG
Advisor NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NOUN - O
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
I. NNP - B-PERSON
Raad NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Merck NNP - B-ORG
: PUNCT - O
Grant NNP - B-PERSON
Investigator NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Research NNP - B-ORG
  _SP - I-ORG
grant NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
Allergan NNP - B-PERSON
: PUNCT - O
Grant PROPN - O
Investigator PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Research NNP - B-GPE
  _SP - I-GPE
grant NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
Infective NNP - B-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
: PUNCT - O

Co PROPN - O
- NOUN - O
Inventor PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Ethanol NNP - I-ORG
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
s NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Shareholder NN - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NN - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Co PROPN - O
- NOUN - O
Inventor PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Ethanol NNP - I-ORG
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Rosenblatt NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
and CCONJ - O
Shareholder NN - B-NORP
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NOUN - O
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
UT NNP - B-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
Co NNP - B-PERSON
- NN - I-PERSON
Inventor NNP - I-PERSON
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Rosenblatt NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
s NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Scientific NNP - B-ORG
Advisor NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NOUN - O
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
I. NNP - B-PERSON
Raad NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Merck NNP - B-ORG
: PUNCT - O
Grant NNP - B-PERSON
Investigator NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Research PROPN - O
grant NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
Allergan NNP - B-PERSON
: PUNCT - O
Grant PROPN - O
Investigator PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Research PROPN - O
grant NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
Infective NNP - B-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
: PUNCT - O

Co PROPN - O
- NOUN - O
Inventor PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Ethanol NNP - I-ORG
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
s NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Shareholder NN - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NN - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Co PROPN - O
- NOUN - O
Inventor PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Ethanol NNP - I-ORG
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Rosenblatt NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
and CCONJ - O
Shareholder NN - B-NORP
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NOUN - O
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
UT NNP - B-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
Co NNP - B-PERSON
- NN - I-PERSON
Inventor NNP - I-PERSON
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Rosenblatt NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
s NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Scientific NNP - B-ORG
Advisor NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NOUN - O
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
I. NNP - B-PERSON
Raad NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Merck NNP - B-ORG
: PUNCT - O
Grant NNP - B-PERSON
Investigator NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Research NNP - B-ORG
  _SP - I-ORG
grant NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
Allergan NNP - B-PERSON
: PUNCT - O
Grant PROPN - O
Investigator PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Research NNP - B-GPE
  _SP - I-GPE
grant NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
Infective NNP - B-ORG
Technologies NNPS - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
: PUNCT - O

Co PROPN - O
- NOUN - O
Inventor PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Citrate NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Ethanol NNP - I-ORG
catheter NOUN - O
lock NOUN - O
solution NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
owned VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Texas NNP - I-ORG
MD NNP - I-ORG
Anderson NNP - I-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Center NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
UTMDACC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
licensed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Novel NNP - B-PERSON
Anti NNP - I-PERSON
- JJ - I-PERSON
Infective NNP - I-PERSON
Technologies NNPS - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
LLC NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
which ADJ - O
Dr. PROPN - O
Raad NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
a DET - O
s NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Shareholder NN - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Licensing NN - B-ORG
agreement NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
royalty NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
attenuated VERB - O
the DET - O
shock NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
impairment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
mucosal ADJ - O
barrier NOUN - O
integrity NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Topical PROPN - O
Iloprost PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
on IN - I-ORG
Gastric NNP - I-ORG
Microcirculation NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Barrier NNP - B-ORG
Function NNP - I-ORG
during ADP - O
Hemorrhagic PROPN - O
Shock PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Dogs NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Physiology NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Angina NNP - B-GPE
and CCONJ - O
Its ADJ - O
Alleviation NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
: PUNCT - O
Insights NOUN - O
From ADP - O
Invasive PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Laboratory PROPN - O
Measurements PROPN - O
During ADP - O
Exercise PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
Novel ADJ - O
Nonantibiotic ADJ - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Based PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Lock PROPN - O
Solution PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Prevention PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Intraluminal PROPN - O
Central PROPN - O
Venous PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Infections PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Cancer PROPN - O
Patients PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
widely ADV - O
used VERB - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
coronary ADJ - O
vasodilator NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
ischemic ADJ - O
heart NOUN - O
diseases NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Nitroglycerin JJ - B-MEDICINE
concentration NOUN - O
dependently ADV - O
relaxed ADJ - O
endothelium NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
intact ADJ - O
rabbit NOUN - O
coronary ADJ - O
arteries NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
were VERB - O
not ADV - O
different ADJ - O
under ADP - O
normoxic ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
hypoxic ADJ - O
conditions NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Responsiveness PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Coronary PROPN - O
Arteries PROPN - O
to ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
under ADP - O
Hypoxia NNP - B-PERSON
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

They PRON - O
are VERB - O
analyzed VERB - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
narrow ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
band NOUN - O
mobility NOUN - O
filter NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
SEADM NNP - B-ORG
's PART - O
P5 ADJ - O
DMA NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
a DET - O
triple ADJ - O
quadrupole NOUN - O
mass NOUN - O
spectrometer NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Sciex NNP - B-ORG
's PART - O
5500 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
configured VERB - O
in ADP - O
series NOUN - O
to PART - O
transmit VERB - O
precursor NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
fragment NOUN - O
ions NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
explosives NOUN - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
PETN NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
RDX NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
TNT NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

For ADP - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
PETN NNP - B-ORG
the DET - O
combined ADJ - O
filtering NOUN - O
techniques NOUN - O
have VERB - O
not ADV - O
lowered VERB - O
ambient ADJ - O
chemical NOUN - O
noise NOUN - O
down ADV - O
to ADP - O
0.01 CD - B-CARDINAL
ppq NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
one NUM - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
most ADV - O
commonly ADV - O
used VERB - O
antihypertensive ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
in ADP - O
our ADJ - O
hospital NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
hypotensive ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
application NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
combined ADJ - O
surgery NOUN - O
for ADP - O
reconstruction NOUN - O
after ADP - O
ipsilateral ADJ - O
maxillectomy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
orbit NOUN - O
evisceration NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

" PUNCT - O
A DET - O
Novel ADJ - O
Nonantibiotic ADJ - O
Nitroglycerin NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Based PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Lock PROPN - O
Solution PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Prevention PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Intraluminal PROPN - O
Central PROPN - O
Venous PROPN - O
Catheter PROPN - O
Infections PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Cancer PROPN - O
Patients PROPN - O
" PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

We PRON - O
assessed VERB - O
patient NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
reported VERB - O
ease NOUN - O
of ADP - O
use NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
satisfaction NOUN - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
eFlow NNP - B-ORG
CS NNP - B-PRODUCT
nebulizer NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
GOLDEN PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
for ADP - O
Obstructive PROPN - O
Lung PROPN - O
Disease PROPN - O
via ADP - O
Electronic PROPN - O
Nebulizer)-5 PROPN - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
ipratropium NOUN - O
efficiently ADV - O
antagonized VERB - O
an DET - O
ACh NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
airway NOUN - O
contraction NOUN - O
in ADP - O
VX NNP - B-GPE
- PUNCT - O
poisoned VERB - O
PCLS PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
EC50 PROPN - O
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
15.8 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
nmol NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
L PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
EC50 PROPN - O
ipratropium NOUN - O
2.3 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
nmol NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
L NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
or CCONJ - O
glycopyrronium NOUN - O
bromide NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
like ADP - O
other ADJ - O
LAMAs NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
inhibits VERB - O
parasympathetic ADJ - O
nerve NOUN - O
impulses NOUN - O
by ADP - O
selectively ADV - O
blocking VERB - O
the DET - O
binding NOUN - O
of ADP - O
acetylcholine NOUN - O
to ADP - O
muscarinic ADJ - O
receptors NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
unusual ADJ - O
in ADP - O
that ADP - O
it PRON - O
preferentially ADV - O
binds VERB - O
to ADP - O
M3 PROPN - O
over ADP - O
M2 PROPN - O
muscarinic ADJ - O
receptors NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
thereby ADV - O
specifically ADV - O
targeting VERB - O
the DET - O
primary ADJ - O
muscarinic ADJ - O
receptor NOUN - O
responsible ADJ - O
for ADP - O
bronchoconstriction NOUN - O
occurring VERB - O
in ADP - O
COPD NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate JJ - B-MEDICINE
facilitated ADJ - O
tracheal NOUN - O
intubation NOUN - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
rigid ADJ - O
video NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
stylet NOUN - O
by ADP - O
decreasing VERB - O
oral ADJ - O
secretions NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
providing VERB - O
better ADJ - O
visualization NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
faster ADJ - O
intubation NOUN - O
with ADP - O
hemodynamic ADJ - O
stability.www.clinicaltrials.gov NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
Identifier NN - B-ORG
: PUNCT - O
NCT03050242 NNP - B-PRODUCT
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Inhalation NNP - B-ORG
Solution NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
drug NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
device NOUN - O
combination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
long ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
acting VERB - O
antimuscarinic ADJ - O
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
administered VERB - O
using VERB - O
the DET - O
eFlow NNP - B-PRODUCT
® NN - I-PRODUCT
closed VERB - O
system NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
eFlow NNP - B-PRODUCT
CS NNP - I-PRODUCT
) PUNCT - O
nebulizer NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
on ADP - O
HRQoL NNP - B-CARDINAL
from ADP - O
the DET - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
for ADP - O
Obstructive PROPN - O
Lung PROPN - O
Disease PROPN - O
Via PROPN - O
Electronic PROPN - O
Nebulizer PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
GOLDEN PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
clinical ADJ - O
studies NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - I-ORG
eFlow NNP - I-ORG
CS NNP - I-ORG
significantly ADV - O
improved VERB - O
SGRQ PROPN - O
Total PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
component NOUN - O
scores NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Health NN - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Related VBN - I-ORG
Quality NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Life NNP - I-ORG
Improvements NNP - I-ORG
in IN - I-ORG
Moderate PROPN - O
to ADP - O
Very ADV - O
Severe ADJ - O
Chronic ADJ - O
Obstructive ADJ - O
Pulmonary PROPN - O
Disease PROPN - O
Patients PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Nebulized PROPN - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
: PUNCT - O
Evidence NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DT - B-LAW
GOLDEN NNP - I-LAW
Studies NNPS - I-LAW
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - I-ORG
eFlow NNP - I-ORG
CS NN - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
The DET - O
First PROPN - O
Nebulized PROPN - O
Long PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Acting PROPN - O
Muscarinic PROPN - O
Antagonist PROPN - O
Approved VERB - O
to PART - O
Treat VERB - O
Chronic PROPN - O
Obstructive ADJ - O
Pulmonary PROPN - O
Disease PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
Effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Incidence NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Hypotension NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Vasopressor PROPN - O
Requirement PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

An DET - O
Open PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Label PROPN - O
Study NOUN - O
Evaluating VERB - O
the DET - O
Performance PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Dose PROPN - O
Indicator PROPN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
Metered PROPN - O
Dose PROPN - O
Inhaler PROPN - O
Delivering PROPN - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Formoterol PROPN - O
Fumarate PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Moderate PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
to ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
Very ADV - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
total NOUN - O
of ADP - O
2379 CD - B-CARDINAL
patients NOUN - O
from ADP - O
3 CD - B-CARDINAL
phase NOUN - O
III CD - B-ORG
studies NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
12-week CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
placebo NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
controlled VERB - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
for ADP - O
Obstructive PROPN - O
Lung PROPN - O
Disease PROPN - O
via ADP - O
Electronic PROPN - O
Nebulizer PROPN - O
[ PUNCT - O
GOLDEN PROPN - O
] PUNCT - O
-3 PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
-4 NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
48-week CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
active NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
controlled VERB - O
GOLDEN-5 NNP - B-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
stratified VERB - O
by ADP - O
high ADJ - O
( PUNCT - O
n=1526 NUM - O
) PUNCT - O
or CCONJ - O
low ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Efficacy PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Safety PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Nebulized PROPN - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - O
eFlow PROPN - O
® NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Atrio PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
ventricular ADJ - O
Block PROPN - O
Following VERB - O
Neostigmine NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
Reversal NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
heart NOUN - O
Transplant PROPN - O
Patients PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - I-ORG
eFlow NNP - I-ORG
® NN - I-ORG
is VERB - O
an DET - O
investigational ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
device NOUN - O
combination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
LAMA NNP - B-ORG
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
administered VERB - O
by ADP - O
an DET - O
eFlow PROPN - O
® NOUN - O
Closed PROPN - O
System PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
eFlow PROPN - O
® PUNCT - O
CS PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
nebulizer NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

III CD - B-ORG
clinical ADJ - O
studies NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
results NOUN - O
from ADP - O
GOLDEN PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
for ADP - O
Obstructive PROPN - O
Lung PROPN - O
Disease PROPN - O
  SPACE - O
via ADP - O
Electronic PROPN - O
Nebulizer PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
phase NOUN - O
II CD - B-ORG
dose NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
finding VERB - O
studies NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
administered VERB - O
by ADP - O
a DET - O
novel NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
investigational ADJ - O
eFlow NN - B-ORG
® NN - I-ORG
Closed NNP - I-ORG
System NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
CS NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
nebulizer NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
eFlow NNP - B-ORG
CS NNP - I-ORG
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
being VERB - O
evaluated VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
maintenance NOUN - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
chronic ADJ - O
obstructive ADJ - O
pulmonary ADJ - O
disease NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
COPD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate JJ - B-MEDICINE
concentration NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
impurity NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
of ADP - O
nebulized ADJ - O
samples NOUN - O
were VERB - O
statistically ADV - O
similar ADJ - O
to ADP - O
those DET - O
of ADP - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
nebulized ADJ - O
samples NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
Vitro PROPN - O
Characterization PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
eFlow PROPN - O
Closed PROPN - O
System PROPN - O
Nebulizer PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
Inhalation PROPN - O
Solution PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Hyperinflation PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Long ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
term NOUN - O
safety NOUN - O
of ADP - O
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - O
eFlow NOUN - O
® PUNCT - O
CS PROPN - O
in ADP - O
moderate ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
to ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
very ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
severe ADJ - O
COPD PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
Results NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Glycopyrrolate NNP - I-MEDICINE
for IN - I-ORG
Obstructive NNP - I-ORG
Lung NNP - I-ORG
Disease NNP - I-ORG
via IN - I-ORG
Electronic NNP - I-ORG
Nebulizer NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
GOLDEN PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
5 CD - B-CARDINAL
randomized VERB - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - O
formoterol NOUN - O
fumarate NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
GFF NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
metered VERB - O
dose NOUN - O
inhaler NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
MDI PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
fixed VERB - O
- PUNCT - O
dose NOUN - O
combination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
long ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
acting VERB - O
muscarinic ADJ - O
antagonist NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
LAMA PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
GP PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
long ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
acting VERB - O
β2-agonist PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
LABA NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
formoterol NOUN - O
fumarate VERB - O
( PUNCT - O
FF PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
delivered VERB - O
via ADP - O
metered VERB - O
dose NOUN - O
inhaler NOUN - O
using VERB - O
innovative ADJ - O
co NOUN - O
- ADJ - O
suspension ADJ - O
delivery NOUN - O
technology NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
dose NOUN - O
was VERB - O
not ADV - O
significantly ADV - O
correlated VERB - O
with ADP - O
decreased VERB - O
sweat NOUN - O
rate NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
maximal ADJ - O
core NOUN - O
temperature NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
case NOUN - O
report NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
for ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
exercise NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
hyperhidrosis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
Effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Nebulized PROPN - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
Posterior PROPN - O
Drooling PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Patients PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Brain PROPN - O
Injury PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
Two CD - B-CARDINAL
Cases NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Different PROPN - O
Brain PROPN - O
Lesions PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
placebo NOUN - O
were VERB - O
received VERB - O
by ADP - O
96 CD - B-CARDINAL
and CCONJ - O
100 CD - B-CARDINAL
patients NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
respectively ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
may VERB - O
be VERB - O
a DET - O
promising ADJ - O
premedication NOUN - O
to PART - O
ensure VERB - O
safe ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
stable ADJ - O
ESD NN - B-ORG
procedures NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
Seebri NNP - B-PERSON
Neohaler NNP - I-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
Maintenance NNP - B-ORG
Therapy NNP - I-ORG
in IN - I-ORG
Patients PROPN - O
with ADP - O
COPD NNS - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
used VERB - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
0.2 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
dose ADV - O
in ADP - O
74 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
patients NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
97.37 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
the DET - O
preferred ADJ - O
anticholinergic ADJ - O
agent NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
not ADV - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
severe ADJ - O
adverse ADJ - O
events NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
worsening NOUN - O
of ADP - O
cognitive ADJ - O
adverse ADJ - O
events NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
was VERB - O
not ADV - O
superior ADJ - O
to ADP - O
placebo VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
whereas ADP - O
2 CD - B-QUANTITY
mg NN - I-QUANTITY
showed VERB - O
a DET - O
significant ADJ - O
clinical ADJ - O
improvement NOUN - O
of ADP - O
nocturnal ADJ - O
sialorrhea NOUN - O
compared VERB - O
with ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
seemed VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
a DET - O
tolerable ADJ - O
anticholinergic ADJ - O
agent NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
clozapine NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
associated VERB - O
sialorrhea NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
Effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
Nocturnal PROPN - O
Sialorrhea PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Patients PROPN - O
Using VERB - O
Clozapine NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Baseline JJ - B-ORG
Symptom NN - I-ORG
Score NN - I-ORG
Impact NOUN - O
on ADP - O
Benefits NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - I-ORG
Formoterol NNP - I-ORG
Metered NNP - I-ORG
Dose NNP - I-ORG
Inhaler NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
COPD NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
a DET - O
long ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
acting VERB - O
muscarinic ADJ - O
antagonist NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
LAMA PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
formoterol NOUN - O
fumarate NOUN - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
long ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
acting VERB - O
beta2 ADJ - O
agonist NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
LABA NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Efficacy PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Safety PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - O
Formoterol PROPN - O
Metered PROPN - O
Dose PROPN - O
Inhaler NOUN - O
Formulated VERB - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
Robinul PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
in ADP - O
short ADJ - O
supply NOUN - O
in ADP - O
recent JJ - B-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
, PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
one NUM - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
most ADV - O
widely ADV - O
used VERB - O
anticholinergic ADJ - O
agents NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
especially ADV - O
in ADP - O
conjunction NOUN - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
anticholinesterase NOUN - O
neostigmine NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
reversal NOUN - O
of ADP - O
neuromuscular ADJ - O
blockade NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
NMB NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
drugs NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
: PUNCT - O
It PRON - O
's VERB - O
time NOUN - O
to PART - O
review VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
given VERB - O
as ADP - O
reversing VERB - O
agents NOUN - O
of ADP - O
muscle NOUN - O
relaxants NOUN - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
reported VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
effective ADJ - O
in ADP - O
reducing VERB - O
postoperative ADJ - O
catheter NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
related VERB - O
bladder NOUN - O
discomfort NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
CRBD PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
killed VERB - O
all DET - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
examined VERB - O
strains NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
P NOUN - O
< X - O
.05 PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
whereas ADP - O
in ADP - O
atropine NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
only ADV - O
the DET - O
clinical ADJ - O
isolates NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Staphylococcus NNP - B-PRODUCT
and CCONJ - O
Acinetobacter NNP - B-PERSON
were VERB - O
killed VERB - O
( PUNCT - O
P NOUN - O
< X - O
.05).Drawing PUNCT - O
up PART - O
atropine NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
at ADP - O
the DET - O
beginning NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
operating NOUN - O
list NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
use VERB - O
within ADP - O
24 CD - B-TIME
hours NNS - I-TIME
if ADP - O
needed VERB - O
are VERB - O
a DET - O
safe ADJ - O
practice NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
do VERB - O
not ADV - O
pose VERB - O
infection NOUN - O
hazard NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
induction NOUN - O
had VERB - O
lower ADJ - O
POH NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
17.4 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
LOS NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
1.9 CD - B-ORG
  _SP - I-ORG
days NNS - B-DATE
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
compared VERB - O
to ADP - O
no DET - O
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
21.6 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
; PUNCT - O
p X - O
  SPACE - O
= SYM - O
  SPACE - O
0.0849 NUM - O
; PUNCT - O
2.7 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
days NNS - B-DATE
; PUNCT - O
p VERB - O
  SPACE - O
< X - O
  SPACE - O
0.0001 CD - B-DATE
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
comparison NOUN - O
to PART - O
hyoscine VERB - O
hydrobromide NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
placebo NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
hypersalivation NOUN - O
induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
clozapine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
GOTHIC1 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
: PUNCT - O
study NOUN - O
protocol NOUN - O
for ADP - O
a DET - O
randomised ADJ - O
controlled VERB - O
feasibility NOUN - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
craniofacial NOUN - O
compensatory NOUN - O
hyperhidrosis NOUN - O
successfully ADV - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
oxybutynin NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
report NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
novel ADJ - O
adverse ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
subsequent ADJ - O
successful ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - O
formoterol NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Bevespi NNP - B-PERSON
Aerosphere NNP - I-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
COPD NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
showed VERB - O
statistically ADV - O
significant ADJ - O
improvement NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
transition NOUN - O
dyspnea NOUN - O
index NOUN - O
focal ADJ - O
score NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
St NNP - B-PERSON
George NNP - I-PERSON
's POS - I-PERSON
Respiratory NNP - B-FAC
Questionnaire NNP - I-FAC
total ADJ - O
score NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
COPD NNP - B-ORG
Assessment NNP - I-ORG
Test NNP - I-ORG
score NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
rescue NOUN - O
medication NOUN - O
use NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
daily JJ - B-DATE
total ADJ - O
symptom NOUN - O
score NOUN - O
versus ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
at IN - B-DATE
week NN - I-DATE
12 CD - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
0.01 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
kg NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
0.005 NUM - O
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
lb NOUN - O
] PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
was VERB - O
administered VERB - O
IM NNP - B-ORG
to ADP - O
all DET - O
dogs NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
3 CD - B-CARDINAL
dogs NOUN - O
received VERB - O
an DET - O
injection NOUN - O
of ADP - O
saline NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
0.9 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
NaCl NNP - B-NORP
] PUNCT - O
solution NOUN - O
on ADP - O
an DET - O
earlier ADJ - O
occasion NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
final ADJ - O
STT NNP - B-ORG
I PRON - O
measurements NOUN - O
were VERB - O
recorded VERB - O
20 CD - B-TIME
minutes NNS - I-TIME
later ADV - O
( PUNCT - O
at ADP - O
T4 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
had VERB - O
no DET - O
effect NOUN - O
on ADP - O
intraocular ADJ - O
pressure NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
respiratory ADJ - O
rate NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DT - B-ORG
Glycopyrrolate NNP - I-MEDICINE
Effect NNP - I-ORG
on ADP - O
syMptoms NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
lung NOUN - O
function NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
GEM2 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
study NOUN - O
assessed VERB - O
the DET - O
efficacy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
safety NOUN - O
of ADP - O
twice ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
daily ADJ - O
glycopyrrolate NN - B-MEDICINE
15.6 CD - B-CARDINAL
μg NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
moderate ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
to ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
severe ADJ - O
airflow ADJ - O
limitation NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Efficacy PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Safety NNP - B-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Twice NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Daily NNP - I-ORG
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
Versus PROPN - O
Placebo PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Patients NNS - B-GPE
With ADP - O
COPD PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
The DT - B-GPE
GEM2 NNP - I-GPE
Study NNP - I-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Efficacy PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Safety NNP - B-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Glycopyrrolate NNP - I-MEDICINE
/ SYM - I-ORG
Formoterol NNP - I-ORG
Metered NNP - I-ORG
Dose NNP - I-ORG
Inhaler NN - I-ORG
Formulated VBN - I-ORG
Using VBG - I-ORG
Co NNP - I-ORG
- NN - I-ORG
Suspension NN - I-ORG
Delivery NNP - I-ORG
Technology NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Patients NNPS - B-ORG
With IN - I-ORG
COPD NNS - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Long ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
term NOUN - O
Stability NNP - B-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Zonisamide NNP - I-ORG
, , - I-ORG
Amitriptyline NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Glycopyrrolate NNP - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
Extemporaneously PROPN - O
Prepared NNP - B-PERSON
Liquid NNP - I-PERSON
- HYPH - I-PERSON
dosage NN - I-PERSON
Forms NOUN - O
at ADP - O
Two CD - B-CARDINAL
Temperatures PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Contact NOUN - O
leukoderma NOUN - O
induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
rotigotine ADJ - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
® PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Clinical ADJ - O
pharmacology NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
efficacy NOUN - O
of ADP - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
® NN - I-ORG
patch NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
restless NOUN - O
leg NOUN - O
syndrome NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine VERB - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Leganto PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
® PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
( -LRB- - I-PERSON
® NNP - I-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
indicated VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
restless NOUN - O
legs NOUN - O
syndrome NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
RLS NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
; PUNCT - O
this DET - O
article NOUN - O
reviews VERB - O
the DET - O
pharmacological ADJ - O
properties NOUN - O
of ADP - O
rotigotine ADJ - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
its ADJ - O
clinical ADJ - O
efficacy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
tolerability NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
RLS NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
bioavailability NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
loaded VERB - O
microemulsion NOUN - O
gel NOUN - O
was VERB - O
105.76%±20.52 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
with ADP - O
respect NOUN - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
marketed VERB - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
patch NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
® PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
microemulsion NOUN - O
gel NOUN - O
irritated VERB - O
the DET - O
skin NOUN - O
less ADJ - O
than ADP - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
available ADJ - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
patch NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
approved VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
RLS NNP - B-ORG
as ADV - O
well ADV - O
as ADP - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
disease NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Horizant NNP - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
gabapentin ADJ - O
enacarbil NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
provide VERB - O
additional ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
options NOUN - O
for ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
RLS NNP - B-ORG
who NOUN - O
are VERB - O
in ADP - O
need NOUN - O
of ADP - O
medications NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
brief ADJ - O
: PUNCT - O
transdermal ADJ - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
new ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
unique ADJ - O
methodology NOUN - O
was VERB - O
developed VERB - O
to PART - O
evaluate VERB - O
the DET - O
association NOUN - O
between ADP - O
periodic ADJ - O
limb NOUN - O
movements NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PLMs PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
nocturnal ADJ - O
blood NOUN - O
pressure NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
BP NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
excursions NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
restless ADJ - O
legs NOUN - O
syndrome NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
RLS).All NN - B-ORG
data NOUN - O
were VERB - O
collected VERB - O
at ADP - O
baseline NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
ENCORE NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
Effects PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
Cardiovascular PROPN - O
Observations PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Patients PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Restless PROPN - O
Legs PROPN - O
Syndrome PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
study NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
placebo NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
controlled VERB - O
polysomnographic ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
of ADP - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
idiopathic ADJ - O
RLS NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

To PART - O
provide VERB - O
real ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
world NOUN - O
data NOUN - O
on ADP - O
caregiver NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
physician NOUN - O
perceptions NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
advantages NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
disadvantages NOUN - O
of ADP - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
* PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
versus ADP - O
oral ADJ - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
Disease PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
PD PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
medication NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Transdermal NNP - B-PERSON
Rotigotine NNP - I-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Neupro)]. NNP - B-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

These DET - O
amines NOUN - O
are VERB - O
precursors NOUN - O
of ADP - O
important ADJ - O
active ADJ - O
pharmaceutical NOUN - O
ingredients NOUN - O
such ADJ - O
as ADP - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
robalzotan NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
ebalzotan NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine VERB - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
® PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine ADJ - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patches NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Transdermal ADJ - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
formulation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergolinic ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
® NNP - I-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
indicated VERB - O
as ADP - O
monotherapy NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
early ADJ - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
as ADP - O
combination NOUN - O
therapy NOUN - O
with ADP - O
levodopa ADJ - O
throughout ADP - O
the DET - O
course NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
disease NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
route NOUN - O
is VERB - O
an DET - O
advantageous ADJ - O
alternative NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
as ADP - O
shown VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DET - O
recent ADJ - O
commercialization NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
passive ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
containing VERB - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
® PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergolinic ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
available ADJ - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
can VERB - O
be VERB - O
applied VERB - O
once ADV - O
daily ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

UCB NNP - B-ORG
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
developing VERB - O
rotigotine ADJ - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
system NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
; PUNCT - O
SPM-962 NNP - B-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
for ADP - O
RLS NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
nonergoline NOUN - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
delivered VERB - O
transdermally ADV - O
using VERB - O
a DET - O
silicone NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
based VERB - O
patch NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro(R PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
; PUNCT - O
UCB NNP - B-ORG
Pharma NNP - I-ORG
GmbH PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
promotes VERB - O
unidirectional ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
flow NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
system NOUN - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
skin NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
formulation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergolinic ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
receptor NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
indicated VERB - O
for ADP - O
use NOUN - O
as ADP - O
monotherapy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
early ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
stage NOUN - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
EU NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
as ADP - O
an DET - O
adjunct NOUN - O
to PART - O
levodopa VERB - O
across ADP - O
all DET - O
disease NOUN - O
stages NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
formulation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergolinic ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
indicated VERB - O
for ADP - O
use NOUN - O
as ADP - O
monotherapy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
early ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
stage NOUN - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
EU NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
as ADP - O
an DET - O
adjunct NOUN - O
to PART - O
levodopa VERB - O
across ADP - O
all DET - O
disease NOUN - O
stages NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergoline ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
developed VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
once ADV - O
daily ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PD PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
using VERB - O
a DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
delivery NOUN - O
system NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
patch NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
provides VERB - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
drug NOUN - O
continuously ADV - O
over ADP - O
24 CD - B-CARDINAL
h. VERB - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
new ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
Rotigotine NNP - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
can VERB - O
be VERB - O
transdermally ADV - O
applied VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine NOUN - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
new ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergoline ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
receptor NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
developed VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
formulation NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
to PART - O
provide VERB - O
sustained ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
delivery NOUN - O
for ADP - O
24 CD - B-CARDINAL
h NOUN - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
once ADV - O
daily ADJ - O
dosing NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

To PART - O
assess VERB - O
the DET - O
response NOUN - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
rotigotine NOUN - O
transdermal ADJ - O
system NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NN - B-MEDICINE
; PUNCT - O
Schwarz NNP - B-PERSON
Pharma NNP - I-PERSON
Ltd NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Monheim NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Germany NNP - B-GPE
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
nonergolinic ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
early ADJ - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
disease NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
novel ADJ - O
dopaminergic ADJ - O
agonist NOUN - O
with ADP - O
24-hour CD - B-CARDINAL
transdermal ADJ - O
delivery NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
formulated VERB - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
transdermal ADJ - O
delivery NOUN - O
system NOUN - O
designed VERB - O
to PART - O
provide VERB - O
a DET - O
selective ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergot ADJ - O
D3/D2/D1 NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
systemic ADJ - O
blood NOUN - O
flow NOUN - O
over ADP - O
a DET - O
24-hour CD - B-CARDINAL
period NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro((R NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
new ADJ - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
ergolinic ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
agonist NOUN - O
transdermal ADJ - O
patch NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
can VERB - O
be VERB - O
applied VERB - O
once ADV - O
daily RB - B-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Four CD - B-CARDINAL
types NOUN - O
of ADP - O
titanium NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
based VERB - O
orthodontic ADJ - O
wires NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
nickel NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
titanium NOUN - O
alloy NOUN - O
wires NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
nickel NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
titanium NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
copper NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
nickel NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
titanium NOUN - O
] PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
beta NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
titanium NOUN - O
alloy NOUN - O
wires NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
titanium NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
molybdenum NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
titanium NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
niobium NOUN - O
] PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
all DET - O
from ADP - O
Ormco NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Glendora NNP - B-GPE
, , - I-GPE
Calif NNP - I-GPE
) PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
similar ADJ - O
sizes NOUN - O
were VERB - O
prepared VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
immersed VERB - O
in ADP - O
5 CD - B-CARDINAL
fluoride NOUN - O
prophylactic ADJ - O
agents NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
acidulated VERB - O
phosphate ADJ - O
fluoride NOUN - O
agents NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
Nupro ADJ - O
APF PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Dentsply NNP - B-ORG
International NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
York NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Pa PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Florentine NNP - B-PERSON
III NNP - I-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Confi NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Dental NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Louisville NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Colo NNP - B-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
] PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
neutral ADJ - O
agent NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
Neutral NNP - I-ORG
( -LRB- - I-ORG
Dentsply NNP - B-ORG
International NNP - I-ORG
) PUNCT - O
] PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
stannous ADJ - O
fluoride ADJ - O
agents NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
Florentine NNP - B-PERSON
II NNP - I-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Confi NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Dental NNP - I-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Perio NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Med NNP - I-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotigotine PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Neupro NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
( PUNCT - O
Transdermal NNP - B-ORG
Patch NNP - I-ORG
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Efficacy NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Prolonged NNP - B-ORG
Exposure NNP - I-ORG
Therapy NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Sertraline NNP - B-PERSON
Hydrochloride NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Their ADJ - O
Combination NOUN - O
Among ADP - O
Combat PROPN - O
Veterans PROPN - O
With ADP - O
Posttraumatic PROPN - O
Stress PROPN - O
Disorder NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Preparation PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Optimization PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Sertraline NNP - B-MEDICINE
Hydrochloride NNP - I-MEDICINE
Tablets PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Improved PROPN - O
Dissolution PROPN - O
Through ADP - O
Crystal PROPN - O
Modification PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Stability NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Allopurinol PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Amitriptyline NNP - B-PERSON
Hydrochloride NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Carbamazepine NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Domperidone NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Isoniazid PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Ketoconazole NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Lisinopril NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Naproxen NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Paracetamol NNP - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Acetaminophen NNP - B-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Sertraline NNP - B-PERSON
Hydrochloride NNP - I-PERSON
in ADP - O
SyrSpend PROPN - O
SF PROPN - O
PH4 PROPN - O
Oral PROPN - O
Suspensions PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Fetal PROPN - O
Exposure NOUN - O
to ADP - O
Sertraline NNP - B-MEDICINE
Hydrochloride NNP - I-MEDICINE

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Stable ADJ - O
Sertraline NNP - B-MEDICINE
Hydrochloride NNP - I-MEDICINE
Formulation PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Method PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
present ADJ - O
invention NOUN - O
relates VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
improved ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
scalable ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
efficient ADJ - O
manufacturing NOUN - O
procedure NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
preparation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
antidepressant ADJ - O
Cis-(1S)-N NNP - B-PERSON
- HYPH - I-PERSON
Methyl-4-(3,4-Dichlorophenyl)-1,2,3,4-tetrahydro-1-napthaleneamine JJ - I-PERSON
hydro NOUN - O
chloride NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Sertraline NNP - B-GPE
Hydrochloride NNP - I-GPE
polymorphic ADJ - O
form NOUN - O
II NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
present ADJ - O
invention NOUN - O
further ADV - O
relates VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
improved ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
modified ADJ - O
procedures NOUN - O
for ADP - O
preparing VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
separating VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
isolating VERB - O
the DET - O
key ADJ - O
intermediates NOUN - O
involved VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
preparationof NOUN - O
Sertraline NNP - B-PRODUCT
Hydrochloride NNP - I-PRODUCT
polymorphic ADJ - O
form NOUN - O
II NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
present ADJ - O
invention NOUN - O
also ADV - O
further ADV - O
relates VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
use NOUN - O
of ADP - O
novel ADJ - O
reagents NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
a DET - O
combination NOUN - O
thereof ADV - O
and CCONJ - O
new ADJ - O
methodologies NOUN - O
to PART - O
prepare VERB - O
some DET - O
o'f NOUN - O
the DET - O
key ADJ - O
intermediates NOUN - O
involved VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
preparation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Polymorphic NNP - B-PRODUCT
Form NNP - I-PRODUCT
II NNP - I-PRODUCT
of ADP - O
Sertraline NNP - B-GPE
Hydrochloride NNP - I-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

PREDNISOLONE JJ - B-MEDICINE
SODIUM NNP - I-MEDICINE
PHOSPHATE NNP - I-MEDICINE
FORMULATIONS NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

PREDNISOLONE JJ - B-MEDICINE
SODIUM NN - I-MEDICINE
PHOSPHATE JJ - I-MEDICINE
FORMULATIONS NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

STABILIZED PROPN - O
PREDNISOLONE NN - B-MEDICINE
SODIUM NN - I-MEDICINE
PHOSPHATE JJ - I-MEDICINE
SOLUTIONS NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

LIQUID NOUN - O
PREDNISOLONE NN - B-MEDICINE
SODIUM JJ - I-MEDICINE
PHOSPHATE JJ - I-MEDICINE
PREPARATION NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
beneficial ADJ - O
in ADP - O
learning NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
memory NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
although ADP - O
the DET - O
underlying VERB - O
protective ADJ - O
mechanism NOUN - O
of ADP - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
cognitive ADJ - O
performance NOUN - O
remains VERB - O
unclear ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
52-Week CD - B-CARDINAL
Study NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Dose PROPN - O
Adjusted VERB - O
Subcutaneous PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Enanthate PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Oil PROPN - O
Self PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Administered VERB - O
via ADP - O
Disposable PROPN - O
Auto PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Injector PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Implementation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DT - B-ORG
Pilot NNP - I-ORG
Pharmacist NNP - I-ORG
Testosterone NNP - I-MEDICINE
Therapy NNP - I-ORG
Management NNP - I-ORG
Service NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
17β NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
Hydroxyandrost-4-en-3-one NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
the DET - O
main ADJ - O
sex NOUN - O
hormone NOUN - O
in ADP - O
males NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
Males PROPN - O
as ADP - O
Enhanced VERB - O
by ADP - O
Onion PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
Allium PROPN - O
Cepa PROPN - O
L. PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
activates VERB - O
singing VERB - O
within ADP - O
days NNS - B-DATE
in ADP - O
castrated VERB - O
male ADJ - O
songbirds NOUN - O
but CCONJ - O
full ADJ - O
song NOUN - O
quality NOUN - O
only ADV - O
develops VERB - O
after ADP - O
a DT - B-DATE
few JJ - I-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
action NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
song NOUN - O
control NOUN - O
system NOUN - O
works VERB - O
in ADP - O
parallel VERB - O
to PART - O
control VERB - O
song NOUN - O
quality NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
females NOUN - O
from ADP - O
a DET - O
previous ADJ - O
experiment NOUN - O
had VERB - O
a DET - O
smaller ADJ - O
POM NOUN - O
volume NOUN - O
in ADP - O
similar ADJ - O
conditions NOUN - O
suggesting VERB - O
the DET - O
existence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
stable ADJ - O
sex NOUN - O
difference NOUN - O
potentially ADV - O
affecting VERB - O
singing VERB - O
behavior NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
trained VERB - O
rats NOUN - O
had VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
lower ADJ - O
claudin NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
than ADP - O
vehicle NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
trained VERB - O
rats NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
treatment NOUN - O
did VERB - O
not ADV - O
exert VERB - O
a DET - O
significant ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
on ADP - O
ZO-1 NNP - B-GPE
protein NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and/or CCONJ - O
training NOUN - O
had VERB - O
no DET - O
significant ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
on ADP - O
ZO-2 NNP - B-NORP
protein NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
rat NOUN - O
spinal ADJ - O
cords NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Hackett NNP - B-PERSON
G. NNP - I-PERSON
Metabolic NNP - I-PERSON
Effects NNP - I-PERSON
of ADP - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Therapy PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Men PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Type NOUN - O
2 NUM - O
Diabetes PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Metabolic PROPN - O
Syndrome PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Metabolic NNP - B-ORG
Effects NNS - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Testosterone NNP - I-MEDICINE
Therapy NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Men PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Type NOUN - O
2 NUM - O
Diabetes PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Metabolic NNP - B-ORG
Syndrome NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
's PART - O
effects NOUN - O
were VERB - O
rapid ADJ - O
( PUNCT - O
~30 NOUN - O
min NOUN - O
after ADP - O
administration NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
mediated VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
part NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
by ADP - O
subjective ADJ - O
reward NOUN - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
aggression NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
thus ADV - O
appears VERB - O
to PART - O
promote VERB - O
human ADJ - O
aggression NOUN - O
through ADP - O
an DET - O
AR PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
related VERB - O
mechanism NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
to PART - O
have VERB - O
stronger ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
in ADP - O
men NOUN - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
select ADJ - O
personality NOUN - O
profiles NOUN - O
because ADP - O
it PRON - O
more ADV - O
strongly ADV - O
upregulates VERB - O
the DET - O
subjective ADJ - O
pleasure NOUN - O
they PRON - O
derive VERB - O
from ADP - O
aggression NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Using VERB - O
a DT - B-ORG
Psychopharmacogenetic JJ - I-ORG
Approach NNP - I-ORG
To PART - O
Identify VERB - O
the DET - O
Pathways PROPN - O
Through PROPN - O
Which PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
People PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Whom PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Promotes PROPN - O
Aggression PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
induced VERB - O
TECs NOUN - O
apoptosis NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
necrosis NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
increased VERB - O
BNIP3 PROPN - O
expression NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
dose NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
dependent ADJ - O
manner NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
also ADV - O
increased VERB - O
Bax PROPN - O
expression NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
decreased VERB - O
Bcl-2 ADJ - O
expression NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
induced VERB - O
a DET - O
loss NOUN - O
of ADP - O
ΔΨm NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
induces VERB - O
renal ADJ - O
tubular ADJ - O
epithelial ADJ - O
cell NOUN - O
death NOUN - O
through ADP - O
the DET - O
HIF-1α NNP - B-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
BNIP3 NNP - I-ORG
pathway NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Erythrocytosis NOUN - O
During ADP - O
Concomitant PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
SGLT2-Inhibitor PROPN - O
Treatment PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Letter NOUN - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
Editor PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
" PUNCT - O
Long PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Term PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Administration PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Insulin PROPN - O
Sensitivity PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Older PROPN - O
Men NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Low ADJ - O
or CCONJ - O
Low PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Normal PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Levels PROPN - O
" PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Benign NNP - B-FAC
Prostatic NNP - I-FAC
Hyperplasia NNP - I-FAC
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Benign NNP - B-ORG
Prostatic NNP - I-ORG
Hyperplasia NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
therapy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
prostate NOUN - O
cancer NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
levels NOUN - O
in ADP - O
castrated VERB - O
patients NOUN - O
are VERB - O
therefore ADV - O
routinely ADV - O
measured VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Focus VERB - O
on ADP - O
Catabolic PROPN - O
/ SYM - O
anabolic PROPN - O
Interplay NNP - B-ORG
Between IN - I-ORG
Cortisol NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Sex NN - B-FAC
Hormone NNP - I-FAC
Binding NNP - I-FAC
Globulin NNP - I-FAC
in ADP - O
Professional NNP - B-ORG
Athletes NNPS - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
Optimal PROPN - O
Indication PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Replacement PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Late PROPN - O
Onset PROPN - O
Hypogonadism PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Predictive PROPN - O
Factors PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Efficacy PROPN - O
Maintenance PROPN - O
after ADP - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Treatment NNP - I-LAW
Cessation NNP - I-LAW
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
has VERB - O
effects NOUN - O
on ADP - O
many ADJ - O
organs NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
systems NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Replacement PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Sexual ADJ - O
Symptoms NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Replacement PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Sexual ADJ - O
Symptoms NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
Men NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Chronic PROPN - O
Hepatitis NNP - B-ORG
C NNP - I-ORG
Infection NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
After ADP - O
Hepatitis NNP - B-ORG
C NNP - I-ORG
Viral NNP - I-ORG
Clearance NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
treatment NOUN - O
appears VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
effective ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
efficacious ADJ - O
in ADP - O
reducing VERB - O
depressive ADJ - O
symptoms NOUN - O
in ADP - O
men NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
particularly ADV - O
when ADV - O
higher ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
dosage NOUN - O
regimens NOUN - O
were VERB - O
applied VERB - O
in ADP - O
carefully ADV - O
selected VERB - O
samples NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Association NNP - B-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Testosterone NNP - I-MEDICINE
Treatment NNP - I-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
therapy NOUN - O
for ADP - O
women NOUN - O
is VERB - O
in ADP - O
widespread ADJ - O
use NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
primarily ADV - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
form NOUN - O
of ADP - O
compounded ADJ - O
preparations NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
off ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
label NOUN - O
use NOUN - O
of ADP - O
formulations NOUN - O
for ADP - O
men NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
cortisol NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
status NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
striving VERB - O
personality NOUN - O
features NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
review NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
empirical ADJ - O
evaluation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Dual NNP - B-GPE
Hormone NNP - I-GPE
hypothesis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
boosting VERB - O
supplements NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
T NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Boosters NNP - I-ORG
) PUNCT - O
are VERB - O
prominently ADV - O
featured VERB - O
on ADP - O
Amazon.com NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
numerous ADJ - O
dedicated ADJ - O
pages NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
claims NOUN - O
that ADP - O
they PRON - O
" PUNCT - O
naturally ADV - O
" PUNCT - O
increase VERB - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
levels NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Imposters PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
An DET - O
Analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Popular PROPN - O
Online PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Boosting PROPN - O
Supplements PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Imposters PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
An DET - O
Analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Popular PROPN - O
Online PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Boosting PROPN - O
Supplements PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
injection NOUN - O
to ADP - O
wild ADJ - O
type NOUN - O
mice NOUN - O
increased VERB - O
the DET - O
levels NOUN - O
of ADP - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Gas6 NNP - B-PERSON
in ADP - O
serum NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
decreased VERB - O
cardiac ADJ - O
apoptosis NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
fibrosis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Response NOUN - O
to ADP - O
Letter PROPN - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
Editor PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
" PUNCT - O
Long PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Term PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Administration PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Insulin PROPN - O
Sensitivity PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Older PROPN - O
Men NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Low ADJ - O
or CCONJ - O
Low PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Normal PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Levels PROPN - O
" PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
insufficiency NOUN - O
may VERB - O
play VERB - O
a DET - O
role NOUN - O
in ADP - O
age NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
related VERB - O
decreases NOUN - O
in ADP - O
bone NOUN - O
mass ADJ - O
density NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
BMD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
osteoporosis NOUN - O
in ADP - O
aging VERB - O
men NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
replacement NOUN - O
therapy NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
T NOUN - O
therapy NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
seems VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
a DET - O
simple ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
convenient ADJ - O
way NOUN - O
to PART - O
increase VERB - O
BMD NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
improve VERB - O
the DET - O
condition NOUN - O
of ADP - O
osteoporosis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Replacement PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
Has VERB - O
Limited PROPN - O
Effect NOUN - O
on ADP - O
Increasing VERB - O
Bone PROPN - O
Mass PROPN - O
Density PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Older PROPN - O
Men PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
Meta PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
analysis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Breast NNP - B-ORG
Cancer NNP - I-ORG
Development NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
a DET - O
Transgender NNP - B-ORG
Male NNP - I-ORG
Receiving VBG - I-ORG
Testosterone NNP - I-MEDICINE
Therapy NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pubertal ADJ - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Correlates PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Adolescent PROPN - O
Impatience PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Dorsal NNP - B-ORG
Striatal NNP - I-ORG
Activity NN - I-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
cypionate NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Stanozolol NNP - B-PERSON
are VERB - O
Anabolic NNP - B-PERSON
- HYPH - I-PERSON
Androgenic NNP - I-PERSON
Steroids PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
AAS NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
are VERB - O
synthetic ADJ - O
substances NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
possess VERB - O
functions NOUN - O
similar ADJ - O
to PART - O
testosterone VB - B-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

Results NOUN - O
demonstrated VERB - O
that ADP - O
both DET - O
AAS NNP - B-ORG
changed VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
the DET - O
heart NOUN - O
morphology NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
cypionate NOUN - O
led VERB - O
to ADP - O
an DET - O
increase NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
ventricular ADJ - O
lumen NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
stanozolol NOUN - O
increased VERB - O
left VERB - O
ventricle NOUN - O
myocardium NOUN - O
thickness NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
could VERB - O
mimic VERB - O
the DET - O
action NOUN - O
of ADP - O
LH NNP - B-ORG
on ADP - O
oocyte NOUN - O
maturation NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
its ADJ - O
action NOUN - O
appears VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
independent ADJ - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
classical ADJ - O
nuclear ADJ - O
androgen NOUN - O
receptor NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
inhibits VERB - O
the DET - O
transcriptional ADJ - O
activation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
AMH NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Serum PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Level PROPN - O
Within ADP - O
Normal PROPN - O
Range NOUN - O
Is VERB - O
Positively ADV - O
Associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
Nonalcoholic NNP - B-ORG
Fatty NNP - I-ORG
Liver NNP - I-ORG
Disease NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Premenopausal NNP - B-GPE
but CCONJ - O
Not ADV - O
Postmenopausal PROPN - O
Women PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
deficiency NOUN - O
can VERB - O
be VERB - O
the DET - O
reason NOUN - O
for ADP - O
such ADJ - O
failure NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Serum PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Levels PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Prostate PROPN - O
Cancer PROPN - O
Risk NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

A DET - O
Single PROPN - O
Post PROPN - O
- ADJ - O
Hoc PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Measurement PROPN - O
is VERB - O
Not ADV - O
Informative ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
monoamine ADJ - O
oxidase NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O

Testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
cortisol ADJ - O
levels NOUN - O
as ADV - O
well ADV - O
as ADP - O
subjective ADJ - O
anger NOUN - O
were VERB - O
assessed VERB - O
prior ADV - O
and CCONJ - O
after ADP - O
the DET - O
task NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
administration NOUN - O
increased VERB - O
activation NOUN - O
in ADP - O
this DET - O
network NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Replacement PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Rehospitalization PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Older ADJ - O
Men PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Deficiency PROPN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
Post NNP - B-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Acute JJ - I-ORG
Care NNP - I-ORG
Setting NN - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Coenzyme NNP - B-ORG
Q10 NNP - I-ORG
Supplementation NNP - I-ORG
on IN - I-ORG
Testosterone NNP - I-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
levels NOUN - O
were VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
higher ADJ - O
in ADP - O
adult NOUN - O
compared VERB - O
to PART - O
immature VERB - O
males NOUN - O
as ADP - O
measured VERB - O
by ADP - O
LC PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
MS PROPN - O
but CCONJ - O
not ADV - O
as ADP - O
measured VERB - O
by ADP - O
EIA NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
lower ADJ - O
than ADP - O
BL NNP - B-GPE
at ADP - O
1 CD - B-MONEY
d CD - I-MONEY
( PUNCT - O
95 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
confidence NOUN - O
interval NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
CI NNP - B-ORG
] PUNCT - O
0.10 CD - B-CARDINAL
- SYM - O
0.34 NUM - O
, PUNCT - O
P NOUN - O
  SPACE - O
< X - O
  SPACE - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
replacement NOUN - O
in ADP - O
castrated VERB - O
males NOUN - O
restored VERB - O
Ang NNP - B-PERSON
II NNP - I-PERSON
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
hypertensive ADJ - O
responses NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
plays VERB - O
a DET - O
permissive ADJ - O
role NOUN - O
in ADP - O
angiotensin NOUN - O
II NNP - B-ORG
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
hypertension NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
cardiac ADJ - O
hypertrophy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
male ADJ - O
rats NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
to PART - O
cortisol VERB - O
ratio NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
aggression NOUN - O
toward ADP - O
one PRON - O
's PART - O
partner NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Evidence NOUN - O
for ADP - O
moderation NOUN - O
by ADP - O
provocation NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Early ADJ - O
Pubertal PROPN - O
Timing PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Associated PROPN - O
With ADP - O
Higher PROPN - O
Levels PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Adolescent PROPN - O
Depression PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Girls PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
cortisol NOUN - O
modulate VERB - O
the DET - O
effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
empathy NOUN - O
on ADP - O
aggression NOUN - O
in ADP - O
children NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
its ADJ - O
binding VERB - O
protein NOUN - O
sex NOUN - O
hormone NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
binding VERB - O
globulin NOUN - O
have VERB - O
been VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
cardiovascular ADJ - O
disease NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
dysglycaemia NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
sex NOUN - O
hormone NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
binding VERB - O
globulin NOUN - O
were VERB - O
measured VERB - O
at ADP - O
baseline NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
used VERB - O
to PART - O
estimate VERB - O
free ADJ - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
sex NOUN - O
hormone NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
binding VERB - O
globulin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
cardiovascular ADJ - O
events NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
report NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Outcome NNP - I-ORG
Reduction NNP - I-ORG
with ADP - O
an DET - O
Initial NNP - B-ORG
Glargine NNP - I-ORG
Intervention NNP - I-ORG
trial NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
promotes VERB - O
anxiolytic ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
like ADJ - O
behavior NOUN - O
in ADP - O
gonadectomized VERB - O
male ADJ - O
rats NOUN - O
via ADP - O
blockade NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
5-HT1A NNP - B-ORG
receptors NOUN - O
" PUNCT - O
[ PUNCT - O
GCE PROPN - O
Vol PROPN - O
254 NUM - O
( PUNCT - O
1 NUM - O
December NNP - B-DATE
2017)14 CD - I-DATE
- SYM - I-DATE
21]. CD - I-DATE

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
levels NOUN - O
were VERB - O
negatively ADV - O
correlated VERB - O
with ADP - O
cortisol ADJ - O
levels NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
administration NOUN - O
to ADP - O
prepubertal ADJ - O
males NOUN - O
led VERB - O
to ADP - O
a DET - O
higher ADJ - O
body NOUN - O
mass NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
greater ADJ - O
expression NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Bip NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Ire1α NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Atf4 NNP - B-PRODUCT
and CCONJ - O
Xbp1s NNP - B-PRODUCT
in ADP - O
the DET - O
liver NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
affects VERB - O
insulin NOUN - O
resistance NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
the DET - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
treatment NOUN - O
on ADP - O
type NOUN - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
diabetes NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
T2D NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
remains VERB - O
controversial ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
MDD NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
metabolic NOUN - O
syndrome NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
MetS PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
men NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
although ADP - O
associations NOUN - O
in ADP - O
women NOUN - O
are VERB - O
less ADV - O
clear ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
T NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
suggested VERB - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
promising ADJ - O
agent NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
bone NOUN - O
osteointegration NOUN - O
when ADV - O
incorporated VERB - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
bioceramic ADJ - O
/ SYM - O
polymer ADJ - O
combination NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
local ADJ - O
application NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
successfully ADV - O
incorporated VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
composites NOUN - O
showed VERB - O
a DET - O
homogeneously ADV - O
distributed VERB - O
porous ADJ - O
structure NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
improves VERB - O
the DET - O
osteogenic ADJ - O
potential NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
composite ADJ - O
in X - O
vitro NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
vivo NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
5 CD - B-CARDINAL
and CCONJ - O
10 CD - B-QUANTITY
mg NN - I-QUANTITY
/ SYM - I-QUANTITY
kg NNS - I-QUANTITY
) PUNCT - O
or CCONJ - O
control NOUN - O
oil NOUN - O
was VERB - O
administered VERB - O
to ADP - O
AAA PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
mice NOUN - O
with ADP - O
castration NOUN - O
for ADP - O
8 CD - B-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
administration NOUN - O
significantly ADV - O
prevent VERB - O
AAA NNP - B-ORG
formation NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
administration NOUN - O
significantly ADV - O
inhibited VERB - O
expression NOUN - O
of ADP - O
inflammatory ADJ - O
cytokines NOUN - O
including VERB - O
IL-6 PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
IL-1b PROPN - O
in ADP - O
aorta NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
explored VERB - O
for ADP - O
treating VERB - O
postmenopausal NOUN - O
symptoms NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
such ADJ - O
as ADP - O
vaginal ADJ - O
atrophy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Ex NNP - B-ORG
Vivo NNP - I-ORG
Evaluation NN - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Intravaginal NNP - I-ORG
Progesterone NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
to TO - I-WORK_OF_ART
Treat VB - I-WORK_OF_ART
the DT - I-WORK_OF_ART
Luteal NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
- PUNCT - O
phase NOUN - O
Deficiency NNP - B-NORP
and CCONJ - O
Vaginal PROPN - O
Atrophy PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Long PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Term PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Supplementation PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Older PROPN - O
Men PROPN - O
Attenuates PROPN - O
Age NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
Related VERB - O
Decline PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Aerobic NNP - B-GPE
Capacity NNP - I-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Does VERB - O
Transdermal PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Increase VERB - O
the DET - O
Risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Developing VERB - O
Breast PROPN - O
Cancer PROPN - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O
