-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
did VERB - O
not ADV - O
have VERB - O
any DET - O
significant ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
cortisol ADJ - O
awakening NOUN - O
response NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
the DET - O
total ADJ - O
daily ADJ - O
cortisol NOUN - O
output NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram CD - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
one NUM - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
newer ADV - O
selective ADJ - O
serotonin NOUN - O
reuptake VERB - O
inhibitors NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
SSRIs PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
considered VERB - O
preferable ADJ - O
due ADP - O
to ADP - O
its ADJ - O
relatively ADV - O
high ADJ - O
efficacy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
acceptability NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Racial ADJ - O
Differences PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
/ SYM - I-ORG
Citalopram NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Related NNP - I-ORG
Weight NNP - I-ORG
Gain NNP - I-ORG
in IN - I-ORG
Children PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Adolescents PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
Natural PROPN - O
Language PROPN - O
Processing PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Based VERB - O
Electronic PROPN - O
Medical PROPN - O
Record PROPN - O
Study PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NN - B-MEDICINE
attenuates VERB - O
fear VERB - O
stress NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
increase NOUN - O
in ADP - O
amygdalar ADJ - O
dopamine NOUN - O
following VERB - O
methamphetamine NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
sensitisation NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Implications NOUN - O
of ADP - O
fine ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
tuning NOUN - O
action NOUN - O
of ADP - O
selective ADJ - O
serotonin NOUN - O
reuptake VERB - O
inhibitors NOUN - O
on ADP - O
emotional ADJ - O
processing NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram VB - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Treatment NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Anxiety NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Chromosome PROPN - O
18p NOUN - O
Deletion NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
ESC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
one CD - B-CARDINAL
of ADP - O
only RB - B-CARDINAL
two CD - I-CARDINAL
antidepressants NOUN - O
approved VERB - O
as ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
for ADP - O
juvenile ADJ - O
depression NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
this DET - O
ancillary ADJ - O
investigation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
vs. ADP - O
Electrical NNP - B-ORG
Current NNP - I-ORG
Therapy NNP - I-ORG
for IN - I-ORG
Treating VBG - I-ORG
Depression NNP - I-ORG
Clinical NNP - I-ORG
Study PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
ELECT NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
TDCS PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
we PRON - O
investigated VERB - O
whether ADP - O
plasma ADJ - O
levels NOUN - O
of ADP - O
several ADJ - O
cytokines NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
neurotrophic ADJ - O
factors NOUN - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
major ADJ - O
depression NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
antidepressant NOUN - O
response NOUN - O
predicted VERB - O
tDCS PROPN - O
effects NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Impact NOUN - O
of ADP - O
CYP2C19 PROPN - O
Genotype PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
Exposure NNP - I-ORG
and CC - I-ORG
Therapeutic PROPN - O
Failure NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
Retrospective PROPN - O
Study NOUN - O
Based VERB - O
on ADP - O
2,087 CD - B-CARDINAL
Patients NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
increased VERB - O
waist NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
median NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
quartiles NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
change NOUN - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
( PUNCT - O
0 CD - B-CARDINAL
; SYM - O

Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
had VERB - O
no DET - O
significant ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
on ADP - O
measures NOUN - O
of ADP - O
insulin NOUN - O
sensitivity NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
insulin NOUN - O
secretion NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
fasting VERB - O
lipids NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
mental ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
HRQoL.Waist ADJ - O
circumference NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
cortisol ADJ - O
levels NOUN - O
increased VERB - O
during ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
escitalopram NN - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
women NOUN - O
with ADP - O
PCOS NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
no DET - O
clinical ADJ - O
depression NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
whereas ADP - O
metabolic ADJ - O
risk NOUN - O
markers NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
mental ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
HRQol NNP - B-PERSON
were VERB - O
unchanged ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NN - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
delayed VERB - O
drug NOUN - O
rash NOUN - O
with ADP - O
deranged VERB - O
liver NOUN - O
function NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
possible ADJ - O
case NOUN - O
of ADP - O
drug NOUN - O
reaction NOUN - O
with ADP - O
eosinophilia ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
systemic ADJ - O
reaction NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Secondary PROPN - O
Prevention PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Chronic PROPN - O
PTSD PROPN - O
by ADP - O
Early ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
Short NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Term NNP - I-ORG
Administration NNP - I-ORG
of ADP - O
Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Seventy CD - B-CARDINAL
- HYPH - I-CARDINAL
three CD - I-CARDINAL
depressive ADJ - O
patients NOUN - O
medicated VERB - O
with ADP - O
Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
n NOUN - O
= SYM - O
37 NUM - O
) PUNCT - O
or CCONJ - O
Duloxetine NNP - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
n NOUN - O
= SYM - O
36 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
were VERB - O
assessed VERB - O
using VERB - O
the DET - O
Hamilton NNP - B-PERSON
depression NOUN - O
rating NOUN - O
scale NOUN - O
over ADP - O
a DET - O
24-week CD - B-CARDINAL
period NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
has VERB - O
some DET - O
unique ADJ - O
features NOUN - O
among ADP - O
selective ADJ - O
serotonin NOUN - O
reuptake VERB - O
inhibitors NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
citalopram NOUN - O
are VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
highest ADJ - O
risk NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
NHT NNP - B-ORG
normalized VERB - O
stress NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
anhedonia NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
molecular ADJ - O
neuroadaptations NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
mouse NOUN - O
model NOUN - O
of ADP - O
depression NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Successful ADJ - O
Use PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Escitalopram NNP - B-MEDICINE
for ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Treatment NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Visual NNP - I-ORG
Hallucinations NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Patients NNP - B-LAW
With IN - I-LAW
Parkinson NNP - I-LAW
Disease NNP - I-LAW
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram CD - B-MEDICINE
monotherapy NOUN - O
is VERB - O
effective ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
safe ADJ - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
MDD NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
Chinese JJ - B-NORP
patients NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
therapeutic ADJ - O
efficacy NOUN - O
is VERB - O
dependent ADJ - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
severity NOUN - O
of ADP - O
MDD NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Escitalopram VB - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
the DET - O
Treatment PROPN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
3-Year CD - B-CARDINAL
- PUNCT - O
Old ADJ - O
Child NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Posttraumatic PROPN - O
Feeding NOUN - O
Disorder NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Imposters PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
An DET - O
Analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Popular PROPN - O
Online PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Boosting PROPN - O
Supplements PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
inhibits VERB - O
the DET - O
transcriptional ADJ - O
activation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
AMH NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Replacement PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Rehospitalization PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Older ADJ - O
Men PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Deficiency PROPN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
Post NNP - B-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Acute JJ - I-ORG
Care NNP - I-ORG
Setting NN - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
sex NOUN - O
hormone NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
binding VERB - O
globulin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
cardiovascular ADJ - O
events NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
report NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Outcome NNP - I-ORG
Reduction NNP - I-ORG
with ADP - O
an DET - O
Initial NNP - B-ORG
Glargine NNP - I-ORG
Intervention NNP - I-ORG
trial NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
explored VERB - O
for ADP - O
treating VERB - O
postmenopausal NOUN - O
symptoms NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
such ADJ - O
as ADP - O
vaginal ADJ - O
atrophy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Low ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
Dose NOUN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Evoked PROPN - O
Resistance PROPN - O
Exercise PROPN - O
after ADP - O
Spinal NNP - B-PERSON
Cord NNP - I-PERSON
Injury NNP - I-PERSON
[ PUNCT - O
TEREX NNP - B-WORK_OF_ART
- HYPH - I-WORK_OF_ART
SCI NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
] -RRB- - I-WORK_OF_ART
on IN - I-WORK_OF_ART
Cardio PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
metabolic PROPN - O
Risk NNP - B-ORG
Factors NNPS - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
An DET - O
open ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
label NOUN - O
randomized VERB - O
clinical ADJ - O
trial NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
had VERB - O
highest ADJ - O
positive ADJ - O
correlation NOUN - O
with ADP - O
testicular ADJ - O
length NOUN - O
followed VERB - O
by ADP - O
testicular ADJ - O
width NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
length NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
body NOUN - O
weight NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
scrotal NOUN - O
circumference NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
mass ADJ - O
activity NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
live ADJ - O
sperm NOUN - O
count NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
initial ADJ - O
motility NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
while ADP - O
it PRON - O
had VERB - O
highest ADJ - O
negative ADJ - O
correlation NOUN - O
with ADP - O
dead ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
abnormal ADJ - O
sperm NOUN - O
count NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Exogenous ADJ - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Increases PROPN - O
Decoy PROPN - O
Effect PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Healthy PROPN - O
Males PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
The DT - B-WORK_OF_ART
Role NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
of IN - I-WORK_OF_ART
Testosterone NNP - I-MEDICINE
in IN - I-WORK_OF_ART
The DT - I-WORK_OF_ART
Improvement NN - I-WORK_OF_ART
of IN - I-WORK_OF_ART
Sexual JJ - I-WORK_OF_ART
Desire NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
in IN - I-WORK_OF_ART
Postmenopausal NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
Women NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
: PUNCT - O
An DET - O
Evidence NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
Based VERB - O
Clinical PROPN - O
Review]. PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Hyperandrogenism NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DT - B-ORG
Postmenopausal NNP - I-ORG
Woman NN - I-ORG
Secondary JJ - I-ORG
to ADP - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Secreting NNP - I-ORG
Ovarian NNP - I-ORG
Stromal NNP - I-ORG
Tumor NNP - I-ORG
with ADP - O
Acoustic NNP - B-PERSON
Schwannoma NNP - I-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone JJ - B-MEDICINE
replacement NOUN - O
in ADP - O
androgen NOUN - O
insensitivity NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
there ADV - O
an DET - O
advantage NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Is VERB - O
a DET - O
Contraceptive PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Should VERB - O
Not ADV - O
Be VERB - O
Used VERB - O
in ADP - O
Men NOUN - O
Who NOUN - O
Desire PROPN - O
Fertility PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Anti JJ - B-NORP
- JJ - I-NORP
Müllerian JJ - I-NORP
Hormone NNP - B-GPE
as ADP - O
a DET - O
Diagnostic PROPN - O
Marker PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Egyptian NNP - B-NORP
Infertile PROPN - O
Polycystic PROPN - O
Ovary PROPN - O
Syndrome PROPN - O
Females PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
Correlations NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Vitamin NN - B-PERSON
D NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Total PROPN - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
Dyslipidemia NNP - B-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
Anthropometric PROPN - O
Parameters PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DT - B-ORG
Physical NNP - I-ORG
Function NNP - I-ORG
Trial NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
PFT NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
was VERB - O
one CD - B-CARDINAL
of ADP - O
seven CD - B-CARDINAL
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Trials PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
TTrials PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
aim NOUN - O
of ADP - O
which ADJ - O
was VERB - O
to PART - O
assess VERB - O
the DET - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
on ADP - O
mobility NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
self NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
reported VERB - O
physical ADJ - O
function NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
falls VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
patient VERB - O
global ADJ - O
impression NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
of ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
change NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PGIC PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
older ADJ - O
men NOUN - O
with ADP - O
low ADJ - O
testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
concentrations NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
self NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
reported VERB - O
mobility NOUN - O
limitation NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
walking VERB - O
speed NOUN - O
of ADP - O
less ADJ - O
than ADP - O
1·2 CD - B-NORP
m NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
s NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
men NOUN - O
with ADP - O
baseline NOUN - O
walking VERB - O
speed NOUN - O
of ADP - O
1·2 CD - B-QUANTITY
m NN - I-QUANTITY
/ SYM - I-QUANTITY
s NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
higher ADJ - O
had VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
greater ADJ - O
improvements NOUN - O
in ADP - O
6MWT NUM - O
distance NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
treatment NOUN - O
effect NOUN - O
14·2 PROPN - O
m NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
6·5 NUM - O
- SYM - O
21·9 PROPN - O
; PUNCT - O
p=0·0004 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
PF10 NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
4·9 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
2·2 CD - B-CARDINAL
- SYM - I-CARDINAL
7·7 CD - I-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
p=0·0005 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
than ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
men NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
men NOUN - O
reporting VERB - O
mobility NOUN - O
limitation NOUN - O
showed VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
more ADJ - O
improvement NOUN - O
in ADP - O
6MWT NUM - O
distance NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
7·6 CD - B-QUANTITY
m CD - I-QUANTITY
, PUNCT - O
1·0 CD - B-DATE
- SYM - I-DATE
14·1 CD - I-DATE
; PUNCT - O
p=0·0237 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
PF10 PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
3·6 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
1·3 NUM - O
- PUNCT - O
5·9 PROPN - O
; PUNCT - O
p=0·0018 NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
than ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
men NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Testosterone NN - B-MEDICINE
therapy NOUN - O
consistently ADV - O
improved VERB - O
self NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
reported VERB - O
walking VERB - O
ability NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
modestly ADV - O
improved VERB - O
6MWT CD - B-PRODUCT
distance NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
across ADP - O
all DET - O
TTtrials NNS - B-NORP
participants NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
did VERB - O
not ADV - O
affect VERB - O
falls VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

To PART - O
assess VERB - O
the DET - O
impact NOUN - O
of ADP - O
systemic ADJ - O
comorbidities NOUN - O
on ADP - O
a DET - O
validated ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
phenotype NOUN - O
score NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
ACTIONS PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
Anxiety PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Cardiovascular PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
Insulin NNP - B-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
diabetes NN - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Obesity NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Neurologic NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Sleep NNP - B-NORP
apnea NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
on ADP - O
outcomes NOUN - O
of ADP - O
transurethral ADJ - O
resection NOUN - O
of ADP - O
prostate NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
TURP NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
benign ADJ - O
prostatic ADJ - O
hyperplasia NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
BPH PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
symptoms NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
medication NOUN - O
discontinuation NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Comorbidities NOUN - O
of ADP - O
men NOUN - O
undergoing VERB - O
TURP PROPN - O
for ADP - O
BPH PROPN - O
from ADP - O
2004 CD - B-DATE
- SYM - I-DATE
15 CD - I-DATE
were VERB - O
assessed VERB - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
validated VERB - O
ACTIONS PROPN - O
phenotype NOUN - O
totaling VERB - O
a DET - O
score NOUN - O
from ADP - O
0 CD - B-CARDINAL
- SYM - O
2 NUM - O
for ADP - O
each DET - O
domain NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Anxiety NNP - B-ORG
, , - I-ORG
Cardiovascular NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
Insulin NNP - B-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
diabetes NN - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Obesity NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Neurologic NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Sleep NNP - B-NORP
apnea NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

Lower ADJ - O
scores NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
p=0.04 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
Neurologic NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
p=0.003 PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Sleep NNP - B-NORP
apnea NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
p=0.04 ADJ - O
) PUNCT - O
domains NOUN - O
were VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
medication NOUN - O
discontinuation NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Testosterone NNP - B-MEDICINE
undecanoate ADJ - O
supplementation NOUN - O
together ADV - O
with ADP - O
human ADJ - O
chorionic ADJ - O
gonadotropin NOUN - O
does VERB - O
not ADV - O
impair VERB - O
spermatogenesis NOUN - O
in ADP - O
males NOUN - O
with ADP - O
isolated VERB - O
hypogonadotropic ADJ - O
hypogonadism NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
retrospective ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NNP - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
a DET - O
cytidine ADJ - O
analog NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
is VERB - O
incorporated VERB - O
into ADP - O
DNA NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
induces VERB - O
the DET - O
specific ADJ - O
inhibition NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
proteasomal ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
mediated VERB - O
degradation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Dnmts NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine JJ - B-MEDICINE
resistance NOUN - O
caused VERB - O
by ADP - O
LAMP2 NNP - B-GPE
deficiency NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
therapeutic ADJ - O
window NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
use NOUN - O
of ADP - O
autophagy NOUN - O
inhibitors NOUN - O
in ADP - O
MDS NNP - B-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
AML NNP - I-ORG
patients NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NN - B-MEDICINE
should VERB - O
be VERB - O
kept VERB - O
in ADP - O
mind NOUN - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
option NOUN - O
for ADP - O
RP NNP - B-PERSON
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
MDS NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Delayed NNP - B-PERSON
Onset NNP - I-PERSON
of ADP - O
Azacitidine NNP - B-MEDICINE
- HYPH - I-ORG
Associated NNP - I-ORG
Pneumotitis PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DT - B-WORK_OF_ART
Case NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
Report NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine VB - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
the DET - O
' PUNCT - O
real ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
world NOUN - O
' PUNCT - O
: PUNCT - O
an DET - O
evaluation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
1101 CD - B-DATE
higher ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
risk NOUN - O
myelodysplastic ADJ - O
syndrome NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
low ADJ - O
blast NOUN - O
count NOUN - O
acute ADJ - O
myeloid ADJ - O
leukaemia NOUN - O
patients NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Ontario NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Canada NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NNP - B-MEDICINE
may VERB - O
be VERB - O
the DET - O
  SPACE - O
preferred ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
for ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
AML NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
MRC NNP - I-ORG
who NOUN - O
are VERB - O
not ADV - O
candidates NOUN - O
for ADP - O
intensive ADJ - O
chemotherapy NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
particularly ADV - O
patients NOUN - O
ages VERB - O
65 CD - B-PERCENT
- SYM - I-PERCENT
74 CD - I-PERCENT
  _SP - I-PERCENT
years NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
those DET - O
with ADP - O
intermediate ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
risk NOUN - O
cytogenetics NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
AZA NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
nucleoside ADJ - O
analog NOUN - O
used VERB - O
for ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
myelodysplasia NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
prediction NOUN - O
of ADP - O
AZA NNP - B-ORG
responsiveness NOUN - O
is VERB - O
important ADJ - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
therapy NOUN - O
management NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NN - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
the DET - O
first JJ - B-ORDINAL
drug NOUN - O
to PART - O
demonstrate VERB - O
a DET - O
survival NOUN - O
benefit NOUN - O
for ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
MDS NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NNP - B-MEDICINE
improves VERB - O
outcome NOUN - O
in ADP - O
higher ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
risk NOUN - O
MDS NNP - B-ORG
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
chromosome NOUN - O
7 CD - B-CARDINAL
abnormalities NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
retrospective ADJ - O
comparison NOUN - O
of ADP - O
GESMD NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
GFM NNP - B-ORG
registries NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NN - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
recommended VERB - O
front ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
line NOUN - O
treatment NOUN - O
for ADP - O
older ADJ - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
acute ADJ - O
myeloid ADJ - O
leukemia NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
AML NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
who NOUN - O
are VERB - O
not ADV - O
candidates NOUN - O
for ADP - O
intensive ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
regimens NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
was VERB - O
recently ADV - O
granted VERB - O
approval NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
European NNP - I-ORG
Union NNP - I-ORG
for ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
adult NOUN - O
AML NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Randomized PROPN - O
Phase PROPN - O
II PROPN - O
Study PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Azacitidine NNP - B-MEDICINE
Alone PROPN - O
or CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
Combination PROPN - O
With ADP - O
Lenalidomide PROPN - O
or CCONJ - O
With ADP - O
Vorinostat PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Higher ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
Risk NOUN - O
Myelodysplastic PROPN - O
Syndromes PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Chronic PROPN - O
Myelomonocytic PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Azacitidine NNP - B-MEDICINE
has VERB - O
become VERB - O
an DET - O
available ADJ - O
therapy NOUN - O
for ADP - O
high ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
risk NOUN - O
myelodysplastic ADJ - O
syndromes NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

KILT NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
Kidney NNP - B-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
IVC NNP - B-ORG
Abnormalities NNPS - I-ORG
with ADP - O
Leg NNP - B-PERSON
Thrombosis NNP - I-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
Syndrome VERB - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
41-Years CD - B-CARDINAL
- PUNCT - O
Old ADJ - O
Man NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Loin PROPN - O
Pain NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CC - I-MEDICINE
Fever NNP - I-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Felbamate VB - B-MEDICINE
as ADP - O
an DET - O
add NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
on PART - O
therapy NOUN - O
for ADP - O
refractory ADJ - O
epilepsy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Some DET - O
new ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
have VERB - O
proven VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
effective ADJ - O
in ADP - O
controlling VERB - O
the DET - O
disease NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Felbamate NNP - B-MEDICINE
, , - I-ORG
Lamotrigine NNP - I-ORG
, , - I-ORG
Topiramate NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Levetiracetam PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Felbamate VB - B-MEDICINE
leads VERB - O
to ADP - O
an DET - O
increase NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
responder NOUN - O
rate NOUN - O
after ADP - O
the DET - O
use NOUN - O
of ADP - O
KD NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Felbamate NNP - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
one NUM - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
second JJ - B-ORDINAL
generation NOUN - O
antiepileptic ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
its ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
as ADP - O
an DET - O
add VERB - O
- PUNCT - O
on PART - O
therapy NOUN - O
to ADP - O
standard ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
are VERB - O
assessed VERB - O
in ADP - O
this DET - O
review NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Felbamate VB - B-MEDICINE
as ADP - O
an DET - O
add NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
on PART - O
therapy NOUN - O
for ADP - O
refractory ADJ - O
epilepsy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Felbamate NNP - B-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
FBM NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
efficacious ADJ - O
in ADP - O
treating VERB - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
refractory ADJ - O
epilepsy NOUN - O
but CCONJ - O
was VERB - O
withdrawn VERB - O
due ADP - O
to ADP - O
cases NOUN - O
of ADP - O
aplastic ADJ - O
anaemia NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
hepatic ADJ - O
failure NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
five CD - B-CARDINAL
reported VERB - O
deaths NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Felbamate VB - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
an DET - O
adult NOUN - O
population NOUN - O
with ADP - O
severe ADJ - O
refractory ADJ - O
epilepsy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

No DET - O
Differences PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Weight PROPN - O
Gain NOUN - O
Between ADP - O
Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Aripiprazole PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Children PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Adolescents PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
2 NUM - O
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
d NOUN - O
was VERB - O
initiated VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
increased VERB - O
to ADP - O
4 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
d ADJ - O
54 CD - B-DATE
days NNS - I-DATE
later RB - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
one NUM - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
second JJ - B-ORDINAL
- PUNCT - O
generation NOUN - O
antipsychotics NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
can VERB - O
efficiently ADV - O
target VERB - O
dopamine NOUN - O
D2 NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
serotonin ADJ - O
5-HT2A PROPN - O
receptors NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Methods NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
widely ADV - O
used VERB - O
second JJ - B-ORDINAL
- PUNCT - O
generation NOUN - O
antipsychotic ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
haloperidol NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
representative ADJ - O
first JJ - B-ORDINAL
- PUNCT - O
generation NOUN - O
antipsychotic ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
were VERB - O
administered VERB - O
to ADP - O
pregnant ADJ - O
C57BL/6N PROPN - O
mice NOUN - O
from ADP - O
embryonic JJ - B-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
6 CD - I-DATE
to IN - I-DATE
16 CD - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Behavioral ADJ - O
Mechanisms PROPN - O
That ADJ - O
Depend VERB - O
on ADP - O
Dopamine PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Serotonin PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Caenorhabditis NNP - B-PRODUCT
elegans NOUN - O
Interact PROPN - O
With ADP - O
the DT - B-GPE
Antipsychotics NNP - I-GPE
Risperidone NNP - I-MEDICINE
and CC - I-GPE
Aripiprazole NNP - I-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Induced VERB - O
Tardive PROPN - O
Dyskinesia PROPN - O
in ADP - O
an DET - O
Autistic NNP - B-LOC
Child NNP - I-LOC
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Associated PROPN - O
Hyperprolactinemia PROPN - O
With ADP - O
Aripiprazole PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
Prospective ADJ - O
Study NOUN - O
to PART - O
Evaluate VERB - O
the DET - O
Effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
CYP2D6 NOUN - O
Polymorphism PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Plasma PROPN - O
level NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
its ADJ - O
Metabolite PROPN - O
in ADP - O
North JJ - B-GPE
Indian NNP - I-GPE
Patients NNPS - I-GPE
with ADP - O
Schizophrenia NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
not ADV - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
an DET - O
increased VERB - O
risk NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
could VERB - O
have VERB - O
potentially ADV - O
contributed VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
pulmonary ADJ - O
embolism NOUN - O
in ADP - O
our ADJ - O
patient NOUN - O
given VERB - O
the DET - O
temporal ADJ - O
association NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
absence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
risk NOUN - O
factors NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
for ADP - O
children NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
adolescents NOUN - O
with ADP - O
autism NOUN - O
spectrum NOUN - O
disorder NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
systematic ADJ - O
review NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
Provides VERB - O
Better PROPN - O
Improvement NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Sleep PROPN - O
Disturbances PROPN - O
Than ADP - O
Haloperidol PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Schizophrenia NNP - B-GPE
Patients NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Cannabis PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Positive PROPN - O
Urinalysis PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Selective ADJ - O
Serotonin PROPN - O
Reuptake VERB - O
Inhibitors NOUN - O
Reduce VERB - O
Longitudinal ADJ - O
Growth NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
Treated VERB - O
Boys NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
induced VERB - O
angioedema NOUN - O
with ADP - O
concurrent ADJ - O
EPS NNP - B-ORG
symptoms NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
report NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
review NOUN - O
of ADP - O
literature NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
associated VERB - O
sinus NOUN - O
tachycardia NOUN - O
potentiated VERB - O
by ADP - O
paliperidone NOUN - O
palmitate VERB - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
patient NOUN - O
with ADP - O
no DET - O
prior ADJ - O
cardiovascular ADJ - O
disease NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
role NOUN - O
of ADP - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
related VERB - O
autonomic ADJ - O
instability NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pretreatment NOUN - O
With ADP - O
Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Ameliorates PROPN - O
Systemic PROPN - O
LPS PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Induced PROPN - O
Oxidative PROPN - O
Stress NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
Cortex PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Hippocampus PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Injectable PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Patients PROPN - O
With ADP - O
Schizophrenia PROPN - O
With ADP - O
or CCONJ - O
Without ADP - O
Prior PROPN - O
Exposure NOUN - O
to ADP - O
Oral PROPN - O
Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
or CCONJ - O
Paliperidone NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
a DET - O
widely ADV - O
accessible ADJ - O
antipsychotic ADJ - O
that ADJ - O
can VERB - O
be VERB - O
used VERB - O
to PART - O
manage VERB - O
psychosis NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
aggression NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
agitation NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
versus ADP - O
haloperidol NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
up IN - B-TIME
to TO - I-TIME
24 CD - I-TIME
hours NNS - I-TIME
follow NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
up)For NOUN - O
the DET - O
outcome NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
specific ADJ - O
behaviour NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
agitation NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
no DET - O
clear ADJ - O
difference NOUN - O
was VERB - O
found VERB - O
between ADP - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
haloperidol NOUN - O
in ADP - O
terms NOUN - O
of ADP - O
efficacy NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
measured VERB - O
as ADP - O
at RB - B-PERCENT
least RBS - I-PERCENT
50 CD - I-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
reduction NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
Positive ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
Negative ADJ - O
Syndrome PROPN - O
Scale PROPN - O

Incidence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
adverse ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
was VERB - O
similar ADJ - O
between ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
groups NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
RR PROPN - O
0.94 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
95 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
CI PROPN - O
0.54 NUM - O
to ADP - O
1.66 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
participants NOUN - O
= SYM - O
124 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
studies NOUN - O
= SYM - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
very ADV - O
low ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
quality NOUN - O
evidence).Risperidone NOUN - O
versus ADP - O
olanzapineOne ADJ - O
small ADJ - O
trial NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
n NOUN - O
= SYM - O
29 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
reported VERB - O
useable ADJ - O
data NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
comparison NOUN - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
versus ADP - O
olanzapine NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

No DET - O
effect NOUN - O
was VERB - O
observed VERB - O
for ADP - O
agitation NOUN - O
measured VERB - O
as ADP - O
PANSS NN - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
PAS NN - I-ORG
endpoint NOUN - O
score NOUN - O
at ADP - O
two CD - B-TIME
hours NNS - I-TIME
( PUNCT - O
MD PROPN - O
2.50 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
95 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
CI NNP - B-ORG
-2.46 PUNCT - O
to ADP - O
7.46 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
very ADV - O
low ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
quality NOUN - O
evidence NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
; PUNCT - O
need VERB - O
to PART - O
use VERB - O
restraints NOUN - O
at ADP - O
four CD - B-DATE
days NNS - I-DATE
( PUNCT - O
RR PROPN - O
1.43 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
95 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
CI PROPN - O
0.39 NUM - O
to ADP - O
5.28 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
very ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
low ADJ - O
quality NOUN - O
evidence NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
; PUNCT - O
specific ADJ - O
movement NOUN - O
disorders NOUN - O
measured VERB - O
as ADP - O
Behavioural NNP - B-ORG
Activity NNP - I-ORG
Rating NNP - I-ORG
Scale NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
BARS NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
endpoint NOUN - O
score NOUN - O
at ADP - O
four CD - B-DATE
days NNS - I-DATE
( PUNCT - O
MD PROPN - O
0.20 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
95 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
CI NNP - B-ORG
-0.43 PROPN - O
to ADP - O
0.83 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
very ADV - O
low ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
quality NOUN - O
evidence).Risperidone NOUN - O
versus ADP - O
quetiapineOne PROPN - O
trial NOUN - O
reported VERB - O
( PUNCT - O
n NOUN - O
= SYM - O
40 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
useable ADJ - O
data NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
comparison NOUN - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
versus ADP - O
quetiapine NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
versus ADP - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
+ CCONJ - O
oxcarbazepineOne PROPN - O
trial NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
n NOUN - O
= SYM - O
68 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
measured VERB - O
agitation NOUN - O
using VERB - O
the DET - O
Positive ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
Negative ADJ - O
Syndrome PROPN - O
Scale PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Excited PROPN - O
Component.(PANSS PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
EC NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
endpoint NOUN - O
score NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
found VERB - O
a DET - O
clear ADJ - O
difference NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
favouring VERB - O
the DET - O
combination NOUN - O
treatment NOUN - O
at ADP - O
one CD - B-DATE
week NN - I-DATE
( PUNCT - O
MD PROPN - O
2.70 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
95 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
CI NNP - B-ORG
0.42 NUM - O
to ADP - O
4.98 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
very ADV - O
low ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
quality NOUN - O
evidence NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
no DET - O
effect NOUN - O
was VERB - O
observed VERB - O
for ADP - O
global ADJ - O
state NOUN - O
using VERB - O
Clinical NNP - B-ORG
Global NNP - I-ORG
Impression NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Improvement NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
CGI PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
I NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O

Incidence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
extrapyramidal ADJ - O
symptoms NOUN - O
after ADP - O
24 CD - B-TIME
hours NNS - I-TIME
was VERB - O
similar ADJ - O
between ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
groups NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
RR PROPN - O
1.59 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
95 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
CI NN - B-ORG
0.49 NUM - O
to ADP - O
5.14 CD - B-CARDINAL
; PUNCT - O
very ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
low ADJ - O
quality NOUN - O
evidence).Risperidone NOUN - O
versus ADP - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
+ CCONJ - O
valproic ADJ - O
acidTwo NOUN - O
trials NOUN - O
compared VERB - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
with ADP - O
a DET - O
combination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
plus CCONJ - O
valproic ADJ - O
acid NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Systemic PROPN - O
Inflammation PROPN - O
Complicates VERB - O
the DET - O
Interpretation PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Therapeutic ADJ - O
Drug PROPN - O
Monitoring PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
has VERB - O
shown VERB - O
promise NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
management NOUN - O
of ADP - O
chorea NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
found VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
safe ADJ - O
in ADP - O
children NOUN - O
less JJR - B-DATE
than IN - I-DATE
five CD - I-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

Risperidone NN - B-MEDICINE
is VERB - O
a DET - O
promising ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
to PART - O
manage VERB - O
children NOUN - O
with ADP - O
choreoathetoid ADJ - O
cerebral ADJ - O
palsy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
is VERB - O
well ADV - O
tolerated VERB - O
in ADP - O
children NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risperidone NNP - B-MEDICINE
Related PROPN - O
Raynaud PROPN - O
's PART - O
Phenomenon NN - B-WORK_OF_ART
: : - I-WORK_OF_ART
An NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
Adolescent NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
Case NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

We PRON - O
reconstructed VERB - O
realized VERB - O
pollen NOUN - O
flow NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
assessed ADJ - O
pollen NOUN - O
immigration NOUN - O
for ADP - O
seven CD - B-CARDINAL
populations NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
insect‐pollinated ADJ - O
herb NOUN - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
vulgaris NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Contemporary ADJ - O
pollen NOUN - O
flow NOUN - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
multiscale NOUN - O
process NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Evidence NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
insect‐pollinated ADJ - O
herb NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
vulgaris NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Comparative NNP - B-ORG
Analysis NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Complete PROPN - O
Chloroplast PROPN - O
Genomes PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Anemoclema NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Anemone PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Hepatica NNP - B-ORG
Revealing NNP - I-ORG
Structural NNP - I-ORG
Variations NNP - I-ORG
Among IN - I-ORG
Genera NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Tribe NNP - B-PERSON
Anemoneae NNP - I-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Ranunculaceae PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
tissue NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
smashing NOUN - O
based VERB - O
ultra ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
rapid ADJ - O
extraction NOUN - O
coupled VERB - O
with ADP - O
ultra ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
performance NOUN - O
liquid NOUN - O
chromatography NOUN - O
tandem NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
mass NOUN - O
spectrometry NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
UPLC NNP - B-ORG
- PUNCT - O
MS PROPN - O
/ SYM - O
MS PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
method NOUN - O
was VERB - O
developed VERB - O
to PART - O
determine VERB - O
10 CD - B-CARDINAL
major ADJ - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
herbs NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Moreover ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
hierarchical ADJ - O
cluster NOUN - O
analysis NOUN - O
was VERB - O
performed VERB - O
to PART - O
compare VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
discriminate VERB - O
the DET - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
herbs NOUN - O
based VERB - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
quantitative ADJ - O
data NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
hierarchical ADJ - O
cluster NOUN - O
analysis NOUN - O
results NOUN - O
demonstrated VERB - O
that ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O

Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
cernua NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
dahurica NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
turczainovii NOUN - O
samples NOUN - O
could VERB - O
be VERB - O
easily ADV - O
discriminated VERB - O
from ADP - O
each DET - O
other ADJ - O
based VERB - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
contents NOUN - O
of ADP - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
established VERB - O
method NOUN - O
is VERB - O
feasible ADJ - O
for ADP - O
quality NOUN - O
control NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
herbs NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
decoction NOUN - O
inhibits VERB - O
Candida PROPN - O
albicans NOUN - O
proliferation NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
adhesion NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
mouse NOUN - O
model NOUN - O
of ADP - O
vulvovaginal ADJ - O
candidiasis NOUN - O
via ADP - O
the DET - O
Dectin-1 NNP - B-ORG
signaling NOUN - O
pathway NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

, PUNCT - O
isolated VERB - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
rhizosphere NOUN - O
soil NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
led VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
isolation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
four CD - B-CARDINAL
new ADJ - O
hybrid ADJ - O
polyketide NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
terpenoid NOUN - O
metabolites NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
- SYM - O
4 NUM - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
together ADV - O
with ADP - O
fourteen CD - B-CARDINAL
known VERB - O
compounds NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
5 CD - B-CARDINAL
- SYM - O
18 NUM - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Application NOUN - O
of ADP - O
linear ADJ - O
gradient NOUN - O
elution NOUN - O
in ADP - O
countercurrent NOUN - O
chromatography NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
separation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NN - I-ORG
Nakai NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Study VERB - O
on ADP - O
morphological ADJ - O
characteristics NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
microscopic ADJ - O
structure NOUN - O
of ADP - O
medicinal ADJ - O
organs NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Bunge PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
Regel NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
the DET - O
present ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
anticancer NOUN - O
activity NOUN - O
of ADP - O
an DET - O
active ADJ - O
compound NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
extracts NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin VERB - O
A NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PsA NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
was VERB - O
isolated VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
examined VERB - O
in ADP - O
vitro NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
vivo NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Ultra ADJ - O
high ADJ - O
performance NOUN - O
liquid NOUN - O
chromatography NOUN - O
coupled VERB - O
with ADP - O
mass NOUN - O
spectrometry NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
combining VERB - O
a DET - O
tissue NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
smashing VERB - O
extraction NOUN - O
technique NOUN - O
was VERB - O
developed VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
simultaneous ADJ - O
quantitative ADJ - O
analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
12 CD - B-CARDINAL
compounds NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rapidly ADV - O
discriminate VERB - O
commercial ADJ - O
medicinal ADJ - O
Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Bge PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Baitouweng NNP - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
Root PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
commonly ADV - O
used VERB - O
traditional ADJ - O
Chinese JJ - B-NORP
medicine NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
was VERB - O
first ADV - O
recorded VERB - O
in ADP - O
Shen NNP - B-PERSON

( PUNCT - O
Bunge NNP - B-ORG
) -RRB- - I-ORG
Regel NNP - I-ORG
from IN - I-ORG
Ranunculaceae NNP - B-GPE
had VERB - O
become VERB - O
the DET - O
authentic ADJ - O
source NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
Baitouweng NNP - B-PERSON
since ADP - O
the DT - B-DATE
Song NNP - I-DATE
Dynasty NNP - I-DATE
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
was VERB - O
consistent ADJ - O
with ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Radix NNP - I-ORG
Pulsatillae NNP - I-ORG
collected VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Chinese NNP - I-ORG
Pharmacopoeia NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
Textual ADJ - O
research NOUN - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
origin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
producing VERB - O
area NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Baitouweng NNP - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
Radix PROPN - O
Pulsatillae)]. PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Comparative ADJ - O
pharmacokinetic ADJ - O
profiles NOUN - O
of ADP - O
five CD - B-CARDINAL
poorly ADV - O
soluble ADJ - O
pulchinenosides NOUN - O
in ADP - O
different ADJ - O
formulations NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
saponins VERB - O
extracts VERB - O
for ADP - O
enhanced ADJ - O
bioavailability NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
patens VERB - O
s.s PRON - O
. PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
one CD - B-CARDINAL
of ADP - O
the DET - O
most ADV - O
endangered ADJ - O
plant NOUN - O
species NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Europe NNP - B-LOC
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

the DET - O
Rare PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Endangered PROPN - O
Plant PROPN - O
Species PROPN - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
patens VERB - O
( PUNCT - O
L. NNP - B-ORG
) -RRB- - I-ORG
Mill NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
East NNP - B-LOC
Central NNP - I-LOC
Europe NNP - I-LOC
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Preparation NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
characterization NOUN - O
of ADP - O
colon NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
targeted VERB - O
particles NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Since ADP - O
these DET - O
natural ADJ - O
products NOUN - O
represented VERB - O
by ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin NOUN - O
D NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PSD PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
were VERB - O
obtained VERB - O
in ADP - O
very ADV - O
small ADJ - O
amounts NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
total ADJ - O
synthesis NOUN - O
developed VERB - O
in ADP - O
this DET - O
paper NOUN - O
will VERB - O
resolve VERB - O
this DET - O
problem NOUN - O
of ADP - O
scarcity NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
Study NOUN - O
on ADP - O
seeds NOUN - O
after ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
ripening VERB - O
regulation NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
key ADJ - O
techniques NOUN - O
for ADP - O
seedling NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
cernua]. VERB - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
this DET - O
regard NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
SB365 NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
saponin ADJ - O
D NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
root NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
which ADJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
used VERB - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
traditional ADJ - O
medicine NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Korea NNP - B-GPE
for ADP - O
several ADJ - O
diseases NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
attracted VERB - O
wide ADJ - O
interest NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

SB365 NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin ADJ - O
D NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
suppresses VERB - O
the DET - O
growth NOUN - O
of ADP - O
gefitinib NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
resistant ADJ - O
NSCLC NNP - B-ORG
cells NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Met NNP - B-GPE
amplification NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
Intestinal ADJ - O
absorption NOUN - O
of ADP - O
pulchinenosides NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
in ADP - O
rats]. ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
this DET - O
study NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
we PRON - O
isolated VERB - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin NOUN - O
A NOUN - O
as ADP - O
an DET - O
active ADJ - O
compound NOUN - O
from ADP - O
P NOUN - O
chinensis NOUN - O
extracts NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
tested VERB - O
its ADJ - O
anticancer NOUN - O
activity NOUN - O
in ADP - O
  SPACE - O
vitro NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
  SPACE - O
vivo NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

In ADP - O
cell NOUN - O
culture NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin VERB - O
A DET - O
significantly ADV - O
inhibited VERB - O
the DET - O
growth NOUN - O
of ADP - O
human ADJ - O
hepatocellular ADJ - O
carcinoma NOUN - O
SMCC-7721 IN - B-PRODUCT
cells NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
pancreatic ADJ - O
BXPC3 NNP - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
SW1990 NNP - B-PRODUCT
cancer NOUN - O
cells NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

In ADP - O
Comet NNP - B-ORG
assay VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
flow VERB - O
cytometric ADJ - O
analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
cell NOUN - O
cycle NOUN - O
distribution NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
annexin NOUN - O
V NOUN - O
expression NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
DNA NOUN - O
damage NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
G2 NN - B-ORG
arrest NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
apoptosis NOUN - O
were VERB - O
identified VERB - O
in ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin ADJ - O
A NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
cancer NOUN - O
cells NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Based VERB - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
results NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Western ADJ - O
blotting NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
p53 NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
cyclin NOUN - O
B PROPN - O
protein NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
were VERB - O
higher ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
whereas ADP - O
Bcl-2 ADJ - O
protein NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
were VERB - O
lower ADJ - O
in ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin VERB - O
A NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
cancer NOUN - O
cells NOUN - O
than ADP - O
in ADP - O
vehicle NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
cells NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Pulsatilla RB - B-MEDICINE
saponin VERB - O
A NOUN - O
may VERB - O
exert VERB - O
its ADJ - O
antitumor NOUN - O
effect NOUN - O
by ADP - O
inducing VERB - O
DNA NOUN - O
damage NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
causing VERB - O
G2 NOUN - O
arrest NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
apoptosis NOUN - O
in ADP - O
cancer NOUN - O
cells NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Pulsatilla RB - B-MEDICINE
saponin VERB - O
A NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
its ADJ - O
derivatives NOUN - O
may VERB - O
be VERB - O
developed VERB - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
new ADJ - O
class NOUN - O
of ADP - O
anticancer ADJ - O
agents NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Cytotoxicity PROPN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
compounds NOUN - O
isolated VERB - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
apoptosis NOUN - O
induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
23-hydroxybetulinic CD - B-CARDINAL
acid NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Sortase VERB - O
A DET - O
inhibitory NOUN - O
metabolites VERB - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
relationship NOUN - O
between ADP - O
climatic ADJ - O
conditions NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
generative ADJ - O
reproduction NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
lowland NOUN - O
population NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
vernalis NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
the DET - O
last ADJ - O
breath NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
relict ADJ - O
plant NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
a DET - O
fluctuating ADJ - O
cycle NOUN - O
of ADP - O
regeneration NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
this DET - O
study NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
23 CD - B-CARDINAL
oleanane ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
type NOUN - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
were VERB - O
isolated VERB - O
from ADP - O
a DET - O
methanol NOUN - O
extract NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Validated VERB - O
rapid ADJ - O
resolution NOUN - O
LC NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
ESI NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
MS NNP - I-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
MS NNP - I-ORG
method VERB - O
for ADP - O
simultaneous ADJ - O
determination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
five CD - B-CARDINAL
pulchinenosides NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

SB365 NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin NOUN - O
D NOUN - O
isolated VERB - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
root NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
exhibited VERB - O
potential ADJ - O
beneficial ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
chemopreventive ADJ - O
agent NOUN - O
for ADP - O
critical ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
conditions NOUN - O
including VERB - O
cancer NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

SB365 NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
saponin ADJ - O
D NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
targets VERB - O
c NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
Met PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
exerts VERB - O
antiangiogenic ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
antitumor NOUN - O
activities NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
aim NOUN - O
of ADP - O
this DET - O
article NOUN - O
is VERB - O
to PART - O
establish VERB - O
a DET - O
risk NOUN - O
assessment NOUN - O
procedure NOUN - O
without ADP - O
full ADJ - O
toxicological ADJ - O
examination NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
using VERB - O
homeopathic ADJ - O
preparations NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
pratensis NN - I-PERSON
L. NNP - B-PERSON
as ADP - O
an DET - O
example NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

First JJ - B-ORG
Report NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Root NNP - I-ORG
Rot NNP - I-ORG
on ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
Caused VERB - O
by ADP - O
Fusarium PROPN - O
oxysporum NOUN - O
in ADP - O
China NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
homeopathic ADJ - O
preparation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
nigricans NOUN - O
is VERB - O
used VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
anxiety NOUN - O
related VERB - O
disorders NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Though ADP - O
in ADP - O
clinical ADJ - O
use NOUN - O
for ADP - O
many JJ - B-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
anxiolytic ADJ - O
activity NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
nigricans NNS - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
Puls NNP - B-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
not ADV - O
been VERB - O
evaluated VERB - O
experimentally ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
study NOUN - O
showed VERB - O
an DET - O
anxiolytic ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
homeopathic ADJ - O
preparation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
nigricans NOUN - O
comparable ADJ - O
to ADP - O
that DET - O
found VERB - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
standard ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
nigricans NOUN - O
extract VERB - O
in ADP - O
arsenic ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
DNA NOUN - O
damage NOUN - O
in ADP - O
testis ADJ - O
cells NOUN - O
of ADP - O
mice NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Isolation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
nematicidal ADJ - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
root NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
their ADJ - O
activities NOUN - O
against ADP - O
Meloidogyne NNP - B-ORG
incognita NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pulsatilla NN - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
medicinal ADJ - O
root NOUN - O
plant NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
used VERB - O
to PART - O
treat VERB - O
a DET - O
wide ADJ - O
range NOUN - O
of ADP - O
disease NOUN - O
conditions NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
this DET - O
research NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
we PRON - O
evaluated VERB - O
the DET - O
inhibitory ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
polysaccharides NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PCPS PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
on ADP - O
glioma NOUN - O
in ADP - O
vivo NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
vitro NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Vero NOUN - O
cells NOUN - O
infected VERB - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
Korean NNP - B-ORG
CVA16 NNP - I-ORG
isolate VERB - O
showed VERB - O
a DET - O
cytopathic ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
2 CD - B-DATE
days NNS - I-DATE
after ADP - O
the DET - O
infection NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
cells NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Cornus NNPS - B-ORG
officinalis ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
Acer NNP - B-ORG
triflorum NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Clematis NNP - B-PRODUCT
heracleifolia NOUN - O
var NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antitumor ADJ - O
activity NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
the DET - O
present ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
quinone NOUN - O
reductase NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
QR PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
inducing VERB - O
activities NOUN - O
of ADP - O
nine CD - B-CARDINAL
known ADJ - O
triterpene NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
dichloromethane NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
ethanol NOUN - O
extract NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
were VERB - O
tested VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pulsatilla RB - B-MEDICINE
koreana VERB - O
             SPACE - O
extract NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PKE NN - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
used VERB - O
to PART - O
treat VERB - O
malaria NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
dysentery NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
Molecular ADJ - O
mechanisms NOUN - O
involved VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
inflammatory ADJ - O
bowel NOUN - O
disease NOUN - O
by ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
decoction]. NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Anatomical ADJ - O
structure NOUN - O
comparison NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
barbloin VERB - O
histochemical ADJ - O
localization NOUN - O
of ADP - O
wild ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
cultivated VERB - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Ranunculaceae NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
essential ADJ - O
oil NOUN - O
obtained VERB - O
by ADP - O
hydrodistillation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
aerial ADJ - O
flowering VERB - O
parts NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
albana NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Stev PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
extraction NOUN - O
condition NOUN - O
of ADP - O
total ADJ - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
cenua NN - I-ORG
by ADP - O
ultrasonic ADJ - O
wave NOUN - O
was VERB - O
optimized VERB - O
by ADP - O
single ADJ - O
factor NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
orthogonal ADJ - O
experiments NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
content NOUN - O
of ADP - O
total ADJ - O
saponins NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
cernua NOUN - O
was VERB - O
4 CD - B-CARDINAL
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
Optimization NOUN - O
of ADP - O
extraction NOUN - O
technics NOUN - O
of ADP - O
total ADJ - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
cernua]. VERB - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Quality NOUN - O
control NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
koreana NOUN - O
based VERB - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
simultaneous ADJ - O
determination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
triterpenoidal NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
by ADP - O
HPLC NNP - B-ORG
- PUNCT - O
ELSD PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
principal ADJ - O
component NOUN - O
analysis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
Protein NOUN - O
analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Trichomonas NNP - B-GPE
vaginalis NOUN - O
treated VERB - O
by ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
in ADP - O
vitro]. ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

For ADP - O
preventive ADJ - O
treatments NOUN - O
in ADP - O
hay NOUN - O
fever NOUN - O
patients NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Arsenicum NNP - B-ORG
album NOUN - O
was VERB - O
the DET - O
most ADV - O
effective ADJ - O
homeopathic NOUN - O
medicine NOUN - O
followed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Nux PROPN - O
vomica NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
pratensis NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Gelsemium NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Sarsaparilla NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Silicea NNP - B-GPE
and CCONJ - O
Natrum NNP - B-ORG
muriaticum NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Isolation NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
evaluation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
immunological ADJ - O
adjuvant ADJ - O
activities NOUN - O
of ADP - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
with ADP - O
less ADJ - O
adverse ADJ - O
reactions NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
new ADJ - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponin NOUN - O
was VERB - O
isolated VERB - O
from ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
cernua NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
along ADP - O
with ADP - O
eight CD - B-CARDINAL
known VERB - O
triterpenoids NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
glycosides NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pre- NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
postinterventional ADJ - O
variability NOUN - O
spectra NOUN - O
of ADP - O
heart NOUN - O
rate NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
blood NOUN - O
flow NOUN - O
of ADP - O
77 CD - B-CARDINAL
subjects NOUN - O
were VERB - O
recorded VERB - O
with ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Medical NNP - I-ORG
Analyzer NNP - I-ORG
System NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
administering VERB - O
homeopathic ADJ - O
preparations NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Aconitum NNP - B-NORP
napellus NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
6c NUM - O
, PUNCT - O
10 NUM - O
M PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
Arsenicum NNP - B-ORG
album NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
200c CD - B-ORDINAL
, PUNCT - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
M PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
Gelsemium PROPN - O
sempervirens NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
200c CD - B-ORDINAL
, PUNCT - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
M PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
Phosphorus NNP - B-GPE
( PUNCT - O
200c CD - B-ORDINAL
, PUNCT - O
1 NUM - O
M PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
nigricans NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
200c NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Sulphur NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
200c NUM - O
, PUNCT - O
1 NUM - O
M NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
versus ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
control NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Sulphur NNP - B-PERSON
200c NNP - I-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
1 CD - B-QUANTITY
M NNP - I-QUANTITY
, PUNCT - O
Gelsemium PROPN - O
200c PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
200c PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
produced VERB - O
a DET - O
62.5 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
response NOUN - O
in ADP - O
HRV NNP - B-ORG
against ADP - O
the DET - O
placebo NOUN - O
response NOUN - O
of ADP - O
16.6 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
East JJ - B-NORP
Asian JJ - I-NORP
traditional ADJ - O
medicine NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
Pulsatillae NNP - B-ORG
Radix NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
PR PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
widely ADV - O
used VERB - O
to PART - O
treat VERB - O
amoebic ADJ - O
dysentery NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
renowned VERB - O
for ADP - O
its ADJ - O
anti ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
inflammatory ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
first JJ - B-ORDINAL
synthesis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
natural ADJ - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
were VERB - O
isolated VERB - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
exhibited VERB - O
excellent NOUN - O
in ADP - O
vitro X - O
cytotoxic ADJ - O
activity NOUN - O
against ADP - O
HL-60 NNP - B-ORG
cells NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
was VERB - O
concisely ADV - O
achieved VERB - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
convergent ADJ - O
approach NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Concise ADJ - O
synthesis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
natural ADJ - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
oleanolic ADJ - O
acid NOUN - O
derivatives NOUN - O
isolated VERB - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
floral ADJ - O
development NOUN - O
of ADP - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
Clematis NNP - B-ORG
species NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
four CD - B-CARDINAL
Anemone NNP - B-ORG
species NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
including VERB - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
( PUNCT - O
Anemoneae NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Ranunculaceae NNP - B-GPE
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
described VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

In ADP - O
Anemone NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
perianth JJ - B-ORDINAL
organs NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
if ADP - O
five CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
are VERB - O
initiated VERB - O
in ADP - O
spiral ADJ - O
sequence NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
group NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Anemone NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
six CD - B-CARDINAL
sepals NOUN - O
are VERB - O
initiated VERB - O
in ADP - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
whorls NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
the DET - O
first JJ - B-ORDINAL
three CD - B-CARDINAL
organs NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
androecium NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
staminodes NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
alternate ADJ - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
inner ADJ - O
sepals NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

In ADP - O
contrast NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
group NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Anemone NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
these DET - O
organs NOUN - O
retain VERB - O
sterile ADJ - O
anthers NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
become VERB - O
small ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
capitate VERB - O
organs NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

For ADP - O
detection NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
differentiation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
types NOUN - O
of ADP - O
triterpenoid NOUN - O
saponins NOUN - O
based VERB - O
on ADP - O
different ADJ - O
aglycons NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
lupane NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
oleanane ADJ - O
skeleton NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O

Diagnostic ADJ - O
fragmentation NOUN - O
pathways NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
silver ADJ - O
complexes NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
saponins NOUN - O
allow VERB - O
successful ADJ - O
identification NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
types NOUN - O
of ADP - O
saponins NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
roots NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Pulsatilla NNP - B-MEDICINE
chinensis NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Bunge PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
Regel NNP - B-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Re ADP - O
: PUNCT - O
Comparison NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Efficacy PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Isosorbide NNP - B-MEDICINE
Mononitrate NNP - I-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Doxazosin PROPN - O
in ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Treatment NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Lower NNP - I-ORG
Urinary NNP - I-ORG
Tract VBP - I-ORG
Symptoms NNPS - B-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Benign NNP - B-ORG
Prostatic NNP - I-ORG
Hyperplasia NNP - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
Randomized VBN - B-ORG
Clinical NNP - I-ORG
Trial NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Isosorbide NNP - B-FAC
Mononitrate NNP - I-FAC
( PUNCT - O
ISMN NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
an DET - O
anti ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
anginal ADJ - O
organic ADJ - O
nitrate NOUN - O
vasodilator NOUN - O
used VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
various ADJ - O
cardiovascular ADJ - O
disorders NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
prophylaxis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
angina ADJ - O
Pectoris NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
poorly ADV - O
absorbed VERB - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
upper ADJ - O
GIT NN - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
hence ADV - O
CR NNP - B-GPE
formulation NOUN - O
is VERB - O
desirable ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Randomized NNP - B-ORG
Comparison NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Isosorbide NNP - I-ORG
Mononitrate NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
PGE2 PROPN - O
Gel PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Cervical PROPN - O
Ripening PROPN - O
at ADP - O
Term PROPN - O
including VERB - O
High PROPN - O
Risk PROPN - O
Pregnancy PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
expansion NOUN - O
of ADP - O
pulse NOUN - O
pressure NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PP NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
the DET - O
individual ADJ - O
dangerous ADJ - O
cardiovascular NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
CV NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
factor NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
by ADP - O
integrating VERB - O
Isosorbide NNP - B-ORG
Mononitrate PROPN - O
with ADP - O
other ADJ - O
hypertension NOUN - O
resisting VERB - O
medicaments NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
good ADJ - O
clinic NOUN - O
curative ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
is VERB - O
obtained VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
synergy VERB - O
effect NOUN - O
is VERB - O
achieved VERB - O
in ADP - O
terms NOUN - O
of ADP - O
reduction NOUN - O
of ADP - O
contraction NOUN - O
pressure NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
wherein ADV - O
the DET - O
combination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
calcium NOUN - O
ion NOUN - O
antagonist NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
rennin NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
angiotensins NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
aldosterone NOUN - O
system NOUN - O
antagon NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
blood NOUN - O
vessel NOUN - O
expanding VERB - O
agent NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
epinephrine NOUN - O
acceptor NOUN - O
retarding VERB - O
agent NOUN - O
can VERB - O
make VERB - O
the DET - O
most ADV - O
ideal ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Silver NNP - B-MEDICINE
Sulfadiazine NNP - I-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Cerium PROPN - O
Nitrate PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Ischemic NNP - B-ORG
Skin NNP - I-ORG
Necrosis NN - I-ORG
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Leg PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Foot PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
Results NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
Prospective PROPN - O
Randomized VERB - O
Controlled PROPN - O
Study PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Silver NNP - B-ORG
Sulfadiazine NNP - I-ORG
Encapsulated VBN - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Lipid PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Based VERB - O
Nanocarriers PROPN - O
for ADP - O
Burn PROPN - O
Treatment PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
aim NOUN - O
of ADP - O
this DET - O
systematic ADJ - O
review NOUN - O
with ADP - O
meta ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
analysis NOUN - O
was VERB - O
to PART - O
compare VERB - O
the DET - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Silver NNP - B-ORG
Sulfadiazine NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
SSD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
other ADJ - O
new ADJ - O
dressings NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
or CCONJ - O
without ADP - O
silver NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
on ADP - O
healing NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
infection NOUN - O
prevention NOUN - O
in ADP - O
burns NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Inhibition NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Tyrosine PROPN - O
Hydroxylase PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Dopaminergic PROPN - O
Neurons PROPN - O
after ADP - O
Treatment PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Paroxetine NNP - B-MEDICINE
but CCONJ - O
Not ADV - O
with ADP - O
Agomelatine PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Male PROPN - O
Rats PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
one NUM - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
selective ADJ - O
serotonin NOUN - O
reuptake VERB - O
inhibitors NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
SSRIs NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
widely ADV - O
prescribed VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
depression NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
anxiety NOUN - O
disorders NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
displayed VERB - O
both DET - O
quasi ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
irreversible ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
irreversible ADJ - O
MDI NN - B-PRODUCT
of ADP - O
CYP2D6 NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
formation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
CYP NNP - B-ORG
- PUNCT - O
dependent ADJ - O
GSH NNP - B-ORG
adducts NOUN - O
was VERB - O
observed VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
while ADP - O
CYP NNP - B-ORG
- PUNCT - O
mediated VERB - O
covalent NOUN - O
binding VERB - O
occurred VERB - O
which ADJ - O
was VERB - O
decreased VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
presence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
GSH NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
ameliorates VERB - O
whole ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
body NOUN - O
allodynia NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Neuroprotective NNP - B-ORG
Effect NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Paroxetine NNP - I-MEDICINE
on IN - I-ORG
Memory NOUN - O
Deficit PROPN - O
Induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
Cerebral NNP - B-ORG
Ischemia NNP - I-ORG
after IN - I-ORG
Transient NNP - I-ORG
Bilateral NNP - I-ORG
Occlusion NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Common NNP - I-ORG
Carotid NNP - I-ORG
Arteries NNPS - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Rat PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
also ADV - O
significantly ADV - O
inhibited VERB - O
the DET - O
increase NOUN - O
of ADP - O
tail NOUN - O
skin NOUN - O
temperature NOUN - O
by ADP - O
yohimbine NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
Efficacy PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Safety PROPN - O
of ADP - O
On PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
demand NOUN - O
Tramadol PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Paroxetine NNP - B-MEDICINE
Use PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Treatment PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Life PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
markedly ADV - O
effective ADJ - O
in ADP - O
50 CD - B-CARDINAL
patients NOUN - O
who NOUN - O
also ADV - O
displayed VERB - O
an DET - O
increased VERB - O
level NOUN - O
of ADP - O
miRNA-451a NOUN - O
but CCONJ - O
reduced ADJ - O
levels NOUN - O
of ADP - O
miRNA-34a-5p ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
miRNA-221 NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
3p NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
blocks VERB - O
the DET - O
human ADJ - O
ether NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
a DET - O
- PUNCT - O
go NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
go NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
related VERB - O
gene NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
HERG PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
channels NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
was VERB - O
started VERB - O
at ADP - O
5 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
evening NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
intention NOUN - O
of ADP - O
titrating VERB - O
up PART - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Development PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Paroxetine NNP - B-MEDICINE
Hydrochloride NNP - I-ORG
Single PROPN - O
Layer PROPN - O
Controlled PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Release PROPN - O
Tablets NOUN - O
Based VERB - O
on ADP - O
3² CD - B-CARDINAL
Factorial NNP - B-LOC
Design NNP - I-LOC
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Therapeutic ADJ - O
Drug PROPN - O
Monitoring PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Fluoxetine PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Norfluoxetine NNP - B-NORP
and CCONJ - O
Paroxetine NNP - B-MEDICINE
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Early ADJ - O
Improvement NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Marriage NOUN - O
Are VERB - O
Determinants NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
12-Month NUM - O
Treatment PROPN - O
Outcome PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Paroxetine NNP - B-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
Outpatients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Panic JJ - B-ORG
Disorder NN - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paroxetine NN - B-MEDICINE
- PUNCT - O
induced VERB - O
multifocal ADJ - O
fixed VERB - O
drug NOUN - O
rash NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
An DET - O
incident NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
hitherto ADV - O
unreported ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Synthesis PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Activity NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Polyethylene NNP - I-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
Chlorhexidine NNP - I-ORG
/ SYM - I-ORG
Vermiculite NNP - I-ORG
Nanocomposites NNPS - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Activities PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Tea PROPN - O
Polyphenol PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Phytopathogens NNP - B-ORG
: : - I-ORG
A NNP - I-ORG
Review NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Long PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Term PROPN - O
Effects PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Phased PROPN - O
Implementation PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Stewardship PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Academic PROPN - O
ICUs NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
2007 CD - B-DATE
- SYM - I-DATE
2015 CD - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
susceptibility NOUN - O
was VERB - O
tested VERB - O
by ADP - O
gradient ADJ - O
diffusion NOUN - O
tests NOUN - O
on ADP - O
buffered ADJ - O
charcoal NOUN - O
yeast NOUN - O
extract VERB - O
agar ADJ - O
medium NOUN - O
supplemented VERB - O
with ADP - O
α NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
ketoglutarate NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
BCYE NNP - B-PRODUCT
- HYPH - I-PRODUCT
α NNP - I-PRODUCT
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
a DET - O
subgroup NOUN - O
of ADP - O
strains NOUN - O
were VERB - O
whole ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
genome ADJ - O
sequenced ADJ - O
using VERB - O
Illumina NNP - B-NORP
technology NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
analysed VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
susceptibility NOUN - O
was VERB - O
tested VERB - O
using VERB - O
the DET - O
agar ADJ - O
dilution NOUN - O
method NOUN - O
according VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
CLSI NNP - B-ORG
guidelines NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Understanding VERB - O
the DET - O
Components PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Calculation PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Impact NN - B-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Monthly NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Seasonal NNP - B-ORG
Variation NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
the DT - I-ORG
Standardized NNP - I-ORG
Antimicrobial NNP - I-MEDICINE
Utilization NNP - I-ORG
Ratio NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
SAAR PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
resistance NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
AMR NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
major ADJ - O
public ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
problem NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
requires VERB - O
publicly ADV - O
available ADJ - O
tools NOUN - O
for ADP - O
rapid ADJ - O
analysis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Currently ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
the DT - B-ORG
Bacterial NNP - I-ORG
Antimicrobial NNP - I-MEDICINE
Resistance NNP - I-ORG
Reference NNP - I-ORG
Gene NNP - I-ORG
Database NNP - I-ORG
contains VERB - O
4,579 CD - B-CARDINAL
antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
resistance NOUN - O
gene NOUN - O
proteins NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
more JJR - B-CARDINAL
than IN - I-CARDINAL
560 CD - I-CARDINAL
HMMs NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

To PART - O
assess VERB - O
the DET - O
predictive ADJ - O
ability NOUN - O
of ADP - O
AMRFinder NNP - B-PRODUCT
, PUNCT - O
we PRON - O
measured VERB - O
the DET - O
consistency NOUN - O
between ADP - O
predicted VERB - O
AMR NNP - B-ORG
genotypes NOUN - O
from ADP - O
AMRFinder NNP - B-ORG
against ADP - O
resistance NOUN - O
phenotypes NOUN - O
of ADP - O
6,242 CD - B-CARDINAL
isolates NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DT - B-EVENT
National NNP - I-EVENT
Antimicrobial NNP - I-MEDICINE
Resistance NNP - I-EVENT
Monitoring NNP - I-EVENT
System NNP - I-EVENT
( PUNCT - O
NARMS NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
resistance NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
AMR NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
among ADP - O
gram NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
negative ADJ - O
bacilli NOUN - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
global ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
problem NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
stewardship NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
an DET - O
evaluation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
structure NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
process NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
their ADJ - O
association NOUN - O
with ADP - O
antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
prescribing NOUN - O
in ADP - O
NHS NNP - B-ORG
hospitals NOUN - O
in ADP - O
England NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Peptide NN - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Stabilized VBN - I-ORG
Emulsions NNPS - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Gels NNPS - B-PERSON
from ADP - O
an DET - O
Arginine PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
Rich PROPN - O
Surfactant PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
like ADP - O
Peptide PROPN - O
with ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Activity PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
peptides NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
particular ADJ - O
α NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
defensins NOUN - O
expressed VERB - O
by ADP - O
Paneth NNP - B-PERSON
cells NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
control NOUN - O
microbiota NOUN - O
composition NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
play VERB - O
a DET - O
key ADJ - O
role NOUN - O
in ADP - O
intestinal ADJ - O
barrier NOUN - O
function NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
homeostasis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

One CD - B-CARDINAL
Health NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Its PRP$ - I-ORG
Importance NN - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Helping VERB - O
to ADP - O
Better PROPN - O
Control PROPN - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Resistance PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
activities NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
B PROPN - O
/ SYM - O
F PROPN - O
by ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
products NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
LAB NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
thirteen CD - B-CARDINAL
LAB NNP - B-ORG
strains NOUN - O
were VERB - O
estimated VERB - O
against ADP - O
fifteen CD - B-CARDINAL
pathogenic ADJ - O
strains NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
were VERB - O
evaluated VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
while ADP - O
whey NOUN - O
substrate VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
selected VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
highest ADJ - O
antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
activities NOUN - O
showing VERB - O
LAB NNP - B-ORG
cultivation NOUN - O
was VERB - O
used VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Role PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Polydopamine NNP - B-ORG
's PART - O
Redox NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Activity NNP - I-ORG
on ADP - O
its ADJ - O
Pro JJ - B-ORG
- ADJ - O
oxidant ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
Radical NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Scavenging NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Activities NNPS - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Resistance NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Prevalence PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Resistance NNP - B-ORG
Genes NNPS - I-ORG
and CC - I-ORG
Molecular PROPN - O
Characterization PROPN - O
in ADP - O
intestinal ADJ - O
Bacteroides NNPS - B-PERSON
fragilis NOUN - O
group NOUN - O
isolates VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Magneto NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Priming NN - I-ORG
Improved VBN - I-ORG
Nutraceutical NNP - I-ORG
Potential PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Activity PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Momordica PROPN - O
charantia VERB - O
L. NNP - B-PERSON
Without IN - I-PERSON
Affecting VERB - O
Nutritive NNP - B-ORG
Value NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

From ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
to ADP - O
Anticancer PROPN - O
Peptides PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
The DET - O
Transformation PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Peptides PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
susceptibility NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Burkholderia NNP - B-GPE
pseudomallei NOUN - O
isolates NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DT - B-LOC
Northern NNP - I-LOC
Vietnam NNP - I-LOC
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
consumption NOUN - O
in ADP - O
five CD - B-CARDINAL
adult NOUN - O
intensive ADJ - O
care NOUN - O
units NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
33-month CD - B-PRODUCT
surveillance NOUN - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
susceptibility NOUN - O
to PART - O
erythromycin VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
ciprofloxacin PROPN - O
was VERB - O
tested VERB - O
in ADP - O
430 CD - B-CARDINAL
clinical ADJ - O
isolates NOUN - O
of ADP - O
C. NNP - B-ORG
jejuni PROPN - O
collected VERB - O
over IN - B-DATE
18 CD - I-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
in ADP - O
a DET - O
Tokyo NNP - B-GPE
general ADJ - O
hospital NOUN - O
between IN - B-DATE
2000 CD - I-DATE
and CC - I-DATE
2017 CD - I-DATE
using VERB - O
the DET - O
broth NOUN - O
microdilution NOUN - O
method NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Engineering PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Surfaces PROPN - O
by ADP - O
Using VERB - O
Temporin PROPN - O
Analogs PROPN - O
to ADP - O
Tune NNP - B-PERSON
the DT - I-PERSON
Biocidal NNP - I-PERSON
/ SYM - O
antiadhesive ADJ - O
Effect PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
resistance NOUN - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
growing VERB - O
problem NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
need NOUN - O
for ADP - O
' PUNCT - O
strong ADJ - O
action NOUN - O
' PUNCT - O
highlighted VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DET - O
Chief NNP - B-ORG
Medical NNP - I-ORG
Officer PROPN - O
for ADP - O
England NNP - B-GPE
in ADP - O
2013 CD - B-DATE
, PUNCT - O
along ADP - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
5 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
year NN - B-DATE
antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
resistance NOUN - O
strategy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
efficacy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
mechanism NOUN - O
of ADP - O
action NOUN - O
of ADP - O
poly(amidoamine NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
( PUNCT - O
PAMAM PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
dendrimers NOUN - O
against ADP - O
opportunistic ADJ - O
pathogens NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Draft NN - B-WORK_OF_ART
Genome NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
Sequence NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
of IN - I-WORK_OF_ART
Bacillus NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
velezensis NOUN - O
OSY NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
GA1 NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Which ADJ - O
Encodes VERB - O
Multiple VERB - O
Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
Metabolites PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Expresses PROPN - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Activity PROPN - O
against ADP - O
Foodborne NNP - B-PERSON
Pathogens NNPS - I-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
prescribing ADJ - O
practices NOUN - O
across ADP - O
the DET - O
national ADJ - O
Veterans NNP - B-ORG
Health NNP - I-ORG
Administration NNP - I-ORG
system NOUN - O
were VERB - O
assessed ADJ - O
using VERB - O
the DET - O
administrative ADJ - O
data NOUN - O
for ADP - O
29 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
530 CD - B-CARDINAL
records NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
peptides NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
AMPs NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
are VERB - O
short ADJ - O
amphipathic ADJ - O
biological ADJ - O
molecules NOUN - O
generally ADV - O
with ADP - O
less JJR - B-CARDINAL
than IN - I-CARDINAL
100 CD - I-CARDINAL
amino ADJ - O
acids NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Guidelines PROPN - O
to ADP - O
Prevent PROPN - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Resistance PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
steps NOUN - O
4 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
6 CD - B-DATE
and CC - I-DATE
9 CD - B-DATE
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
peptides NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
AMPs NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
play VERB - O
essential ADJ - O
roles NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
innate ADJ - O
immune ADJ - O
system NOUN - O
to PART - O
protect VERB - O
against ADP - O
a DET - O
wide ADJ - O
variety NOUN - O
of ADP - O
pathogens NOUN - O
in ADP - O
aquatic ADJ - O
environments NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

AbstractBackgroundAntimicrobials NOUN - O
are VERB - O
frequently ADV - O
administered VERB - O
to ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
an DET - O
advanced ADJ - O
stage NOUN - O
of ADP - O
illnesses NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Antimicrobials NOUN - O
were VERB - O
commonly ADV - O
prescribed VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
their ADJ - O
overall ADJ - O
consumption NOUN - O
was VERB - O
significant ADJ - O
despite ADP - O
their ADJ - O
limited ADJ - O
efficacy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Overuse NNP - B-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Antimicrobials NNPS - I-ORG
in ADP - O
the DET - O
End NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
of ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
life NOUN - O
Care NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Factors NOUN - O
Influencing VERB - O
Physicians PROPN - O
’ CCONJ - O
Prescribing PROPN - O
Behaviors PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Treating VERB - O
Patients NOUN - O
With ADP - O
an DET - O
Advanced PROPN - O
Stage PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Illnesses PROPN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
Robust PROPN - O
Era PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Stewardship PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
Cost NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
effectiveness NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Lock NNP - I-ORG
Solutions NNPS - I-ORG
for ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Prevention NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Central NNP - I-ORG
Line NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Associated NNP - I-ORG
Bloodstream NNP - I-ORG
Infections NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
activity NOUN - O
analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
recombinant ADJ - O
protein NOUN - O
purified VERB - O
from ADP - O
the DET - O
transgenic ADJ - O
HRs NOUN - O
showed VERB - O
that ADP - O
the DET - O
( PUNCT - O
CBD)2-DrsB1 NNP - B-NORP
recombinant ADJ - O
protein NOUN - O
had VERB - O
a DET - O
significant ADJ - O
( PUNCT - O
p VERB - O
  SPACE - O
< X - O
  SPACE - O
0.01 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
antimicrobial JJ - B-MEDICINE
effect NOUN - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
growth NOUN - O
of ADP - O
different ADJ - O
fungal ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
bacterial ADJ - O
pathogens NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Cationic JJ - B-ORG
Poly([R]-3-hydroxybutyrate NNP - I-ORG
) PUNCT - O
Copolymers NOUN - O
as ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Agents NNPS - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Impact NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Stewardship PROPN - O
Interventions PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Antimicrobial NNP - B-MEDICINE
Utilization NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Asymptomatic NNP - B-GPE
Bacteriuria NNP - I-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Perphenazine NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
dextran NOUN - O
sulfate NOUN - O
were VERB - O
used VERB - O
as ADP - O
the DET - O
drug NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
polysaccharide VERB - O
models NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
respectively ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Perphenazine NN - B-MEDICINE
- HYPH - I-ORG
Associated VBN - I-ORG
Hyperosmolar NNP - I-ORG
Hyperglycemic NNP - I-ORG
State NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Perphenazine NN - B-MEDICINE
treatment NOUN - O
had VERB - O
similar ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Perphenazine NN - B-MEDICINE
enanthate NOUN - O
was VERB - O
used VERB - O
to PART - O
allow VERB - O
adaptation NOUN - O
to ADP - O
captivity NOUN - O
in ADP - O
11 CD - B-CARDINAL
Pyrenean JJ - B-NORP
chamois NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
Rupicapra NNP - B-GPE
pyrenaica PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Crystalline NNP - B-PERSON
Forms NNP - I-PERSON
of ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Tri NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Mesylate NNP - I-ORG
Salt NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Perphenazine NNP - I-MEDICINE
- HYPH - I-ORG
Gaba NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Process NNP - B-WORK_OF_ART
of IN - I-WORK_OF_ART
Producing VBG - I-WORK_OF_ART
the DT - I-WORK_OF_ART
Same JJ - I-WORK_OF_ART

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
sustained ADJ - O
release NOUN - O
capsule NOUN - O
for ADP - O
oral ADJ - O
administration NOUN - O
containing VERB - O
tablets NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
wherein ADV - O
each DET - O
tablet NOUN - O
comprises VERB - O
25 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
propafenone NN - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
capsule NOUN - O
for ADP - O
oral ADJ - O
administration NOUN - O
of ADP - O
propafenone JJ - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
, PUNCT - O
wherein ADV - O
the DET - O
capsule NOUN - O
contains VERB - O
microtablets NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
wherein ADV - O
the DET - O
amount NOUN - O
of ADP - O
lubricant NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
if ADP - O
any DET - O
, PUNCT - O
comprise VERB - O
s VERB - O
less JJR - B-PERCENT
than IN - I-PERCENT
0.1 CD - I-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
of ADP - O
the DET - O
weight NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
microtablets NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
stability NOUN - O
of ADP - O
propafenone JJ - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
i.v PRON - O
. PUNCT - O

Solutions NOUN - O
of ADP - O
propafenone NN - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
0.5 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
mL PROPN - O
in ADP - O
5 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
dextrose VERB - O
injection NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
5 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
dextrose ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
0.2 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
sodium NOUN - O
chloride NOUN - O
injection NOUN - O
were VERB - O
prepared VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

All DET - O
samples NOUN - O
of ADP - O
propafenone NN - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
mL PROPN - O
in ADP - O
5 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
dextrose ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
0.2 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
sodium NOUN - O
chloride NOUN - O
injection NOUN - O
taken VERB - O
from ADP - O
PVC NNP - B-ORG
bags NOUN - O
precipitated VERB - O
when ADV - O
thawed VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Stability NOUN - O
of ADP - O
propafenone JJ - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
i.v PRON - O
. PUNCT - O
solutions NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
electrophysiologic ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
propafenone JJ - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
in ADP - O
the DET - O
neonatal ADJ - O
canine NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Several ADJ - O
class NOUN - O
IA PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
disopyramide VERB - O
phosphate ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
quinidine NOUN - O
sulfate NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
class NOUN - O
IC PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
flecainide NOUN - O
acetate VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
propafenone JJ - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
class NOUN - O
III PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
amiodarone ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
dofetilide NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
sotalol NOUN - O
hydrochloride NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
blood NOUN - O
samples NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
0 CD - B-CARDINAL
- SYM - I-CARDINAL
15 CD - I-CARDINAL
h NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
subjects NOUN - O
were VERB - O
taken VERB - O
after ADP - O
oral ADJ - O
administration NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
single ADJ - O
dose NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
400 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
of ADP - O
propafenone JJ - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

This DET - O
method NOUN - O
after ADP - O
validation NOUN - O
procedures NOUN - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
applied VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
multisample NOUN - O
analyses NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
human ADJ - O
pharmacokinetic ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
with ADP - O
10 CD - B-CARDINAL
healthy ADJ - O
volunteers NOUN - O
after ADP - O
an DET - O
oral ADJ - O
dose NOUN - O
of ADP - O
300 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
propafenone NN - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
aim NOUN - O
of ADP - O
this DET - O
study NOUN - O
was VERB - O
evaluation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
intravenous ADJ - O
propafenone NN - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
effects NOUN - O
on ADP - O
maintenance NOUN - O
of ADP - O
atrial ADJ - O
signal NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
averaged VERB - O
ECG NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
ASAECG NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
during ADP - O
time NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
domain NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
frequency NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
domain NOUN - O
analyses NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
paroxysmal ADJ - O
atrial ADJ - O
fibrillation NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PAF NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
accompanying VERB - O
ischemic ADJ - O
heart NOUN - O
disease NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
IHD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
obtained VERB - O
results NOUN - O
have VERB - O
indicated VERB - O
that ADP - O
intravenous ADJ - O
propafenone NN - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
did VERB - O
not ADV - O
change VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
time NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
domain NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
frequency NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
domain NOUN - O
parameters NOUN - O
of ADP - O
ASAECG NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
PAF NNP - B-ORG
during ADP - O
IHD NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

One CD - B-CARDINAL
of ADP - O
these DET - O
promising ADJ - O
new ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
propafenone JJ - B-MEDICINE
hydrochloride NN - I-MEDICINE
( PUNCT - O
Rhythmol NNP - B-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
will VERB - O
soon ADV - O
be VERB - O
available ADJ - O
for ADP - O
use NOUN - O
in ADP - O
this DET - O
country NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Partner PROPN - O
Conflict PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Support PROPN - O
as ADP - O
Moderators PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Alcohol NNP - B-MEDICINE
Use PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Alcohol NNP - B-MEDICINE
Problems NNP - I-ORG
and CC - I-ORG
Marital NNP - I-ORG
Satisfaction NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Young PROPN - O
Adult PROPN - O
Marital PROPN - O
Dyads NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Support NOUN - O
for ADP - O
evidence NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
based VERB - O
alcohol NN - B-MEDICINE
policy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Ireland NNP - B-GPE
: PUNCT - O
results NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Community NNP - I-ORG
Action NNP - I-ORG
on IN - I-ORG
Alcohol NNP - I-MEDICINE
Pilot NNP - I-ORG
Project NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

This DET - O
paper NOUN - O
provides VERB - O
a DET - O
brief ADJ - O
overview NOUN - O
of ADP - O
research NOUN - O
on ADP - O
women NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
alcohol NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
introduces VERB - O
a DET - O
virtual ADJ - O
issue NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Alcoholism PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Alcohol NN - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Women PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
Brief PROPN - O
Overview PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

New ADJ - O
Estimates NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Mean PROPN - O
Ethanol PROPN - O
Content PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Beer PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Wine PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Spirits NNS - B-ORG
Sold VBN - I-ORG
in ADP - O
the DT - B-GPE
United NNP - I-GPE
States NNP - I-GPE
Show NNP - I-GPE
a DT - I-GPE
Greater NNP - I-GPE
Increase NN - I-GPE
in ADP - O
Per ADP - O
Capita PROPN - O
Alcohol NNP - B-MEDICINE
Consumption PROPN - O
than ADP - O
Previous ADJ - O
Estimates NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Understanding VBG - B-ORG
Social NNP - I-ORG
and CC - I-ORG
Cultural NNP - I-ORG
Contexts NNP - I-ORG
of ADP - O
Alcohol NNP - B-MEDICINE
Misuse NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Mexican NNP - B-WORK_OF_ART
- HYPH - I-WORK_OF_ART
Origin NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
Hispanic NNP - I-WORK_OF_ART
Men NNPS - I-WORK_OF_ART
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Alcohol NN - B-MEDICINE
consumption NOUN - O
appears VERB - O
to PART - O
modulate VERB - O
the DET - O
status NOUN - O
of ADP - O
inflammation NOUN - O
in ADP - O
depressive ADJ - O
patients NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
2012 CD - B-DATE
to ADP - O
2013 NUM - O
National PROPN - O
Epidemiologic PROPN - O
Survey PROPN - O
on ADP - O
Alcohol NNP - B-MEDICINE
and CCONJ - O
Related PROPN - O
Conditions PROPN - O
III PROPN - O
conducted VERB - O
in ADP - O
- PUNCT - O
person NOUN - O
interviews NOUN - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
nationally ADV - O
representative ADJ - O
sample NOUN - O
of ADP - O
U.S. NNP - B-GPE
adults NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
N NNP - B-ORG
  _SP - I-ORG
= SYM - O
  SPACE - O
36,309 NUM - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Participants NOUN - O
at ADP - O
each DET - O
site NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
United NNP - B-GPE
States NNP - I-GPE
, PUNCT - O
n DET - O
  SPACE - O
= SYM - O
  SPACE - O
132 NUM - O
; PUNCT - O
France NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
n DET - O
  SPACE - O
= SYM - O
  SPACE - O
132 NUM - O
) PUNCT - O
were VERB - O
asked VERB - O
to PART - O
complete VERB - O
an DET - O
Internet NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
based VERB - O
survey NOUN - O
including VERB - O
the DET - O
APT NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
APT NNP - B-ORG
Choice NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Alcohol NNP - B-MEDICINE
Use NNP - I-ORG
Disorders NNP - I-ORG
Identification NNP - I-ORG
Test NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Daily NNP - B-ORG
Drinking NNP - I-ORG
Questionnaire NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Drinking NNP - B-ORG
Motives NNPS - I-ORG

Slope NOUN - O
analyses NOUN - O
were VERB - O
performed VERB - O
on ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Non NNP - I-ORG
- NNP - I-ORG
Alcoholic NNP - I-ORG
Cross NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Price NNP - I-ORG
demand NOUN - O
to PART - O
assess VERB - O
substitutability NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Alcohol NN - B-MEDICINE
consumption NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Spanish JJ - B-NORP
primary ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
care NOUN - O
providers NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
national ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
cross ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
sectional ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Alcohol NNP - B-MEDICINE
Abstainer NNP - I-ORG
Status NNP - I-ORG
and CCONJ - O
Prazosin NNP - B-ORG
Treatment NNP - I-ORG
in IN - I-ORG
Association NNP - I-ORG
with IN - I-ORG
Changes NNP - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Posttraumatic NNP - B-ORG
Stress NNP - I-ORG
Disorder NN - I-ORG
Symptoms NNS - I-ORG
in ADP - O
Veterans NNPS - B-GPE
with ADP - O
Comorbid NNP - B-PERSON
Alcohol NNP - I-MEDICINE
Use NNP - I-PERSON
Disorder PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
Posttraumatic PROPN - O
Stress PROPN - O
Disorder NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Alcohol NN - B-MEDICINE
use VERB - O
at ADP - O
baseline NOUN - O
was VERB - O
measured VERB - O
as ADP - O
g NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
wk NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
frequency NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
use VERB - O
over ADP - O
the DET - O
risk NOUN - O
limit NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O
