-DOCSTART- -X- - O

She PRON - O
was VERB - O
earlier ADV - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
Cap NNP - B-PERSON
venlafaxine NN - B-Drug
up IN - B-CARDINAL
to IN - I-CARDINAL
30 CD - I-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
day NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
had VERB - O
a DET - O
relapse NOUN - O
of ADP - O
depressive JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
symptoms NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
when ADV - O
an DET - O
attempt NOUN - O
was VERB - O
made VERB - O
to PART - O
taper VERB - O
off PART - O
venlafaxine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
aim NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
Fluoxetine NNP - B-Drug
for ADP - O
Autistic PROPN - O
Behaviors NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
FAB PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
study NOUN - O
is VERB - O
to PART - O
determine VERB - O
the DET - O
efficacy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
safety NOUN - O
of ADP - O
low ADJ - O
dose NOUN - O
fluoxetine NN - B-Drug
compared VERB - O
with ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
reducing VERB - O
the DET - O
frequency NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
severity NOUN - O
of ADP - O
repetitive ADJ - O
stereotypic ADJ - O
behaviors NOUN - O
in ADP - O
children NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
adolescents NOUN - O
with ADP - O
an DET - O
autism NN - B-Disease_Symptom
spectrum NN - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
ASD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CONCLUSION NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Paroxetine NN - B-Drug
use NOUN - O
during ADP - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
treatment NOUN - O
is VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
an DET - O
increased VBN - B-Disease_Symptom
risk NN - I-Disease_Symptom
of IN - I-Disease_Symptom
death NN - I-Disease_Symptom
from IN - I-Disease_Symptom
breast NN - I-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
supporting VERB - O
the DET - O
hypothesis NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
paroxetine NN - B-Drug
can VERB - O
reduce VERB - O
or CCONJ - O
abolish VERB - O
the DET - O
benefit NOUN - O
of ADP - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
women NOUN - O
with ADP - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

So CCONJ - O
if ADP - O
the DET - O
CPAP NNP - B-ORG
continues VERB - O
to PART - O
not ADV - O
help VERB - O
general ADJ - O
fatigue NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
new ADJ - O
doc NOUN - O
is VERB - O
more ADV - O
than ADP - O
willing ADJ - O
to PART - O
prescribe VERB - O
Modafinil NNP - B-PERSON
at ADP - O
my ADJ - O
request NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Thanks NOUN - O
Dr PROPN - O
Feelgood NNP - B-PERSON
! PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Do VERB - O
/ SYM - O
did VERB - O
you PRON - O
have VERB - O
joint JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
pain NN - I-Disease_Symptom
with ADP - O
# SYM - O
Tamoxifen NN - B-PERSON
? PUNCT - O

AIs NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

What NOUN - O
helped VERB - O
relieve VERB - O
your ADJ - O
pain NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

# $ - B-CARDINAL
breastcancer NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Comparison NOUN - O
of ADP - O
intravitreal NOUN - O
bevacizumab NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
intravitreal ADJ - O
triamcinolone NN - B-Drug
acetonide NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
macular NOUN - O
grid NOUN - O
augmentation NOUN - O
in ADP - O
refractory NN - B-Disease_Symptom
diffuse IN - I-Disease_Symptom
diabetic JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
macular NN - I-Disease_Symptom
edema NN - I-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
prospective ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
randomized VERB - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
administration NOUN - O
of ADP - O
aripiprazole NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
produced VERB - O
a DET - O
significant ADJ - O
improvement NOUN - O
of ADP - O
all DET - O
psychopathological ADJ - O
dimensions NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
obsessive ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
compulsive ADJ - O
symptoms NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
eating VBG - B-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

# SYM - O
ATIinstructorwisdom NOUN - O
" PUNCT - O
Olanzapine NNP - B-Drug
is VERB - O
an DET - O
anti ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
anxiety JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
medication NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Same ADJ - O
family NOUN - O
as ADP - O
Ativan NNP - B-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

" PUNCT - O

Not ADV - O
that ADV - O
funny ADJ - O
... PUNCT - O

but CCONJ - O
its ADJ - O
an DET - O
anti ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
psychotic ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Two CD - B-DATE
- HYPH - I-DATE
year NN - I-DATE
sustained VERB - O
weight NN - B-Disease_Symptom
loss NN - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
metabolic ADJ - O
benefits NOUN - O
with ADP - O
controlled VERB - O
- PUNCT - O
release NOUN - O
phentermine NOUN - O

/ SYM - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
obese JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
overweight ADJ - O
adults NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
SEQUEL NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
randomized ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
placebo NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
controlled VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
phase VERB - O
40 CD - B-CARDINAL
extension NOUN - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

" PUNCT - O

Money NOUN - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
strange ADJ - O
thing NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

It PRON - O
ranks VERB - O
with ADP - O
lovetas NNS - B-Drug
our ADJ - O
greatest ADJ - O
source NOUN - O
of ADP - O
joy NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
with ADP - O
death NOUN - O
as ADP - O
our ADJ - O
greatest ADJ - O
source NOUN - O
of ADP - O
anxiety NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

" PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O
.oe PUNCT - O

Moore PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

When ADV - O
your ADJ - O
scar ADJ - O
tissue NOUN - O
came VERB - O
back ADV - O
and CCONJ - O
you PRON - O
had VERB - O
to PART - O
get VERB - O
an DET - O
injection NOUN - O
of ADP - O
cortisone NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
your ADJ - O
ankle NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
it PRON - O
hurt VBD - B-Disease_Symptom
so ADV - O
fricking VERB - O
bad ADJ - O
💁 NNP - B-ORG
🏼 NNP - I-ORG
😭 NN - I-ORG
😭 NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Using VERB - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
only ADJ - O
design NOUN - O
with ADP - O
7 CD - B-CARDINAL
high ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
risk NOUN - O
hypertensive ADJ - O
individuals NOUN - O
from ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
Genetics NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Hypertension NNP - I-ORG
Associated NNP - I-ORG
Treatment NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
GenHAT PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
study NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
we PRON - O
examined VERB - O
whether ADP - O
seven CD - B-CARDINAL
single ADJ - O
nucleotide NOUN - O
polymorphisms NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
SNPs PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
angiotensinogen NOUN - O
gene NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
AGT NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
interact VERB - O
with ADP - O
three CD - B-CARDINAL
classes NOUN - O
of ADP - O
antihypertensive ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
including VERB - O
chlorthalidone NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
a DET - O
thiazide ADV - O
diuretic ADJ - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
lisinopril JJ - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
an DET - O
ACE NNP - B-ORG
inhibitor NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
amlodipine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
a DET - O
calcium NOUN - O
channel NOUN - O
blocker NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
to PART - O
modify VERB - O
the DET - O
risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
incident NOUN - O
coronary JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
heart NN - I-Disease_Symptom
disease NN - I-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
CHD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
heart NN - B-Disease_Symptom
failure NN - I-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
HF NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
among ADP - O
Caucasian JJ - B-NORP
and CCONJ - O
African JJ - B-NORP
American JJ - I-NORP
participants NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
separately ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Cymbalta NNP - B-ORG
is VERB - O
killing VERB - O
me PRON - O
... PUNCT - O
literally ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

I PRON - O
feel VERB - O
like ADP - O
I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
dying VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

This DET - O
ca VERB - O
n't ADV - O
be VERB - O
real ADJ - O
..... PUNCT - O

😣 NNP - B-ORG
😤 NNP - I-ORG
😩 NNP - I-ORG
😷 PROPN - O
😳 PROPN - O
😭 NOUN - O

# NN - B-CARDINAL
spoonie NOUN - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
chronicillness NOUN - O

# $ - B-MONEY
cymbalta JJ - I-MONEY

# SYM - O
withdrawals NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Buprenorphine NNP - B-ORG
Outpatient NNP - I-ORG
Outcomes NNP - I-ORG
Project NN - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
can VERB - O
Suboxone PRP - B-GPE
be VERB - O
a DET - O
viable ADJ - O
outpatient NOUN - O
option NOUN - O
for ADP - O
heroin NN - B-Disease_Symptom
addiction NN - I-Disease_Symptom
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

If ADP - O
effective ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
pregabalin NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
whose ADJ - O
beneficial ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
on ADP - O
pain NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
sleep NOUN - O
quality NOUN - O
in ADP - O
fibromyalgia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
have VERB - O
been VERB - O
demonstrated VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
could VERB - O
complement VERB - O
the DET - O
antidepressant ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
anxiolytic ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Here ADV - O
the DET - O
therapeutic ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
triamcinolone NN - B-Drug
acetonide NOUN - O
ointment NOUN - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
relatively ADV - O
expensive ADJ - O
medication NOUN - O
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
compared VERB - O
with ADP - O
phenytoin DET - O
syrup NOUN - O
on ADP - O
aphthous JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
ulcers NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Behcet NNP - B-ORG
's PART - O
syndrome NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
above ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
revealed VERB - O
that ADP - O
the DET - O
compounds NOUN - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
-chloro SYM - O
57 NUM - O
H- CCONJ - O
[ PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-DATE
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
] PUNCT - O
triazino NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
-b]indol SYM - O
57 CD - B-DATE
( PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-TIME
H)-one NNP - I-TIME
( PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
e NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-DATE
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
-dibromo SYM - O
57 NUM - O
H- PROPN - O
[ PUNCT - O
57 NUM - O
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-DATE
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
] PUNCT - O
triazino NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
-b]indol SYM - O
57 CD - B-DATE
( PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-TIME
H)-one NNP - I-TIME
( PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
i NUM - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
-dibromo SYM - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
-methyl SYM - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
H- NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-DATE
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
] PUNCT - O
triazino NOUN - O
[ PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
-b]indol SYM - O
57 CD - B-DATE
( PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-TIME
H)-one NNP - I-TIME
( PUNCT - O
57 CD - B-CARDINAL
k NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
possess VERB - O
excellent ADJ - O
anticonvulsant NOUN - O
activity NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
series NOUN - O
with ADP - O
little ADJ - O
CNS NNP - B-ORG
depressant NOUN - O
effect NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
no DET - O
neurotoxicity NN - B-Disease_Symptom
as ADP - O
compared VERB - O
to ADP - O
standard ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
phenytoin VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
carbamazepine VB - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Why ADV - O
am VERB - O
I PRON - O
still ADV - O
awake VBP - B-Disease_Symptom
you PRON - O
ask VERB - O
? PUNCT - O

Prednisone JJ - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

I PRON - O
will VERB - O
never ADV - O
take VERB - O
prednisone NN - B-Drug
ever ADV - O
again ADV - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

All DET - O
of ADP - O
these DET - O
rashes NNS - B-Disease_Symptom
were VERB - O
observed VERB - O
within ADP - O
84 CD - B-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
of ADP - O
the DET - O
initiation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
lamotrigine NN - B-Drug
therapy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

There ADV - O
's VERB - O
not ADV - O
enough ADJ - O
Effexor NNP - B-PERSON
in ADP - O
the DET - O
world NOUN - O
to PART - O
deal VERB - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
this DET - O
park NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

L. NNP - B-PERSON
Schmidt NNP - I-PERSON
very ADV - O
excited ADJ - O
by ADP - O
results NOUN - O
of ADP - O
bevacizumab NN - B-Drug
+ CCONJ - O
erlotinib NOUN - O
in ADP - O
HLRCC NNP - B-ORG
metastatic ADJ - O
pap2RCC NOUN - O
results NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
ORR PROPN - O
65 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
# SYM - O
NSGC2015 CD - B-PERSON

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

My ADJ - O
medmix NOUN - O
for ADP - O
# $ - B-MONEY
bipolar JJ - I-MONEY
& CC - I-MONEY
amp NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
bpd ADV - O
now ADV - O
that ADP - O
the DET - O
seasons NOUN - O
are VERB - O
changing VERB - O
: PUNCT - O
geodon VB - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
lamictal JJ - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
Zoloft NNP - B-ORG
& CC - I-ORG
amp NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
extra ADJ - O
clonazepam NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
add VERB - O
Wellbutrin NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
so ADV - O
far ADV - O
so ADV - O
good ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pseudotumor NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
cerebri RB - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
ciprofloxacin VBD - B-Drug
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
report NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Went VERB - O
in PART - O
to PART - O
get VERB - O
a DET - O
nasty ADJ - O
bee NN - B-Disease_Symptom
sting NN - I-Disease_Symptom
checked VERB - O
out PART - O
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
Doc NNP - B-PERSON
said VERB - O
prednisone NN - B-Drug
might VERB - O
make VERB - O
me PRON - O
feel VERB - O
crazy JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

Not ADV - O
to PART - O
worry VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
I PRON - O
've VERB - O
been VERB - O
crazy JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
for ADP - O
years NNS - B-DATE
👍 NOUN - O
🏻 PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Trazodone NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
methandone NOUN - O
induced VERB - O
erectile IN - B-Disease_Symptom
dysfunction NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

About RB - B-DATE
40 CD - I-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
ago RB - I-DATE
I PRON - O
was VERB - O
told VERB - O
I PRON - O
would VERB - O
outgrow VERB - O
my ADJ - O
# SYM - O
Migraines PROPN - O
... PUNCT - O
never ADV - O
happened VERB - O
. PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O

I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
now ADV - O
resorting VERB - O
to ADP - O
Kenalog NNP - B-ORG
skull VERB - O
injections NOUN - O
for ADP - O
relief NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

@108dragonsx PROPN - O
this DET - O
Keytruda NNP - B-PERSON
trial NOUN - O
is VERB - O
the DET - O
2nd JJ - B-ORDINAL

Nsclc NNP - B-ORG
trial NOUN - O
using VERB - O
pegpH20-the DET - O
Primal NNP - B-ORG
w ADP - O
Docetaxel NNP - B-ORG
was VERB - O
expanded VERB - O
to PART - O
add VERB - O
more ADJ - O
centers NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
o NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
w NOUN - O
no DET - O
changes NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

So CCONJ - O
if ADP - O
I PRON - O
have VERB - O
Lamotrigine NNP - B-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
have VERB - O
a DET - O
rash NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
it PRON - O
does VERB - O
n't ADV - O
mean VERB - O
I PRON - O
have VERB - O
The DET - O
Rash NNP - B-PERSON

... PUNCT - O
does VERB - O
it PRON - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
switching VERB - O
antidepressants NOUN - O
after ADP - O
being VERB - O
on ADP - O
Citalopram NNP - B-ORG
for ADP - O
10 CD - B-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

Suffering VERB - O
withdrawals NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
physical ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
mental ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

Do VERB - O
n't ADV - O
like VERB - O
this DET - O
at ADV - O
all ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
off ADV - O
birth NOUN - O
control NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
Zoloft NNP - B-PERSON

and CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
losing VERB - O
weight NOUN - O
again ADV - O
! PUNCT - O

Woo ADV - O
hoo INTJ - O
, PUNCT - O
no DET - O
more ADJ - O
medicine NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
makes VERB - O
me PRON - O
fat ADJ - O
! PUNCT - O
! PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

They PRON - O
also ADV - O
highlight VERB - O
the DET - O
potential ADJ - O
mediating VERB - O
role NOUN - O
of ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
duloxetine NN - B-Drug
on ADP - O
the DET - O
negative ADJ - O
relationship NOUN - O
between ADP - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
- PUNCT - O
related VERB - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
outcomes NOUN - O
of ADP - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Ugggh ADJ - O
# SYM - O
migraine NOUN - O
sucks VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

First RB - B-ORDINAL
one NUM - O
I PRON - O
've VERB - O
had VERB - O
since ADP - O
the DET - O
# SYM - O
topamax NOUN - O
though ADV - O
, PUNCT - O

so CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
ca VERB - O
n't ADV - O
complain VERB - O
too ADV - O
much ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

It PRON - O
's VERB - O
been VERB - O
working VERB - O
great ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

@3liza PROPN - O
cannabis VERB - O
balm NOUN - O
on ADP - O
my ADJ - O
neck NOUN - O
is VERB - O
the DET - O
only ADJ - O
thing NOUN - O
I PRON - O
can VERB - O
take VERB - O
for ADP - O
sleep NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

Trazodone NN - B-Drug
makes VERB - O
me PRON - O
hallucinate VB - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
benadryl NOUN - O
makes VERB - O
me PRON - O
feel VERB - O
like ADP - O
shit NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

geodon NN - B-Drug
has VBZ - B-Disease_Symptom
altered VBN - I-Disease_Symptom
my PRP$ - I-Disease_Symptom
ability NN - I-Disease_Symptom
to TO - I-Disease_Symptom
sleep VB - I-Disease_Symptom
i PRON - O
think VERB - O
... PUNCT - O
like ADP - O
... PUNCT - O
its ADJ - O
either CCONJ - O
super ADJ - O
fucking ADJ - O
restful ADJ - O
or CCONJ - O
not ADV - O
restful ADJ - O
at ADV - O
all ADV - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Time NOUN - O
to PART - O
start VERB - O
the DET - O
semi ADV - O
- ADJ - O
annual ADJ - O
twitter NOUN - O
experiment NOUN - O
again ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

This DET - O
time NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Adderall NNP - B-PERSON
to PART - O
combat VERB - O
the DET - O
ADHD NNP - B-ORG
rabbit NOUN - O
hole NOUN - O
problem NOUN - O
! PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

RESULTS NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Among ADP - O
37 CD - B-CARDINAL
patients NOUN - O
who NOUN - O
developed VERB - O
delirium NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
37 CD - B-CARDINAL
patients NOUN - O
received VERB - O
antipsychotics NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
such ADJ - O
as ADP - O
risperidone NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
37 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
quetiapine NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
37 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
parenteral ADJ - O
haloperidol NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
37 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
delirium NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

An DET - O
18 CD - B-DATE
year NN - I-DATE
old JJ - I-DATE
male NOUN - O
diagnosed VERB - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
of ADP - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
affective JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
BPAD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
developed VERB - O
neuroleptic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
malignant JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
syndrome NN - I-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
NMS NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
following VERB - O
treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
olanzapine NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
18 CD - B-DATE
mg NN - I-DATE
per IN - I-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
an DET - O
atypical ADJ - O
antipsychotic ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

This DET - O
study NOUN - O
investigated VERB - O
the DET - O
effectiveness NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
on ADP - O
symptoms NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
impairment NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
safety NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Equasym NNP - B-ORG
XL NNP - I-ORG
( PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
combination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
62 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
immediate ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
release NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
62 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
modified VERB - O
- PUNCT - O
release NOUN - O
MPH NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
ADHD NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
daily JJ - B-DATE
clinical ADJ - O
practice NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Update NOUN - O
on ADP - O
optimal ADJ - O
use NOUN - O
of ADP - O
lisdexamfetamine NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
ADHD NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Moreover ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
number NOUN - O
of ADP - O
weeks NNS - B-DATE
with ADP - O
no DET - O
or CCONJ - O
minimal ADJ - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
symptoms NOUN - O
was VERB - O
estimated VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
  SPACE - O
86 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
for ADP - O
pregabalin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
only ADV - O
  SPACE - O
86 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
for ADP - O
venlafaxine NN - B-Drug
XR NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
comparison NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
incidence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
myelodysplastic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
syndrome NN - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
acute ADJ - O
myeloid JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
leukaemia NN - I-Disease_Symptom
following VERB - O
melphalan NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
cyclophosphamide NOUN - O
treatment NOUN - O
for ADP - O
myelomatosis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CONCLUSION NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Administration NOUN - O
of ADP - O
melatonin NOUN - O
along ADP - O
with ADP - O
ritalin NN - B-Drug
improves VERB - O
height NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
weight NN - B-Disease_Symptom
growth NOUN - O
of ADP - O
children NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CONCLUSIONS NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

We PRON - O
suggest VERB - O
that ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
particularly ADV - O
with ADP - O
quetiapine NN - B-Drug
may VERB - O
have VERB - O
anti ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
inflammatory ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
in ADP - O
arthritis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
comorbid VERB - O
major JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
depression NN - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
eventually ADV - O
led VERB - O
to ADP - O
a DET - O
remission NOUN - O
of ADP - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
to ADP - O
normal ADJ - O
general ADJ - O
function NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Topamax NNP - B-Drug
+ CCONJ - O
phentermine NOUN - O
= SYM - O
thinner JJR - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
happier ADJ - O
me PRON - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

BACKGROUND NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

The DET - O
aim NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
present ADJ - O
analysis NOUN - O
was VERB - O
to PART - O
evaluate VERB - O
the DET - O
recurrence NOUN - O
pattern NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
recurrent NOUN - O
malignant ADJ - O
glioma NN - B-Disease_Symptom
after ADP - O
re NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
irradiation NOUN - O
in ADP - O
combination NOUN - O
with ADP - O
bevacizumab NN - B-Drug
as ADP - O
there ADV - O
is VERB - O
limited ADJ - O
data NOUN - O
on ADP - O
how ADV - O
to PART - O
optimally ADV - O
choose VERB - O
dose NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
fractionation NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
delineation NOUN - O
margins NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Stevens NNP - B-ORG
johnson NOUN - O
syndrome NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
patient NOUN - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
lamotrigine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
side NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
effects NOUN - O
observed VERB - O
were VERB - O
dryness NOUN - O
of ADP - O
mouthwith NOUN - O
the DET - O
nortriptyline NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
nausea NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
headache NN - B-Disease_Symptom
with ADP - O
fluvoxamine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Did VERB - O
you PRON - O
know VERB - O
that ADP - O
early JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
menopause NN - I-Disease_Symptom
can VERB - O
be VERB - O
caused VERB - O
by ADP - O
Chemotherapy NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
Hormonal PROPN - O
Therapy PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Tamoxifen NNP - B-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
even ADV - O
Ovarian NNP - B-GPE
Shutdown NNP - I-GPE
or CCONJ - O
Removal PROPN - O
? PUNCT - O

# $ - B-CARDINAL
vagtalk NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Tamoxifen JJ - B-Drug
side NOUN - O
effects NOUN - O
include VERB - O
irritability NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

Will VERB - O
have VERB - O
to PART - O
figure VERB - O
out PART - O
how ADV - O
to ADP - O
time NOUN - O
taking VERB - O
it PRON - O
so ADP - O
as ADP - O
not ADV - O
to PART - O
actually ADV - O
kill VERB - O
anybody NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

you PRON - O
want VERB - O
to PART - O
see VERB - O
the DET - O
real ADJ - O
# SYM - O
TheWalkingDead NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

Find VERB - O
people NOUN - O
on ADP - O
Topamax NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

I PRON - O
ca VERB - O
n't ADV - O
stay VERB - O
awake ADJ - O
more JJR - B-CARDINAL
than IN - I-CARDINAL
2 CD - I-CARDINAL
hrs NOUN - O
at ADP - O
a DET - O
time NOUN - O
w/o ADP - O
chugging VERB - O
red ADJ - O
bulls NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

" PUNCT - O

The DET - O
only ADJ - O
way NOUN - O
out ADV - O
is VERB - O
through ADP - O

" PUNCT - O
Check VERB - O
out PART - O
my ADJ - O
new ADJ - O
post NOUN - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
of ADP - O
# $ - B-MONEY
Paxil NNP - I-MONEY
# VBD - I-MONEY
through ADP - O
# $ - B-MONEY
panic NN - I-MONEY

# $ - B-MONEY
anxiety NN - I-MONEY
# $ - I-MONEY
pain NN - I-MONEY

# NN - B-CARDINAL
hope NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Quetiapine NN - B-GPE
for ADP - O
acute ADJ - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
depression NN - I-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
systematic ADJ - O
review NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
meta ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
analysis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
mean ADJ - O
( PUNCT - O
standard ADJ - O
deviation NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O

ADHD NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
RS NNP - I-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
IV NNP - I-ORG
total ADJ - O
score NOUN - O
at ADP - O
baseline NOUN - O
was VERB - O
  SPACE - O

83 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
( PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O
83 NUM - O
  SPACE - O
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
lisdexamfetamine NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O
83 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
( PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O
83 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
  SPACE - O
83 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
( PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O
83 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
) PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
OROS NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
MPH NNP - I-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

This DET - O
study NOUN - O
investigated VERB - O
the DET - O
feasibility NOUN - O
of ADP - O
CA NNP - B-ORG
IX PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
directed VERB - O
immunoliposomes NOUN - O
for ADP - O
targeted VERB - O
delivery NOUN - O
of ADP - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
to ADP - O
human ADJ - O
lung NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
cells NOUN - O
in ADP - O
vitro NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CASE NNP - B-ORG
PRESENTATION PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O

A DET - O
91 CD - B-CARDINAL
-year NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
old ADJ - O
Caucasian JJ - B-NORP
Australian JJ - B-NORP
woman NOUN - O
with ADP - O
arthritis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
was VERB - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
course NOUN - O
of ADP - O
escitalopram NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
mirtazapine NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
quetiapine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Suboxone NN - B-GPE
is VERB - O
a DET - O
drug NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
helps VERB - O
addicts NOUN - O
recover NOUN - O
by ADP - O
controlling VERB - O
cravings NNS - B-Disease_Symptom
& CCONJ - O
amp NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
preventing VERB - O
withdrawal NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

Feds NOUN - O
improve VERB - O
access NOUN - O
to PART - O
address VERB - O
heroin NOUN - O
issue NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Is VERB - O
it PRON - O
stupid ADJ - O
to PART - O
take VERB - O
extra ADJ - O
Olanzapine NNP - B-GPE
now ADV - O
? PUNCT - O
! PUNCT - O

So ADV - O
desperate ADJ - O
for ADP - O
sleep NN - B-Disease_Symptom

but CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
need VERB - O
to PART - O
not ADV - O
be VERB - O
a DET - O
zombie NOUN - O
2moro CD - B-PRODUCT
. PUNCT - O

Hmmm UH - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

everyone NOUN - O
should VERB - O
take VERB - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
once ADV - O
in ADP - O
their ADJ - O
life NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
even ADV - O
if ADP - O
they PRON - O
do VERB - O
n't ADV - O
suffer VERB - O
from ADP - O
insomnia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

like INTJ - O
.... PUNCT - O
the DET - O
deepest ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
sleeping VBG - B-Disease_Symptom
beauty NN - I-Disease_Symptom
sleep NN - I-Disease_Symptom

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Friend NOUN - O
has VERB - O
neurotoxic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
reaction NN - I-Disease_Symptom
to ADP - O
# SYM - O
Celexa NNP - B-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
what NOUN - O
does VERB - O
the DET - O
doctor NOUN - O
do VERB - O
? PUNCT - O

Tell VERB - O
her PRON - O
to PART - O
get VERB - O
off PART - O
? PUNCT - O

No INTJ - O
Prescribes PROPN - O
her PRON - O

# SYM - O
Welbutrin NNP - B-PERSON
Brilliant NNP - I-PERSON

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Of ADP - O
the DET - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
anti ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
breast JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
drugs NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
showed VERB - O
IC PROPN - O
13 NUM - O
= SYM - O
  SPACE - O

13 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
microM NOUN - O
to ADP - O
BC NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
M NNP - I-ORG
13 NUM - O
cells NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
paclitaxel NOUN - O
had VERB - O
much ADV - O
less ADJ - O
sensitivity NOUN - O
than ADP - O
AZ PROPN - O
13 NUM - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Population NOUN - O
pharmacokinetics NOUN - O
of ADP - O
methylphenidate JJ - B-Drug
hydrochloride NOUN - O
extended VERB - O
- PUNCT - O
release NOUN - O
multiple ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
layer NOUN - O
beads NOUN - O
in ADP - O
pediatric ADJ - O
subjects NOUN - O
with ADP - O
attention NN - B-Disease_Symptom
deficit NN - I-Disease_Symptom
hyperactivity NN - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

significantly ADV - O
reduced VERB - O
( PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O
61 CD - B-PERCENT
  _SP - I-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
) PUNCT - O
weight NN - B-Disease_Symptom
gain NN - I-Disease_Symptom
induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
olanzapine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Rotting VERB - O
throughout ADP - O
now ADV - O
it PRON - O
seems VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

At ADP - O
the DET - O
prompting NOUN - O
of ADP - O
my ADJ - O
wife NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
son NOUN - O
I PRON - O
am VERB - O
taking VERB - O
Olanzapine NNP - B-GPE
. PUNCT - O

An DET - O
Anti JJ - B-ORG
- JJ - I-ORG
Psychotic JJ - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Mood NNP - B-PERSON
Suppressor NNP - I-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

Humph PROPN - O
I PRON - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

To PART - O
investigate VERB - O
the DET - O
antidepressant ADJ - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
high ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
dose NOUN - O
milnacipran NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
we PRON - O
retrospectively ADV - O
compared VERB - O
three CD - B-CARDINAL
groups NOUN - O
of ADP - O
inpatients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
major JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
depression NN - I-Disease_Symptom
; PUNCT - O
those DET - O
who NOUN - O
were VERB - O
given VERB - O
milnacipran ADJ - O
> CCONJ - O
83 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
day NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
high ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
dose NOUN - O
milnacipran NOUN - O
group NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
those DET - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
milnacipran NOUN - O
at ADP - O
maximum ADJ - O
doses NOUN - O
of ADP - O
83 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
day NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
standard ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
dose NOUN - O
milnacipran NOUN - O
group NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
those DET - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
paroxetine NN - B-Drug
at ADP - O
maximum ADJ - O
doses NOUN - O
of ADP - O
83 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
day NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
paroxetine NN - B-Drug
group NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

METHODS NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Pooled VERB - O
data NOUN - O
were VERB - O
analyzed VERB - O
from ADP - O
four CD - B-CARDINAL
randomized VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
double ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
blind ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
placebo NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
controlled VERB - O
studies NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
compared VERB - O
duloxetine VBP - B-Drug
at ADP - O
the DET - O
dose NOUN - O
range NOUN - O
approved VERB - O
in ADP - O
Japan NNP - B-GPE
( PUNCT - O
71 CD - B-DATE
mg NN - I-DATE
/ SYM - I-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
) PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
other ADJ - O
SSRIs NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
paroxetine VB - B-Drug
71 CD - B-DATE
mg NN - I-DATE
/ SYM - I-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
or CCONJ - O
escitalopram VERB - O
71 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
day NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
placebo NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
major JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
depressive JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

As ADP - O
specific ADJ - O
examples NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
glioblastoma NOUN - O
multiforme NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
GBM NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
primary ADJ - O
central ADJ - O
nervous ADJ - O
system NOUN - O
lymphoma NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
PCNSL NN - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
blood NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
borne VERB - O
metastases NOUN - O
from ADP - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
are VERB - O
discussed VERB - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
context NOUN - O
of ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
respectively ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
mAbs PROPN - O
bevacizumab NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
rituximab X - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
trastuzumab NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
each DET - O
of ADP - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
already ADV - O
widely ADV - O
used VERB - O
against ADP - O
tumor NOUN - O
outside ADP - O
the DET - O
brain NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

We PRON - O
are VERB - O
reporting VERB - O
two CD - B-CARDINAL
cases NOUN - O
of ADP - O
suicidal JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
attempt NN - I-Disease_Symptom
that ADJ - O
occurred VERB - O
concomitantly ADV - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
use NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Duloxetine NNP - B-PERSON
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Addition NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Docetaxel NNP - B-ORG
to ADP - O
SOC NNP - B-ORG
can VERB - O
improve VERB - O
survival NOUN - O
for ADP - O
men NOUN - O
with ADP - O
newly ADV - O
diagnosed VERB - O
prostate NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
that ADJ - O
has VERB - O
spread VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

N. NNP - B-ORG
Clarke NNP - I-ORG

# NOUN - O
NCRI2015 NNP - B-GPE

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Could VERB - O
a DET - O
breast NOUN - O
cancer NOUN - O
drug NOUN - O
wipe VERB - O
out ADV - O
MRSA NNPS - B-ORG
in ADP - O
hospitals NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

Tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
can VERB - O
help VERB - O
the DET - O
body NOUN - O
trap NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
kill VERB - O
... PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Tired JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

I PRON - O
hate VERB - O
dos ADP - O
wage NOUN - O
changes NOUN - O
in ADP - O
lamotrigine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

The DET - O
tiredness NOUN - O
is VERB - O
always ADV - O
sudden ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
New NNP - B-ORG
York NNP - I-ORG
Times NNP - I-ORG
story NOUN - O
in ADP - O
March NNP - B-DATE
2011 CD - I-DATE
detailed ADJ - O
FDA NNP - B-ORG
warnings NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Topamax NNP - B-ORG
raising VERB - O
the DET - O
risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
birth NN - B-Disease_Symptom
defects NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O
   SPACE - O

1.713.238.7758 PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Fun ADJ - O
fact NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
Ciprofloxacin NNP - B-Drug
destroys VERB - O
your ADJ - O
Achilles NNPS - B-PRODUCT
tendon ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Pretreatment NOUN - O
metabotypes NOUN - O
may VERB - O
predict VERB - O
which ADJ - O
depressed JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
patients NOUN - O
will VERB - O
respond VERB - O
to ADP - O
acute ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
16 CD - B-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
) PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
sertraline NN - B-Drug
or CCONJ - O
placebo NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

BACKGROUND NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Combinations NOUN - O
of ADP - O
trastuzumab NOUN - O
with ADP - O
either CCONJ - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
or CCONJ - O
vinorelbine NOUN - O
are VERB - O
considered VERB - O
valuable ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
options NOUN - O
for ADP - O
HER PROPN - O
43 NUM - O
-positive PUNCT - O
metastatic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
breast NN - I-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
patients NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

never ADV - O
take VERB - O
a DET - O
vyvanse NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
adderall NN - B-Drug
at ADP - O
8 CD - B-TIME
pm NN - I-TIME
cause NOUN - O
you PRON - O
wo VERB - O
n't ADV - O
sleep VB - B-Disease_Symptom
at ADV - O
all ADV - O
😒 NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Management NOUN - O
of ADP - O
attention NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
deficit NOUN - O
hyperactivity NOUN - O
disorder NOUN - O
in ADP - O
adults NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
focus VERB - O
on ADP - O
methylphenidate JJ - B-Drug
hydrochloride NN - I-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

yesterday NN - B-DATE
: PUNCT - O
plenty NOUN - O
of ADP - O
sleep NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
copious ADJ - O
amount NOUN - O
of ADP - O
coffee NOUN - O
& CCONJ - O
amp NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
vyvanse NN - B-Drug
= ADP - O
me PRON - O
dead ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
unproductive ADJ - O
zombie NN - B-Disease_Symptom

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

METHODS NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

This DET - O
is VERB - O
a DET - O
retrospective ADJ - O
review NOUN - O
of ADP - O
all DET - O
retinoblastoma NN - B-Disease_Symptom
patients NOUN - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
intra ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
arterial ADJ - O
melphalan NN - B-Drug
at ADP - O
the DT - B-ORG
University NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
California NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
San NNP - B-GPE
Francisco NNP - I-GPE
from ADP - O
March NNP - B-DATE
9 CD - I-DATE
to IN - I-DATE
August NNP - I-DATE
9 CD - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Zoloft NNP - B-GPE
seriously ADV - O
makes VERB - O
you PRON - O
sweat VB - B-Disease_Symptom
like ADP - O
no DET - O
other ADJ - O

it PRON - O
's VERB - O
embarrassing ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
purpose NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
study NOUN - O
was VERB - O
to PART - O
investigate VERB - O
the DET - O
toxicity NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
efficacy NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
combination NOUN - O
of ADP - O
gemcitabine NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
untreated ADJ - O
advanced JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
urothelial JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
carcinoma NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Lisdexamfetamine NOUN - O
dimesylate NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
LDX PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
is VERB - O
approved VERB - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
once ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
daily JJ - B-DATE
treatment NOUN - O
for ADP - O
attention NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
deficit NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
hyperactivity NOUN - O
disorder NOUN - O
in ADP - O
children NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
adolescents NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
adults NOUN - O
in ADP - O
some DET - O
countries NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Asthma NN - B-ORG
control NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
patient ADJ - O
perception NOUN - O
were VERB - O
assessed VERB - O
prior ADV - O
to ADP - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
92 CD - B-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
after ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
introduction NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Montelukast NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
pre ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
introduction ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
post ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
introduction ADJ - O
results NOUN - O
were VERB - O
compared VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
CYP NNP - B-ORG
18 CD - B-CARDINAL
C NOUN - O
18 CD - B-CARDINAL
polymorphisms NOUN - O
on ADP - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
sensitivity NOUN - O
may VERB - O
therefore ADV - O
not ADV - O
only ADV - O
be VERB - O
mediated VERB - O
by ADP - O
a DET - O
variation NOUN - O
in ADP - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
metabolite NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
but CCONJ - O
also ADV - O
by ADP - O
an DET - O
effect NOUN - O
on ADP - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
risk NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
molecular NOUN - O
subtype NOUN - O
due ADJ - O
to ADP - O
variation NOUN - O
in ADP - O
lifelong ADJ - O
exposure NOUN - O
to ADP - O
estrogens NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
effect NOUN - O
of ADP - O
olanzapine NN - B-Drug
augmentation NOUN - O
therapy NOUN - O
on ADP - O
other ADJ - O
features NOUN - O
of ADP - O
sleep NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
e.g. ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
sleep NN - B-Disease_Symptom
continuity NN - I-Disease_Symptom
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
e.g. ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
illness NOUN - O
severity NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
cognitive ADJ - O
function NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
were VERB - O
also ADV - O
determined VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

No DET - O
changes NOUN - O
in ADP - O
blood NOUN - O
pressure NOUN - O
were VERB - O
found VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
pulse NN - B-Disease_Symptom
decreased VBD - I-Disease_Symptom
  SPACE - O

36 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
+ CCONJ - O
/- PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O

36 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
for ADP - O
haloperidol NOUN - O
with ADP - O
lorazepam ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
  SPACE - O
36 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
+ CCONJ - O
/- PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O

36 CD - B-CARDINAL
  SPACE - O
for ADP - O
ziprasidone NN - B-CARDINAL
( PUNCT - O
P NOUN - O
= SYM - O
NS PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

We PRON - O
hereby ADV - O
report VERB - O
our ADJ - O
experience NOUN - O
with ADP - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
treatment NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
refractory NOUN - O
CDH NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

# $ - B-CARDINAL
QandA PROPN - O

More ADJ - O
research NOUN - O
needs VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
done VERB - O
in ADP - O
regards NOUN - O
to PART - O
asthma NN - B-Disease_Symptom
med VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

Singulair NNP - B-ORG
( PUNCT - O
Montelukast NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
causes VERB - O
neuropsychiatric ADJ - O
side NOUN - O
effects NOUN - O
in ADP - O
kids NOUN - O
! PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Operation NOUN - O
Bilgy PROPN - O
Cortisone NNP - B-Drug
– ADV - O
protecting VERB - O
Australia NNP - B-GPE
from ADP - O
virilisms NNS - B-Disease_Symptom

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

He PRON - O
doubled VERB - O
the DET - O
dose NOUN - O
of ADP - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
87 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
on ADP - O
the DT - B-TIME
night NN - I-TIME
prior ADV - O
to ADP - O
presentation NOUN - O
to PART - O
calm VERB - O
his ADJ - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
numbing NN - B-Disease_Symptom
of IN - I-Disease_Symptom
my PRP$ - I-Disease_Symptom
knee NN - I-Disease_Symptom
has VERB - O
worn VERB - O
off PART - O
. PUNCT - O

Please INTJ - O
start VERB - O
working VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
cortisone NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

Plllleeeaaasseee PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

🙌 JJ - B-PERSON
🏼 PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

One CD - B-CARDINAL
such ADJ - O
recent ADJ - O
development NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
lisdexamfetamine NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
LDX NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
was VERB - O
FDA NNP - B-ORG
approved VERB - O
for ADP - O
treating VERB - O
ADHD NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
children NOUN - O
in ADP - O
early JJ - B-DATE
81 CD - I-DATE
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
adults NOUN - O
in ADP - O
early JJ - B-DATE
81 CD - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Seeing VERB - O
6th JJ - B-ORDINAL
pt NOUN - O
s NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
p X - O
# NOUN - O
labralrepair NOUN - O
w ADP - O
recurrent NOUN - O
# NN - B-CARDINAL
pelvicpain NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Never ADV - O
c NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
o'd ADV - O
hip NOUN - O
pain NOUN - O
& CCONJ - O
amp NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
cortisone NN - B-Drug
injection NOUN - O
failed VERB - O
to PART - O
help VERB - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
vulvodynia NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

# $ - B-CARDINAL
pelvicmafia PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

day NOUN - O
2 NUM - O
of ADP - O
Latuda NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
starting VERB - O
to PART - O
notice VERB - O
similar ADJ - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
as ADP - O
what NOUN - O
I PRON - O
had VERB - O
on ADP - O
Geodon NNP - B-PERSON
but CCONJ - O
at ADP - O
a DET - O
more ADV - O
manageable ADJ - O
amount NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Stop VERB - O
talking VERB - O
about ADP - O
# SYM - O
VamosEspaña NNP - B-ORG
! PUNCT - O

Let VERB - O
's PRON - O
discuss VERB - O
Citalopram NNP - B-PERSON
Tratamiento NNP - I-PERSON
Alcoholismo NNP - I-PERSON
New NNP - I-PERSON
England PROPN - O
! PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

METHODS NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Commercially ADV - O
insured VERB - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
fibromyalgia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
aged VERB - O
92 CD - B-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
who NOUN - O
initiated VERB - O
duloxetine NN - B-Drug
or CCONJ - O
pregabalin NOUN - O
in ADP - O
92 CD - B-CARDINAL
with ADP - O
92 CD - B-CARDINAL
-month NOUN - O
continuous ADJ - O
enrollment NOUN - O
before ADP - O
and CCONJ - O
after ADP - O
initiation NOUN - O
were VERB - O
identified VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

We PRON - O
described VERB - O
a DET - O
very ADV - O
rare ADJ - O
case NOUN - O
of ADP - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
induced VERB - O
acute ADJ - O
onset NOUN - O
myopia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
during ADP - O
use NOUN - O
for ADP - O
migraine NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

We PRON - O
present VERB - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
of ADP - O
a DET - O
63 CD - B-CARDINAL
-year NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
old ADJ - O
boy NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
who NOUN - O
had VERB - O
severe ADJ - O
relapsing VERB - O
pancreatitis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
three CD - B-CARDINAL
times NOUN - O
in ADP - O
two CD - B-DATE
months NNS - I-DATE
within ADP - O
63 CD - B-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
after ADP - O
starting VERB - O
treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
methylphenidate NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
Ritalin NNP - B-PERSON
) PUNCT - O
due ADP - O
to ADP - O
attention NN - B-Disease_Symptom
deficit NN - I-Disease_Symptom
hyperactivity NN - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
ADHD NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Bloody ADJ - O
citalopram NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

Takes VERB - O
six CD - B-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
to PART - O
start VERB - O
having VERB - O
an DET - O
effect NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
miss VERB - O
it PRON - O
for ADP - O
two CD - B-DATE
days NNS - I-DATE

and CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
have VERB - O
an DET - O
emotional JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
breakdown NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Quetiapine NNP - B-GPE
has VERB - O
demonstrated VERB - O
efficacy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
schizophrenia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
specific ADJ - O
symptom NOUN - O
clusters NOUN - O
such ADJ - O
as ADP - O
agitation NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
sleep NN - B-Disease_Symptom
problems NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
mood NN - B-Disease_Symptom
disorders NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

prozac NN - B-Drug
made VERB - O
me PRON - O
tired JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
suicidal NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
numb JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

but CCONJ - O
at ADP - O
least ADJ - O
it PRON - O
stopped VERB - O
me PRON - O
from ADP - O
turning VERB - O
into ADP - O
a DET - O
complete ADJ - O
wreck NOUN - O
like ADP - O
now ADV - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
rapid ADJ - O
onset NOUN - O
of ADP - O
sertraline NN - B-Drug
plus CCONJ - O
short ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
term NOUN - O
deanxit NOUN - O
indicated VERB - O
that ADP - O
it PRON - O
might VERB - O
be VERB - O
an DET - O
inspiring ADJ - O
strategy NOUN - O
to PART - O
manage VERB - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
within ADP - O
the DT - B-DATE
first JJ - I-DATE
two CD - I-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
in ADP - O
chronic ADJ - O
somatic ADJ - O
diseases NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
not ADV - O
a DET - O
doctor NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
anything NOUN - O

but CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
just ADV - O
realized VERB - O
the DET - O
ER PROPN - O
DO PROPN - O
prescribed VERB - O
50 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
prednisone JJ - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
800 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg PRON - O
ibuprofen ADJ - O
... PUNCT - O

won't ADJ - O
that ADJ - O
cause NOUN - O
GI NNP - B-ORG
ulceration NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

To ADP - O
the DET - O
best ADJ - O
of ADP - O
our ADJ - O
knowledge NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
this DET - O
is VERB - O
the DET - O
largest ADJ - O
population NOUN - O
based VERB - O
study NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
shows VERB - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
use NOUN - O
for ADP - O
more JJR - B-DATE
than IN - I-DATE
three CD - I-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
or CCONJ - O
patients NOUN - O
older JJR - B-DATE
than IN - I-DATE
32 CD - I-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
was VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
a DET - O
significantly ADV - O
increased VERB - O
risk NOUN - O
for ADP - O
developing VERB - O
endometrial JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Fluoxetine NN - B-Drug
induces VERB - O
vasodilatation NN - B-Disease_Symptom
of ADP - O
cerebral ADJ - O
arterioles NOUN - O
by ADP - O
co NOUN - O
- ADJ - O
modulating ADJ - O
NO DET - O
/ SYM - O
muscarinic ADJ - O
signalling NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
results NOUN - O
for ADP - O
duloxetine NN - B-Drug
are VERB - O
compared VERB - O
with ADP - O
published VERB - O
data NOUN - O
for ADP - O
other ADJ - O
antidepressants NOUN - O
in ADP - O
neuropathic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
pain NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

They PRON - O
found VERB - O
that ADP - O
the DET - O
risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
suicide NN - B-Disease_Symptom
was VERB - O
higher ADJ - O
in ADP - O
people NOUN - O
who NOUN - O
received VERB - O
fluoxetine NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
79 CD - B-CARDINAL
per ADP - O
79 CD - B-DATE
, PUNCT - O
79 CD - B-DATE
person NN - I-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
, PUNCT - O
79 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
CI PROPN - O
79 NUM - O
to PART - O
79 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
than ADP - O
in ADP - O
those DET - O
receiving VERB - O
dosulepine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
dothiepin NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
view NOUN - O
of ADP - O
this DET - O
clinical ADJ - O
picture NOUN - O
a DET - O
provisional ADJ - O
diagnosis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
angioedema NN - B-Disease_Symptom
secondary ADJ - O
to ADP - O
Lisinopril NNP - B-ORG
was VERB - O
made VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
it PRON - O
was VERB - O
discontinued VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Phase VERB - O
II NNP - B-ORG
multicentre ADV - O
randomised VERB - O
study NOUN - O
of ADP - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
plus CCONJ - O
epirubicin NOUN - O
vs ADP - O
59 CD - B-CARDINAL
-fluorouracil ADJ - O
plus CCONJ - O
epirubicin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
cyclophosphamide VERB - O
in ADP - O
metastatic ADJ - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Bilateral ADJ - O
cystoid NN - B-Disease_Symptom
macular NN - I-Disease_Symptom
edema NN - I-Disease_Symptom
following VERB - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
chemotherapy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
patient NOUN - O
with ADP - O
retinitis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
pigmentosa NN - I-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
report NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Both DET - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
citalopram NN - B-Drug
have VERB - O
been VERB - O
related VERB - O
to ADP - O
the DET - O
increase NN - B-Disease_Symptom
of IN - I-Disease_Symptom
intraocular JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
pressure NN - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
development NOUN - O
of ADP - O
glaucoma NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Available ADJ - O
studies NOUN - O
specifically ADV - O
addressing VERB - O
the DET - O
role NOUN - O
of ADP - O
montelukast NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
the DET - O
elderly ADJ - O
are VERB - O
scarce ADJ - O
; PUNCT - O
however ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
leukotriene NOUN - O
modifiers NOUN - O
have VERB - O
been VERB - O
demonstrated VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
safe ADJ - O
in ADP - O
this DET - O
age NOUN - O
group NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
even ADV - O
though ADP - O
cases NOUN - O
of ADP - O
acute ADJ - O
hepatitis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
occurrence NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Churg NNP - B-ORG
- HYPH - I-ORG
Strauss NNP - I-ORG
syndrome NOUN - O
have VERB - O
been VERB - O
described VERB - O
in ADP - O
elderly ADJ - O
patients NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
whether ADP - O
this DET - O
is VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
age NOUN - O
is VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
confirmed VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Epilepsies NNS - B-Disease_Symptom
with ADP - O
primary ADJ - O
or CCONJ - O
unclassified ADJ - O
GTCs NOUN - O
can VERB - O
respond VERB - O
to ADP - O
any DET - O
one CD - B-CARDINAL
of ADP - O
the DET - O
five CD - B-CARDINAL
broad ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
spectrum ADJ - O
antiepileptic ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
AEDs NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
: PUNCT - O
valproate NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
lamotrigine NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
levetiracetam NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
zonisamide NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CONCLUSIONS NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Overall ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
regimen NOUN - O
of ADP - O
T PROPN - O
- PUNCT - O
DM PROPN - O
1 NUM - O
as ADV - O
well ADV - O
as ADP - O
pertuzumab ADJ - O
in ADP - O
combination NOUN - O
with ADP - O
trastuzumab NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
is VERB - O
efficacious ADJ - O
with ADP - O
fewer ADJ - O
side NOUN - O
effects NOUN - O
as ADP - O
compared VERB - O
with ADP - O
other ADJ - O
regimens NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
especially ADV - O
for ADP - O
advanced ADJ - O
HER PROPN - O
1 NUM - O
+ CCONJ - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
've VERB - O
lost VERB - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
st NOUN - O
12 CD - B-CARDINAL
lbs NOUN - O
in ADP - O
11 CD - B-DATE
months NNS - I-DATE
! PUNCT - O

Nearly ADV - O
back ADV - O
to ADP - O
my ADJ - O
skinny ADJ - O
self NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

# $ - B-MONEY
IHateQuetiapine NN - I-MONEY

# SYM - O
Quetiapine NOUN - O
# NOUN - O
weightloss ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

You PRON - O
're VERB - O
on ADP - O
suboxone NN - B-Drug

but CCONJ - O
you PRON - O
're VERB - O
clean ADJ - O
? PUNCT - O

Ok INTJ - O
bro NOUN - O
... PUNCT - O

Whatever ADJ - O
helps VERB - O
you PRON - O
sleep VB - B-Disease_Symptom
at ADP - O
night NN - B-TIME
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Feeling VERB - O
so ADV - O
much ADV - O
better ADJ - O
being VERB - O
manic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
is VERB - O
rough ADJ - O
I PRON - O
experience VERB - O
racing NN - B-Disease_Symptom
thoughts NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
high ADJ - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
etc X - O
. PUNCT - O

Lamictal NNP - B-PERSON
is VERB - O
helping VERB - O
# $ - B-MONEY
BipolarDisorder NNP - I-MONEY
# $ - I-MONEY
mania NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Moderate ADJ - O
risk NOUN - O
for ADP - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
breastcancer NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
consider VERB - O
use NOUN - O
of ADP - O
SERMs NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
raloxifene NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
; PUNCT - O
data NOUN - O
on ADP - O
benefit NOUN - O
incomplete ADJ - O
in ADP - O
this DET - O
risk NOUN - O
profile NOUN - O

# SYM - O
NSGC2015 PROPN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
've VERB - O
been VERB - O
up ADV - O
since ADP - O
6 CD - B-TIME
am VBP - I-TIME
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
busy ADJ - O
all DET - O
day NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

You PRON - O
'd VERB - O
think VERB - O
I PRON - O
'd VERB - O
be VERB - O
asleep JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
... PUNCT - O
nope INTJ - O
. PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O

Thanks NOUN - O
# PROPN - O
Prednisone NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

fucking VERB - O
love NOUN - O
zyprexa NNS - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
i PRON - O
just ADV - O
ate VERB - O
an DET - O
enitre ADJ - O
chicken NOUN - O
alfredo NOUN - O
thing NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
was VERB - O
meant VERB - O
for ADP - O
like INTJ - O
4 CD - B-CARDINAL
people NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
i PRON - O
am VERB - O
still ADV - O
hungry JJ - B-Disease_Symptom

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

# SYM - O
AAFPFMX NNP - B-PERSON
Duloxetine NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
while ADP - O
indicated VERB - O
for ADP - O
treating VERB - O
fibromyalgia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
has VERB - O
small ADJ - O
to PART - O
moderate ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
on ADP - O
the DET - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
scores NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

They PRON - O
put VERB - O
me PRON - O
on ADP - O
xanex NOUN - O
for ADP - O
my ADJ - O
# NN - B-CARDINAL
anxiety NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
zyprexa NN - B-Drug
for ADP - O
my ADJ - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
bipolardisorder NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

some DT - B-DATE
days NNS - I-DATE
I PRON - O
feel VERB - O
like ADP - O
a DET - O
zombie NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
but CCONJ - O
I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
optimistic ADJ - O
about ADP - O
it PRON - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
results NOUN - O
of ADP - O
this DET - O
study NOUN - O
suggest VERB - O
that ADP - O
duloxetine NN - B-Drug
may VERB - O
provide VERB - O
a DET - O
significant ADJ - O
reduction NOUN - O
in ADP - O
symptoms NOUN - O
for ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
obsessive ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
compulsive ADJ - O
disorder NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Shrink PROPN - O
doubled VERB - O
my ADJ - O
Lamictal NNP - B-NORP
dose NOUN - O
to ADP - O
200 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
daily RB - B-DATE
. PUNCT - O

My ADJ - O
Trazadone NN - B-Drug
from ADP - O
50 CD - B-QUANTITY
mg NN - I-QUANTITY
to ADP - O
150 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
at ADP - O
bedtime NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

This DET - O
could VERB - O
be VERB - O
interesting ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

# SYM - O
BiPolarFun ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

If ADP - O
you PRON - O
hate VERB - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
cymbalta NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
you PRON - O
know VERB - O
it PRON - O
clap VERB - O
your ADJ - O
hands NOUN - O
! PUNCT - O

😣 VERB - O
😩 PROPN - O
😷 NOUN - O
😤 NUM - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
👏 PROPN - O
# SYM - O
spoonie NOUN - O
# $ - B-MONEY
chronicillness NN - I-MONEY

# $ - B-MONEY
invisibleillness NN - I-MONEY

# NN - B-CARDINAL
chronicpain NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

BACKGROUND NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

To PART - O
report VERB - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
of ADP - O
branch NOUN - O
retinal JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
vein NN - I-Disease_Symptom
occlusion NN - I-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
a DET - O
young ADJ - O
adult NOUN - O
with ADP - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
mood NN - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
quetiapine NN - B-Drug
fumarate ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Risk NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Mortality PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
including VERB - O
Sudden NNP - B-ORG
Cardiac NNP - I-ORG
Death NNP - I-ORG
) PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
Major PROPN - O
Cardiovascular NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
Events NNPS - I-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
Users NNPS - B-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Olanzapine NNP - I-ORG
and CC - I-ORG
Other JJ - I-ORG
Antipsychotics NNPS - I-ORG
: PUNCT - O
A DET - O
Study NOUN - O
with ADP - O
the DET - O
General PROPN - O
Practice PROPN - O
Research PROPN - O
Database PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

DID VBD - B-PERSON
U NNP - I-PERSON
KNOW NNP - I-PERSON
: PUNCT - O
five CD - B-TIME
minutes NNS - I-TIME
of ADP - O
Radiohead NNP - B-GPE
can VERB - O
immediately ADV - O
nullify VERB - O
2 CD - B-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
of ADP - O
effexor NN - B-Drug
? PUNCT - O

# $ - B-MONEY
SAD NN - I-MONEY
# $ - I-MONEY
pnw NN - I-MONEY

# NN - B-MONEY
grey NN - I-MONEY
# NN - B-CARDINAL
roughoutthere NOUN - O

# SYM - O
depressionisreal ADJ - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Secondary ADJ - O
Bilateral ADJ - O
Angle NOUN - O
Closure NOUN - O
Glaucoma NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
due ADP - O
to ADP - O
Topiramate NNP - B-ORG
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Treatment NOUN - O
was VERB - O
started VERB - O
with ADP - O
prednisone NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
azithromycin NOUN - O
with ADP - O
subsequent ADJ - O
improvement NOUN - O
in ADP - O
vision NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CASE NNP - B-ORG
PRESENTATION PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O

A NOUN - O
46 CD - B-CARDINAL
-year PUNCT - O
- PUNCT - O
old ADJ - O
female NOUN - O
complained VERB - O
of ADP - O
sudden ADJ - O
onset NOUN - O
of ADP - O
blurred VBN - B-Disease_Symptom
vision NN - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
46 CD - B-DATE
days NNS - I-DATE
prior ADV - O
to ADP - O
this DET - O
she PRON - O
had VERB - O
commenced VERB - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
therapy NOUN - O
for ADP - O
migraine NN - B-Disease_Symptom
prophylaxis NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

So CCONJ - O
fellow ADJ - O
pre ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
menopausal ADJ - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
survivors NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
what NOUN - O
is VERB - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
like ADP - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
objective NOUN - O
of ADP - O
this DET - O
study NOUN - O
was VERB - O
to PART - O
evaluate VERB - O
the DET - O
effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
rupatadine NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
RUP NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
versus ADP - O
desloratadine NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
DES PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
subjects NOUN - O
with ADP - O
seasonal ADJ - O
allergic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
rhinitis NN - I-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
SAR NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Is VERB - O
steroid ADV - O
induced VERB - O
psychosis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
a DET - O
thing NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

( PUNCT - O
Like ADP - O
short ADJ - O
term NOUN - O
prednisone NN - B-Drug
tx NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
aripiprazole NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
an DET - O
obese ADJ - O
subject NOUN - O
with ADP - O
borderline NOUN - O
personality NN - B-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
obsessive ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
compulsive ADJ - O
symptoms NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
bulimia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
nervosa NN - I-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
case NOUN - O
report NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

This DET - O
62 CD - B-CARDINAL
-week NOUN - O
randomized VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
double ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
blind ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
placebo NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
controlled VERB - O
clinical ADJ - O
trial NOUN - O
will VERB - O
compare VERB - O
the DET - O
efficacy NOUN - O
of ADP - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
with ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
study VERB - O
the DET - O
tolerability NOUN - O
of ADP - O
topiramate NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
PTSD NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Cholestatic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
jaundice NN - I-Disease_Symptom
induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
duloxetine NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
a DET - O
patient NOUN - O
with ADP - O
major JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
depressive JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Ovarian ADJ - O
cysts NOUN - O
in ADP - O
women NOUN - O
receiving VERB - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
for ADP - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Hey INTJ - O
# NOUN - O
breastcancer NOUN - O
people- NOUN - O
anyone NOUN - O
on ADP - O
# SYM - O
Tamoxifen PROPN - O
and CCONJ - O
# SYM - O
Prozac NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

Hearing VERB - O
it PRON - O
can VERB - O
make VERB - O
the DET - O
hormone NOUN - O
blocker NOUN - O
not ADV - O
work VERB - O
as ADV - O
well ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

Anyone NOUN - O
else ADV - O
hear VERB - O
this DET - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

fluoxetine NN - B-Drug
) PUNCT - O
can VERB - O
reduce VERB - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
- PUNCT - O
related VERB - O
behaviors NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

having VERB - O
sweaty NN - B-Disease_Symptom
palms NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
as ADP - O
a DET - O
citalopram NN - B-Drug
side NOUN - O
effect NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
using VERB - O
a DET - O
computer NOUN - O
mouse NOUN - O
sucks VERB - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Major ADJ - O
reanalysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
original ADJ - O
trial NOUN - O
docs NOUN - O
from ADP - O
# $ - B-MONEY
GSK NNP - I-MONEY
’s POS - I-MONEY
# $ - B-CARDINAL
Study NOUN - O
329 CD - B-CARDINAL
, PUNCT - O
concludes VERB - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
paroxetine NOUN - O
neither CCONJ - O
safe ADJ - O
nor CCONJ - O
effective ADJ - O
4 CD - B-CARDINAL
adoles'ts NOUN - O
w/ NOUN - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
cortisone NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
chemical NOUN - O
inflammation NOUN - O
on ADP - O
experimental ADJ - O
mucormycosis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
Rhizopus NOUN - O
oryzae VERB - O
infection NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Thus ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
we PRON - O
hypothesized VERB - O
that ADP - O
CVD NNP - B-ORG
would VERB - O
prevent VERB - O
and/or CCONJ - O
reverse VERB - O
mania NN - B-Disease_Symptom
- PUNCT - O
like ADJ - O
behavioral ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
neurochemical ADJ - O
alterations NOUN - O
induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
lisdexamfetamine NN - B-Drug
dimesylate NN - I-Drug
( PUNCT - O
LDX PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Three CD - B-CARDINAL
patients NOUN - O
had VERB - O
resolution NOUN - O
of ADP - O
canaliculitis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
on ADP - O
combination NOUN - O
broad ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
spectrum NOUN - O
topical ADJ - O
antibiotic ADJ - O
therapy NOUN - O
using VERB - O
ciprofloxacin NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
fortified VERB - O
cefazolin NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Duloxetine NNP - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
serotonin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
noradrenaline ADJ - O
reuptake NOUN - O
inhibitor NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
celecoxib NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
non ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
steroidal ADJ - O
anti ADJ - O
- ADJ - O
inflammatory ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
are VERB - O
commonly ADV - O
used VERB - O
analgesics NOUN - O
for ADP - O
persistent ADJ - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
however ADV - O
with ADP - O
moderate ADJ - O
gastrointestinal JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
side NOUN - O
effects NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
analgesia NOUN - O
tolerance NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

.@NoraReed PUNCT - O

woot VERB - O
! PUNCT - O

Yeah INTJ - O
, PUNCT - O
Effexor NNP - B-PERSON
was VERB - O
a DET - O
wonder NOUN - O
drug NOUN - O
in ADP - O
college NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
it PRON - O
turned VERB - O
me PRON - O
from ADP - O
a DET - O
really ADV - O
really ADV - O
anxious JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
kid NOUN - O
into ADP - O
a DET - O
really ADV - O
anxious JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
kid NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
exact ADJ - O
pathogenesis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
DRESS JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
syndrome NN - I-Disease_Symptom
is VERB - O
not ADV - O
completely ADV - O
understood VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
while ADP - O
it PRON - O
is VERB - O
reported VERB - O
that ADP - O
amoxicillin NOUN - O
could VERB - O
trigger VERB - O
it PRON - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
who NOUN - O
are VERB - O
taking VERB - O
allopurinol NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
sulfasalazine NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
NSAIDs PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
carbamazepine NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
strontium NOUN - O
ranelate NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
lisinopril JJ - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
lansoprazole NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
minocycline NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

PiperJ VERB - O
: PUNCT - O
" PUNCT - O
$ SYM - O
HALO PROPN - O
Broad PROPN - O
Potential PROPN - O
for ADP - O
PEGPH20 NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Onco PROPN - O
May PROPN - O
Emerge PROPN - O
in ADP - O
Near PROPN - O
Term PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
PEGPH20 PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
+ SYM - O
docetaxel NNP - B-Drug
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
second JJ - B-ORDINAL
- PUNCT - O
line NOUN - O
NSCLC NNP - B-ORG
update NOUN - O
in ADP - O
November NNP - B-DATE
. PUNCT - O

" PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Bevacizumab NNP - B-Drug
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
glioblastoma NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

PURPOSE PROPN - O
: PUNCT - O

To PART - O
examine VERB - O
the DET - O
impact NOUN - O
of ADP - O
newly ADV - O
initiated VERB - O
pregabalin NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
duloxetine VB - B-Drug
treatment NOUN - O
on ADP - O
fibromyalgia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
( PUNCT - O
FM PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
patients NOUN - O
' PART - O
encounters NOUN - O
with ADP - O
potential ADJ - O
drug NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
drug NOUN - O
interactions NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
DDIs PROPN - O
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
the DET - O
health NOUN - O
care NOUN - O
cost NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
utilization NOUN - O
consequences NOUN - O
of ADP - O
those DET - O
interactions NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
impact NOUN - O
of ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
on ADP - O
opioid ADJ - O
utilization NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

vyvanse NN - B-Drug
makes VERB - O
me PRON - O
like ADP - O
SOOOO PROPN - O
damn ADV - O
happy JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
until ADP - O
the DT - B-DATE
next JJ - I-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
then ADV - O
i PRON - O
m VERB - O
like INTJ - O
painfully ADV - O
depressed JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
but CCONJ - O
like INTJ - O
........ PUNCT - O

worth ADJ - O
it PRON - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

All ADJ - O
the DET - O
shyt ADV - O
- PUNCT - O
slinging VERB - O
politicians NOUN - O
are VERB - O
leaving VERB - O
me PRON - O
depressed JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O

It PRON - O
's VERB - O
time NOUN - O
for ADP - O
my ADJ - O
Effexor NNP - B-PERSON
XR NNP - I-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
I PRON - O
guess VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Comparison NOUN - O
of ADP - O
therapeutic ADJ - O
effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
omega NOUN - O
12 CD - B-CARDINAL
and CCONJ - O
methylphenidate NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
ritalin NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
treating VERB - O
children NOUN - O
with ADP - O
attention NN - B-Disease_Symptom
deficit NN - I-Disease_Symptom
hyperactivity NN - I-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

--Question NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Those DET - O
who NOUN - O
are VERB - O
taking VERB - O
or CCONJ - O
have VERB - O
taken VERB - O
# SYM - O
Prozac NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
what NOUN - O
did VERB - O
it PRON - O
make VERB - O
you PRON - O
feel VERB - O
like ADP - O
? PUNCT - O

# NN - B-CARDINAL
bpd ADP - O
# NN - B-MONEY
mentalillness NN - I-MONEY
# NN - I-MONEY
ptsd NN - I-MONEY

# NN - B-CARDINAL
pmdd X - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
other ADJ - O
news NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
I PRON - O
met VERB - O
a DET - O
cute ADJ - O
old ADJ - O
guy NOUN - O
with ADP - O
horrible ADJ - O
angioedema NN - B-Disease_Symptom
due ADP - O
to ADP - O
lisinopril NN - B-Drug

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CUSP PROPN - O
28 NUM - O
* PUNCT - O
treatment NOUN - O
protocol NOUN - O
for ADP - O
recurrent NOUN - O
glioblastoma NN - B-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
aprepitant NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
artesunate VERB - O
, PUNCT - O
auranofin NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
captopril NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
celecoxib NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
disulfiram NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
itraconazole NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
ritonavir NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
sertraline NN - B-Drug
augmenting VERB - O
continuous ADJ - O
low ADJ - O
dose NOUN - O
temozolomide NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

This DET - O
study NOUN - O
aimed VERB - O
to PART - O
evaluate VERB - O
the DET - O
effectiveness NOUN - O
of ADP - O
electroconvulsive ADJ - O
therapy NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
ECT NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
persistent ADJ - O
METH NNP - B-ORG
psychosis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
patients NOUN - O
hospitalized VERB - O
at ADP - O
Shahid NNP - B-ORG
Beheshti NNP - I-ORG
Hospital NNP - I-ORG
, PUNCT - O
Kerman NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
Iran NNP - B-GPE
, PUNCT - O
from ADP - O
12 CD - B-CARDINAL
September NNP - B-DATE
12 CD - I-DATE
until ADP - O
12 CD - B-DATE
September NNP - I-DATE
12 CD - I-DATE
, PUNCT - O
who NOUN - O
were VERB - O
not ADV - O
remitted VERB - O
after ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
olanzapine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

i PRON - O
had VERB - O
heard VERB - O
that DET - O
modafinil NN - B-Drug
makes VERB - O
your ADJ - O
piss JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
smell NN - I-Disease_Symptom
bad JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

if ADP - O
you PRON - O
're VERB - O
wondering VERB - O
whether ADP - O
that DET - O
's VERB - O
true ADJ - O
: PUNCT - O

yes INTJ - O
. PUNCT - O

it PRON - O
is VERB - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Changes NOUN - O
in ADP - O
ovarian ADJ - O
function NOUN - O
in ADP - O
premenopausal ADJ - O
women NOUN - O
with ADP - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
undergoing VERB - O
adjuvant ADJ - O
TC PROPN - O
( PUNCT - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
cyclophosphamide NOUN - O
) PUNCT - O
chemotherapy NOUN - O
during ADP - O
a DET - O
brief ADJ - O
period NOUN - O
of ADP - O
amenorrhea NN - B-Disease_Symptom
around ADP - O
the DET - O
last ADJ - O
chemotherapy NOUN - O
cycle NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Montelukast NN - B-ORG
is VERB - O
a DET - O
selective ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
competitive ADJ - O
cysteinyl NOUN - O
leukotriene NOUN - O
receptor NOUN - O
antagonist NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
CystLTRA NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
is VERB - O
increasingly ADV - O
used VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
allergic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
asthma NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Long ADJ - O
term NOUN - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
therapy NOUN - O
may VERB - O
cause VERB - O
: PUNCT - O
? PUNCT - O

Answer NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Endometrium NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

BACKGROUND NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Carbamazepine NNP - B-Drug
has VERB - O
been VERB - O
used VERB - O
as ADP - O
AEDs NOUN - O
since ADP - O
80 CD - B-DATE
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
is VERB - O
most ADV - O
effective ADJ - O
against ADP - O
partial JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
seizures NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

duloxetine VB - B-Drug
compared VERB - O
with ADP - O
placebo NOUN - O
resulted VERB - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
greater ADJ - O
reduction NOUN - O
in ADP - O
pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
in IN - I-Disease_Symptom
OA NNP - I-Disease_Symptom
knee NN - I-Disease_Symptom
after ADP - O
approximately RB - B-DATE
10 CD - I-DATE
to TO - I-DATE
13 CD - I-DATE
weeks NNS - I-DATE
of ADP - O
therapy NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Meta ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
duloxetine NN - B-Drug
vs. X - O
pregabalin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
gabapentin NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
diabetic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
peripheral JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
neuropathic JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
pain NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

And CCONJ - O
this DET - O
is VERB - O
why ADV - O
after ADP - O
the DET - O
prednisone NN - B-Drug
is VERB - O
out ADP - O
of ADP - O
my ADJ - O
system NOUN - O

I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
going VERB - O
to PART - O
try VERB - O
citalopram NN - B-Drug
again ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

Fuck NOUN - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

As ADP - O
a DET - O
daily JJ - B-DATE
# NOUN - O
modafinil NOUN - O
user NOUN - O
( PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
a DET - O
sleep NN - B-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
) PUNCT - O
I PRON - O
keep VERB - O
an DET - O
eye NOUN - O
on ADP - O
headlines NOUN - O
like ADP - O
that DET - O
. PUNCT - O

Does VERB - O
n't ADV - O
seem VERB - O
get VERB - O
much ADJ - O
attention NOUN - O
in ADP - O
Australia NNP - B-GPE
though ADV - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
one CD - B-CARDINAL
case NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
phantom NOUN - O
limb NN - B-Disease_Symptom
pain NN - I-Disease_Symptom
responded VERB - O
partially ADV - O
to PART - O
treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
high ADJ - O
doses NOUN - O
of ADP - O
paroxetine NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
then ADV - O
replacement VERB - O
with ADP - O
milnacipran NOUN - O
further ADV - O
improved VERB - O
the DET - O
pain NOUN - O
relief NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
long ADJ - O
- PUNCT - O
term NOUN - O
full ADJ - O
pain NOUN - O
relief NOUN - O
was VERB - O
achieved VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

ha INTJ - O
, PUNCT - O
interacts NOUN - O
with ADP - O
topamax DT - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

think VERB - O
i PRON - O
took VERB - O
that DET - O
once ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

think VERB - O
it PRON - O
caused VERB - O
nightmares NNS - B-Disease_Symptom
or CCONJ - O
something NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

BACKGROUND NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Despite ADP - O
its ADJ - O
frequent ADJ - O
use NOUN - O
as ADP - O
a DET - O
hypnotic ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
has VERB - O
not ADV - O
been VERB - O
systematically ADV - O
assessed VERB - O
in ADP - O
fibromyalgia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
patients NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

never ADV - O
taken VERB - O
a DET - O
drug NOUN - O
like ADP - O
Effexor NNP - B-PERSON
- PUNCT - O
if ADP - O
i PRON - O
miss VERB - O
1 CD - B-CARDINAL
day(v NUM - O
rare)feel CCONJ - O
like ADP - O
i PRON - O
have VERB - O
the DET - O
flu&amp;am NOUN - O
ill.so PROPN - O
awful.but CCONJ - O

it PRON - O
seems VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
working VERB - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
mentalhealth NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Bronchiolitis NN - B-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
no DET - O
evidence NOUN - O
for ADP - O
antibx ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
Neva NNP - B-PERSON
, PUNCT - O
INHs NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
pred ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
montelukast NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

# SYM - O
GPupdate NN - B-MONEY

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

$ SYM - O
SNTA PROPN - O
Shares NOUN - O
Plunge PROPN - O
71 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT

After ADP - O
Terminating PROPN - O
Trial PROPN - O
of ADP - O
Lung NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
Cancer NNP - I-Disease_Symptom
Drugs NOUN - O
Ganetespib PROPN - O
, PUNCT - O
Docetaxel NNP - B-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Topiramate NN - B-Drug
deserves VERB - O
to PART - O
be VERB - O
investigated VERB - O
in ADP - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
comorbid NOUN - O
alcoholism NN - B-Disease_Symptom
since ADP - O
this DET - O
compound NOUN - O
effectively ADV - O
improves VERB - O
physical ADJ - O
health NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
quality NOUN - O
of ADP - O
life NOUN - O
of ADP - O
alcohol NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
dependent ADJ - O
individuals NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Lisinopril NNP - B-Drug
is VERB - O
an DET - O
angiotensin NOUN - O
- PUNCT - O
converting VERB - O
enzyme ADJ - O
( PUNCT - O
ACE NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
inhibitor NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
primarily ADV - O
used VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
hypertension NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
congestive JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
heart NN - I-Disease_Symptom
failure NN - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
heart NN - B-Disease_Symptom
attack NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
anticonvulsant NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
lamotrigine NN - B-Drug
( PUNCT - O
LMG NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
, PUNCT - O
reduces VERB - O
interictal ADJ - O
epileptiform NOUN - O
discharges NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
is VERB - O
effective ADJ - O
in ADP - O
seizures NNS - B-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
both CCONJ - O
primary ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
partial JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
epilepsy NN - I-Disease_Symptom
syndromes NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Mood NN - B-ORG
stabilizers NOUN - O
are VERB - O
used VERB - O
primarily ADV - O
in ADP - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O
  SPACE - O

Lithium NNP - B-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
Lamictal NNP - B-NORP
are VERB - O
notable ADJ - O
for ADP - O
treating VERB - O
both DET - O
mania NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Started VERB - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
for ADP - O
depression NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
insomnia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
yesterday NN - B-DATE
. PUNCT - O

I PRON - O
feel VERB - O
like ADP - O
a DET - O
zzzombie NOUN - O
today NN - B-DATE
. PUNCT - O

* PUNCT - O
crashes NOUN - O

* PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Additionally ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
lower ADJ - O
expression NOUN - O
levels NOUN - O
of ADP - O
miR NOUN - O
92 CD - B-CARDINAL
a DET - O
92 CD - B-QUANTITY
p NN - I-QUANTITY
were VERB - O
associated VERB - O
with ADP - O
poor ADJ - O
prognosis NOUN - O
for ADP - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
- PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

And CCONJ - O
my ADJ - O
advice NOUN - O
would VERB - O
be VERB - O
to PART - O
never ADV - O
touch VERB - O
venlafaxine NN - B-Drug
ever ADV - O
unless ADP - O
you PRON - O
're VERB - O
fond ADJ - O
of ADP - O
hallucinations NNS - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
vertigo NN - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
nausea NN - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

This DET - O
prednisone NN - B-Drug
has VERB - O
me PRON - O
swollen VB - B-Disease_Symptom
up RP - I-Disease_Symptom
like ADP - O
a DET - O
helium NN - B-Disease_Symptom
balloon NN - I-Disease_Symptom
! PUNCT - O
! PUNCT - O

🎈 PROPN - O

🎈 ADV - O

🎈 ADV - O

🎈 NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

We PRON - O
wish VERB - O
to PART - O
report VERB - O
another DET - O
case NOUN - O
of ADP - O
TD NNP - B-ORG
, PUNCT - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
male ADJ - O
patient NOUN - O
with ADP - O
schizophrenia NN - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
developed VERB - O
after ADP - O
27 CD - B-DATE
months NNS - I-DATE
of ADP - O
treatment NOUN - O
with ADP - O
olanzapine NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Omg NOUN - O
upped VERB - O
topamax DT - B-Drug
dose NOUN - O
on ADP - O
Thursday NNP - B-DATE
( PUNCT - O
for ADP - O
chronic ADJ - O
migraine NN - B-Disease_Symptom
) PUNCT - O
tonight NN - B-TIME
I PRON - O
ca VERB - O
n't ADV - O
stop VERB - O
itching VBG - B-Disease_Symptom
all ADV - O
over ADP - O

# SYM - O
topamax DT - B-Drug
# SYM - O
Migraine NN - B-Disease_Symptom
# NOUN - O
sideeffects VERB - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Both DET - O
first JJ - B-ORDINAL
and CCONJ - O
second JJ - B-ORDINAL
generation NOUN - O
antipsychotics NOUN - O
are VERB - O
widely ADV - O
used VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
FDA NNP - B-ORG
has VERB - O
approved VERB - O
olanzapine RB - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
risperidone NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
quetiapine NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
ziprasidone NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
aripiprazole NOUN - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
acute JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
mania NN - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Been VERB - O
to ADP - O
GP NNP - B-ORG
today- NOUN - O
dosage NOUN - O
of ADP - O
# $ - B-CARDINAL
migraine NOUN - O
meds NOUN - O
altered VERB - O
agn NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
lowered VERB - O
Betablockers NNS - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
propranolol NOUN - O
80 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
from ADP - O
160 CD - B-CARDINAL
) PUNCT - O
& CCONJ - O
amp NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
upped ADJ - O
Topiramate NN - B-ORG
to ADP - O
125 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
from ADP - O
75 CD - B-CARDINAL

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Dietary PROPN - O
intake NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
growth NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
development NOUN - O
of ADP - O
children NOUN - O
with ADP - O
ADHD NNP - B-ORG
in ADP - O
a DET - O
randomized VERB - O
clinical ADJ - O
trial NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Ritalin NNP - B-PERSON
and CCONJ - O
Melatonin NNP - B-PERSON
co NOUN - O
- NOUN - O
administration NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Through ADP - O
circadian JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
cycle NN - I-Disease_Symptom
modification NN - I-Disease_Symptom
or CCONJ - O
appetite NOUN - O
enhancement NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Randomized VERB - O
controlled VERB - O
study NOUN - O
of ADP - O
intravitreal NOUN - O
bevacizumab NN - B-Drug
0.16 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
injected VERB - O
one CD - B-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
before ADP - O
surgery NOUN - O
for ADP - O
proliferative JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
diabetic JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
retinopathy NN - I-Disease_Symptom
… NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

# SYM - O

WCLC2015 PUNCT - O
Adding VERB - O
bevacizumab NN - B-Drug
to PART - O
chemotherapy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
resected VERB - O
NSCLC NNP - B-ORG
did VERB - O
not ADV - O
improve VERB - O
overall ADJ - O
survival NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
according VERB - O
to ADP - O
new ADJ - O
data NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
guess VERB - O
a DET - O
cortisone NN - B-Drug
injection NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
foot NOUN - O
does VERB - O
n't ADV - O
last VERB - O
long ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

Only ADV - O
one CD - B-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
of ADP - O
not ADV - O
so ADV - O
bad ADJ - O
pain NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Results NOUN - O
of ADP - O
E1505 PROPN - O
announced VERB - O
for ADP - O
the DET - O
first JJ - B-ORDINAL
time NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

No DET - O
difference NOUN - O
in ADP - O
OS NNP - B-ORG
or CCONJ - O
DFS NNP - B-ORG
by ADP - O
adding VERB - O
Avastin NNP - B-PERSON
to PART - O
adjuvant ADJ - O
chemo NOUN - O
after ADP - O
surgery NOUN - O
in ADP - O
NSCLC NNP - B-ORG

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Since ADP - O
changing VERB - O
to ADP - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
falling VERB - O
asleep JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
around RB - B-TIME
10 CD - I-TIME
pm NN - I-TIME
at IN - I-TIME
night NN - I-TIME
. PUNCT - O

I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
usually ADV - O
awake ADJ - O
till ADP - O
around ADV - O
12 NUM - O
/ SYM - O
1 NUM - O
am NOUN - O
so ADV - O
can VERB - O
tell VERB - O
its ADJ - O
a DET - O
side NOUN - O
effect NOUN - O
😳 NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

BACKGROUND NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

Clinical ADJ - O
trials NOUN - O
assessing VERB - O
efficacy NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
safety NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Intramuscular NNP - B-ORG
( -LRB- - I-ORG
IM NNP - I-ORG
) -RRB- - I-ORG
Olanzapine NN - I-ORG
in ADP - O
acute JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
schizophrenia NN - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
acute NN - B-Disease_Symptom
mania NN - I-Disease_Symptom
have VERB - O
previously ADV - O
been VERB - O
undertaken VERB - O
in ADP - O
studies NOUN - O
required VERB - O
for ADP - O
drug NOUN - O
registration NOUN - O
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
who NOUN - O
were VERB - O
required VERB - O
to PART - O
give VERB - O
informed ADJ - O
consent NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
swear VERB - O
geodon NN - B-Drug
just ADV - O
makes VERB - O
me PRON - O
go VB - B-Disease_Symptom
to IN - I-Disease_Symptom
bed NN - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
wake VERB - O
up PART - O
at ADP - O
reasonable ADJ - O
times NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

CONCLUSION NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

The DET - O
effectiveness NOUN - O
of ADP - O
triamcinolone NN - B-Drug
acetonide NOUN - O
ointment NOUN - O
was VERB - O
more ADJ - O
than ADP - O
phenytoin VERB - O
on ADP - O
aphthous JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
ulcers NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
patients NOUN - O
with ADP - O
Behcet NNP - B-ORG
's PART - O
syndrome NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

( PUNCT - O
Modafinil NNP - B-ORG
is VERB - O
like ADP - O
Vyvanse NNP - B-Drug
or CCONJ - O
Adderall NNP - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
it PRON - O
's VERB - O
a DET - O
stimulant NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

Except ADP - O
that ADP - O
it PRON - O
's VERB - O
not ADV - O
addictive ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
makes VERB - O
me PRON - O
extremely ADV - O
more ADV - O
productive JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

METHODS NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O

We PRON - O
further ADV - O
investigated VERB - O
axillary ADJ - O
treatment NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
retrospective ADJ - O
analysis NOUN - O
of ADP - O
28 CD - B-CARDINAL
consecutive ADJ - O
patients NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
aged VERB - O
28 CD - B-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
, PUNCT - O
with ADP - O
operable ADJ - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
a DET - O
clinically ADV - O
clear ADJ - O
axilla NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
treated VERB - O
between IN - B-CARDINAL
28 CD - I-CARDINAL
and CC - I-CARDINAL
28 CD - I-CARDINAL
; SYM - O
28 CD - B-CARDINAL
received VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
28 CD - B-CARDINAL
did VERB - O
not ADV - O
receive VERB - O
axillary ADJ - O
dissection NOUN - O
; PUNCT - O
28 CD - B-CARDINAL
mg NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
day NOUN - O
tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
was VERB - O
prescribed VERB - O
for ADP - O
at RB - B-DATE
least RBS - I-DATE
28 CD - I-DATE
years NNS - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
results NOUN - O
showed VERB - O
that ADP - O
As ADP - O
24 CD - B-CARDINAL
O NUM - O
24 CD - B-CARDINAL
combined VERB - O
with ADP - O
ascorbic ADJ - O
acid NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
ifosfamide NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
prednisone JJ - B-Drug
chemotherapy NOUN - O
may VERB - O
be VERB - O
a DET - O
choice NOUN - O
treatment NOUN - O
for ADP - O
repeatedly ADV - O
relapsed VERB - O
and CCONJ - O
refractory ADJ - O
MM NNS - B-ORG
patients NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Verapamil NNP - B-PERSON
also ADV - O
increased VERB - O
the DET - O
area NOUN - O
under ADP - O
the DET - O
blood NOUN - O
concentration NOUN - O
time NOUN - O
curve NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
the DET - O
gastrointestinal JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
toxicity NN - I-Disease_Symptom
of ADP - O
melphalan NN - B-Drug
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
41 CD - B-CARDINAL
-year PUNCT - O
- PUNCT - O
old ADJ - O
Caucasian JJ - B-NORP
woman NOUN - O
with ADP - O
known VERB - O
Parkinson PROPN - O
's PART - O
disease NOUN - O
was VERB - O
being VERB - O
treated VERB - O
with ADP - O
quetiapine NN - B-Drug
for ADP - O
hallucinations NNS - B-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

In ADP - O
16 CD - B-CARDINAL
insufficient ADJ - O
responders NOUN - O
to ADP - O
previous ADJ - O
ADHD NNP - B-ORG
medications NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
benefit VERB - O
from ADP - O
Ritalin NNP - B-PERSON
( PUNCT - O
) PUNCT - O
LA NNP - B-GPE
was VERB - O
above ADP - O
average ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
effect NOUN - O
duration NOUN - O
was VERB - O
significantly ADV - O
prolonged VERB - O
as ADP - O
compared VERB - O
to ADP - O
pretreatment NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Someone NOUN - O
koppel NOUN - O
citalopram NN - B-Drug
for ADP - O
the DET - O
anxiety NN - B-Disease_Symptom

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

am VERB - O
I PRON - O
going VERB - O
to PART - O
regret VERB - O
taking VERB - O
my ADJ - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
in ADP - O
the DET - O
morning NOUN - O
? PUNCT - O

most ADJ - O
def NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

am VERB - O
I PRON - O
going VERB - O
to PART - O
regret VERB - O
it PRON - O
while ADP - O
I PRON - O
have VERB - O
the DET - O
deepest JJS - B-Disease_Symptom
sleep NN - I-Disease_Symptom
of ADP - O
my ADJ - O
life?no PROPN - O
way NOUN - O
😎 NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
'm VERB - O
awake ADJ - O
wanting VERB - O
to PART - O
take VERB - O
more ADJ - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
because ADP - O
my ADJ - O
legs NOUN - O
hurt VERB - O
. PUNCT - O

Pain NN - B-Disease_Symptom
killing NOUN - O
is VERB - O
not ADV - O
the DET - O
purpose NOUN - O
of ADP - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug

but CCONJ - O
... PUNCT - O
😏 X - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Paxil JJ - B-Drug
withdrawal NOUN - O
update NOUN - O
: PUNCT - O
still ADV - O
on ADP - O
1/2 CD - B-CARDINAL
pill NOUN - O
every DET - O
other ADJ - O
day NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
so ADV - O
sleepy JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
dizzy JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
and CCONJ - O
a DET - O
little ADJ - O
sad JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O

Since ADP - O
I PRON - O
know VERB - O
the DET - O
reason NOUN - O
it PRON - O
's VERB - O
ok ADJ - O
. PUNCT - O

… VERB - O
over ADV - O
soon ADV - O
! PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

A DET - O
secondary ADJ - O
aim NOUN - O
was VERB - O
to PART - O
assess VERB - O
whether ADP - O
Prednisone NNP - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
a DET - O
drug NOUN - O
that ADJ - O
induces VERB - O
insulin NOUN - O
resistance NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
stimulates VERB - O
HCV NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
viral ADJ - O
entry NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
replication NOUN - O
in ADP - O
replicon NOUN - O
culture NOUN - O
systems NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
increases VERB - O
HCV NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
viral ADJ - O
load NOUN - O
in ADP - O
this DET - O
population NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

The DET - O
results NOUN - O
suggested VERB - O
that ADP - O
celecoxib NOUN - O
may VERB - O
hasten VERB - O
the DET - O
onset NOUN - O
of ADP - O
therapeutic ADJ - O
action NOUN - O
of ADP - O
sertraline NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
increase VERB - O
response NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
remission NOUN - O
rate NOUN - O
in ADP - O
depressive JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
disorders NNS - I-Disease_Symptom
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Evaluation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
nasal NOUN - O
symptoms NOUN - O
induced VERB - O
by ADP - O
platelet NOUN - O
activating VERB - O
factor NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
after ADP - O
nasal ADJ - O
challenge NOUN - O
in ADP - O
both CCONJ - O
healthy ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
allergic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
rhinitis NN - I-Disease_Symptom
subjects NOUN - O
pretreated VERB - O
with ADP - O
rupatadine NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
levocetirizine NOUN - O
or CCONJ - O
placebo NOUN - O
in ADP - O
a DET - O
cross VERB - O
- PUNCT - O
over ADJ - O
study NOUN - O
design NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Several ADJ - O
studies NOUN - O
have VERB - O
suggested VERB - O
that ADP - O
antiepileptic ADJ - O
drugs NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
such ADJ - O
as ADP - O
gabapentin NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
lamotrigine NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
may VERB - O
be VERB - O
effective ADJ - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
treatment NOUN - O
of ADP - O
PTSD NNP - B-Disease_Symptom
symptoms NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Mark NNP - B-PERSON
/ SYM - O
peterson NOUN - O
doing VERB - O
well ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
d NOUN - O
/ SYM - O
c'd NOUN - O
the DET - O
trazodone NN - B-Drug
due ADP - O
to ADP - O
cont ADJ - O
tiredness NN - B-Disease_Symptom
in ADP - O
the DT - B-DATE
day NN - I-DATE
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Biweekly PROPN - O
docetaxel NN - B-Drug
, PUNCT - O
cisplatin ADJ - O
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
85 CD - B-CARDINAL
-fluorouracil PUNCT - O

( PUNCT - O
DCF NNP - B-ORG
) PUNCT - O
chemotherapy NOUN - O
for ADP - O
advanced ADJ - O
esophageal JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
squamous JJ - I-Disease_Symptom
cell NN - I-Disease_Symptom
carcinoma NN - I-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
phase NOUN - O
I PRON - O
dose VERB - O
- PUNCT - O
escalation NOUN - O
study NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

[ PUNCT - O
86 NUM - O
, PUNCT - O
86 CD - B-CARDINAL
] PUNCT - O
comparing VERB - O
monotherapy NOUN - O
with ADP - O
valproate NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
lithium NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
or CCONJ - O
carbamazepine VB - B-Drug
in ADP - O
children NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
adolescents NOUN - O
with ADP - O
bipolar JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
disorder NN - I-Disease_Symptom
, PUNCT - O
response NOUN - O
rates NOUN - O
were VERB - O
86 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
, PUNCT - O
86 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
, PUNCT - O
and CCONJ - O
86 CD - B-PERCENT
% NN - I-PERCENT
respectively ADV - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Interestingly ADV - O
, PUNCT - O
systemic ADJ - O
application NOUN - O
of ADP - O
carboplatin ADJ - O
and CCONJ - O
melphalan NN - B-Drug
demonstrated VERB - O
significant ADJ - O
reduction NOUN - O
in ADP - O
the DET - O
tumor NN - B-Disease_Symptom
population NOUN - O
, PUNCT - O
which ADJ - O
could VERB - O
be VERB - O
quantitatively ADV - O
analyzed VERB - O
by ADP - O
the DET - O
estimation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
the DET - O
mean ADJ - O
intensity NOUN - O
of ADP - O
GFP PROPN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Association PROPN - O
of ADP - O
body NOUN - O
composition NOUN - O
with ADP - O
outcome NOUN - O
of ADP - O
docetaxel JJ - B-Drug
chemotherapy NOUN - O
in ADP - O
metastatic JJ - B-Disease_Symptom
prostate NN - I-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
: PUNCT - O
a DET - O
retrospective ADJ - O
review NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Tamoxifen NN - B-Drug
downregulation NOUN - O
of ADP - O
miR NOUN - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
increases VERB - O
2 CD - B-CARDINAL
and CCONJ - O
promotes VERB - O
breast NN - B-Disease_Symptom
cancer NN - I-Disease_Symptom
cell NOUN - O
survival NOUN - O
and CCONJ - O
endocrine NOUN - O
resistance NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

Neurotoxic NNP - B-PERSON
syndrome NOUN - O
developed VERB - O
after ADP - O
taking VERB - O
sertraline NN - B-Drug
and CCONJ - O
risperidone NOUN - O
. PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

I PRON - O
took VERB - O
150 CD - B-QUANTITY
milligrams NNS - I-QUANTITY
of ADP - O
Zoloft NNP - B-GPE
now ADV - O
I PRON - O
have VERB - O
a DET - O
headache NN - B-Disease_Symptom
damn NOUN - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O

What NOUN - O
are VERB - O
the DET - O
Side PROPN - O
Effects NOUN - O
of ADP - O
Tamoxifen NNP - B-Drug
? PUNCT - O

# $ - B-MONEY
BreastCancerAwarenessMonth NN - I-MONEY

# SYM - O
GoPinkDayNg PUNCT - O

-DOCSTART- -X- - O
